["You're Not Gonna Get it" playing]
[music fades]
- [gunfire]
- [soldier] Go! Go! Keep moving!
- [explosion]
- [grunts]
[screaming continues]
[soldier 2] Go! Go! Keep moving!
- [soldiers screaming]
- [breathes heavily]
Mask on, boys, mask on!
[pants]
[soldier] Mask on!
- Where you going? Where you going?
- No, I'm going back.
- Hey. Let me help you. Mask.
- No, I've gotta go back.
Mask! Mask!
- Okay.
- [breathes heavily]
My name's Leo. I'll be right behind you.
Keep forward. Keep forward. Go! Go! Go!
I'll be right behind you.
[soldiers grunting]
- [high-pitched ringing]
- [soldiers grunting]
[soldier 2] Mask on! Mask!
[inhales deeply, coughs]
[soldier 2] Mask on!
[soldier 2 speaks indistinctly] …mask.
[incoming bomb whistling]
[breathes heavily] Where's your mask?
[soldier 3 coughs]
I've been shot.
Take me back. Take me back!
Stop. Stop it, please!
[groaning, muffled screaming]
- [grunting]
- [gasping]
[panting]
[experimental jazz music playing]
[applause]
[speaking French]
[continues speaking French]
Bonne nuit! [chuckles]
[soft music playing]
[Harper] Took me a minute to find you.
Yeah, I...
I left Teenie's as soon as I could.
When did you get back?
Little while ago.
What have you been doing? Just dancing?
Yeah. [chuckles] I was traveling a bit.
I was dancing with a troupe.
We did the Orpheum Circuit.
- Oh, wow.
- [chuckles]
And you? How was it?
Oh, it's, uh... [sighs]
It's not like how they write
- in the papers.
- Hmm.
- They never actually talk to any soldiers.
- [chuckles] Oh, I do.
I hear they just hand out medals
on the ride home.
How many did you get?
I just got the ride. [chuckles]
It sounded... sounded bad over there.
I wrote you.
Uh, when I stopped by Teenie's,
they said that they, um...
They sent my letters on.
I never got any.
Oh.
So tonight,
what did you think my dance was about?
[scoffs] I didn't know it had
to be about anything. [sighs]
[chuckles] It was the story of Josephine,
the first wife of Napoleon.
She's lighting a fire to Osiris.
- She's begging him for a child.
- [mumbles]
I don't know if anybody got that
from what I saw.
[chuckles] Yeah, um...
[both chuckle]
[clears throat]
How long you been doing this?
This is my third run,
but I might book the Balaban.
- [Harper] Really?
- I've, uh, got the numbers just about.
Kind of a small crowd, no?
That's how they like it. They pay more.
I brought you something back.
What makes you think I want it?
Well, you can speak French now,
but I still know you.
[sighs]
[Harper] It's Parisian.
[dancer] What happened here?
Oh, it caught on my pocketknife.
I sewed it though.
[chuckles]
Paris?
When did you get such good taste?
It's fine, but j-just look.
[dancer] We shouldn't be out here.
Harper, I don't do this anymore.
[Harper] Ah, come on. Just look.
You'll know this.
What are they made out of?
Silk?
Nah, rayon.
- No, she's too rich for that.
- No, look. They're running thin.
She wears that pair to church.
A woman doesn't put on silk
to get on her knees.
[chuckles] How do you know her?
You remember Sister Flora
from Saint Michael's?
Yeah. The one who used to try
to baptize us in the lake?
Yeah, yeah. She's, uh...
She's at Saint Adalbert's now.
I bumped into her.
She runs a veteran's dinner
on Wednesdays in the basements.
That's where she's headed tonight.
So, she fed you and you followed her home?
That's how you taught me to do it.
We were kids.
I thought you would've come up
- with something else by now.
- [door closes]
She's out. She's out. Come on. Let's go.
What? Harper, no. [stammers]
I don't need to rob
little old ladies anymore.
Oh, fine. I'll just give
the silk stockings to someone else.
What?
[sighs] Come on.
Oh, my God.
[Harper] What else you got
back there, huh?
What about this one? [sighs]
[Harper] Eh.
Why do they always leave
the little heads on those things anyway?
- It's fashion.
- Oh.
Didn't all the girls
wear things like this in Paris?
Oh, uh, how should I know? Huh?
- Oh. Well, you have eyes, don't you?
- You know what?
I d... Uh, I didn't have time to look, so…
Harp, you always look.
You'd hide under a cattle box
and spy on me.
No, I wasn't spying on you.
Yes. [chuckles]
You were peeping like a little rat.
[grunts]
Is that what you, uh...
Is that what you think I was doing?
- Then what were you doing?
- I was looking out for you.
What?
[beeping]
What's that?
I don't know.
It's coming from over there.
- In here?
- No, here, here.
- Is that...
- Harper.
Hang on. Hang on.
[beeping continues rapidly]
- That's it.
- That it?
Yeah.
What? Let me see that.
- What is that?
- Wait.
- [gasps, exhales sharply]
- [beeping stops]
It's different now.
How'd it do that?
[door closes]
- [gasps] Sh-Shit. L-Let's go.
- Yeah.
- Harper. Someone's coming.
- I'll be right there.
Harper, what are you doing? Let's go.
Right there.
- Where'd you get this?
- [gasps]
Where did you get the watch from?
I know you. Saint Adalbert's.
You never pray before the meal.
No, you don't know me.
You get out! Get out! Get out!
- Get out! Get out!
- Stop! Stop!
- [grunts]
- I just wanna know about the watch.
I just wanna know about the watch.
- I have money. I have money.
- Is it from Europe?
- Huh? Is that where you got it from?
- I... I don't know.
- No, you do know 'cause you hid it good.
- [whimpering]
You know what it is.
You know what it's worth.
Tell me. Where'd you get it?
You could never know.
You're a small man. [grunts]
And you're a fucking bitch.
You think I don't know who you are?
That's your husband's picture
- on your dresser.
- [whimpers]
And you light that same candle
for him every night.
Yeah. [breathing heavily]
Been watching you.
Now, you can't lie to me.
So…
[gasping]
…where'd you get the watch?
What happened up there?
Oh, nothing.
Just ducked under the bed. [sniffs]
Why did you stay behind?
Well, to make sure she didn't spot you.
You got the Balaban coming up.
I didn't want her to ruin that, you know?
[sniffs, breathes heavily]
What?
We used to do this all the time.
Yeah, when there was no one at home.
She could've called the police.
She didn't see me. Look what I got you.
Look. Here. Give me your wrist.
I mean, look at that, huh.
It's made for you.
I'll go and give it back to her,
if that's what you want.
I don't need it. It's hers.
Well, she didn't do anything
to deserve it.
You know, she puts on cheap stockings
to come down
to church and give me her charity.
It's a hustle for God's grace,
and she's gotten way more of that than us.
You know? [chuckles]
We need to take what we're owed.
- [beeps]
- Oh, look.
6:00 a.m. in Paris.
[Leo] Pony up, boys. Pony up.
[players chattering]
All bets down. Bets down.
All bets down. Here we go.
[Leo] Bets down. All bets down.
And watch her spin.
Watch her spin, watch her spin.
- And-and-and-and-and-and…
- [players yell]
Look at that. Who wants to go again? Huh?
- Bets down. Bets down.
- [player] No, no.
That's three out of four for you.
No fucking way that happens.
I don't like losers anyway.
Who wants to spin? Huh?
Harp! You wanna lay down some change here?
You're gonna take
the wrong man's nickel someday.
What's wrong with you, huh?
They hiring today?
Uh, just signed up a few loaders
for Marshall Field's.
Might pull some of us in
for the anchor watch.
- Oh, God.
- What?
- Nah.
- No?
I'll come back tomorrow.
Hey, where you goin'?
I don't know.
Back to the Hopkins, I guess.
How'd it go with your new girl?
She's not new.
She lend you some money?
No. Why?
You're usually the last one left,
not the first one leaving.
Hey, hey, hey. What do you have?
[stammers] Nothing, nothing. Nothing.
It's nothing.
Huh?
[sighs]
There's a spot I heard about.
It's, uh... I might go see what's there.
Where?
It's in Lake View.
Let's run back to the Hopkins first,
grab our kits.
Wha... What do we need the kits for?
Come on. Let's go.
[Leo] Legion. Support your local Legion.
Legion. Support your local Legion.
Legion, ma'am? Support your local Legion?
[passerby] Oh. No, thank you. So, yeah.
- Is this it?
- I guess.
It's not what I thought
it would look like.
- What's it supposed to look like?
- I don't know.
You know what you're doing?
Mm-hmm.
Could be someone home.
Uh, there's an inch
of dust on those shutters.
No one's here.
[clattering]
- Oh, come on, come on.
- [Harper sniffs]
Whose house is this anyways?
I only know the cousin.
She says he travels all over.
He likes to collect nice things.
Hmm.
[crackling, rumbling]
[creaking]
You hear that?
Oh, fuck me. His cousin wasn't lying.
Don't get any ideas.
We're not carrying that thing.
[grunts] Where'd he get this stuff?
All over, I guess.
Who covers up their windows like this?
- What's he so scared of?
- People like us.
[metal items tinkling]
- You sure no one's home?
- Uh, can't be.
They would've heard us by now.
See what they got upstairs.
[clattering]
[Leo] What the fuck?
[thump]
[sniffs]
[clears throat]
Must be a little tight in there.
You all right?
[voice, heavy accent] Your concern
is noted. You can leave now.
There's money in the trunk downstairs.
- Take it and go.
- Oh, well…
that's very generous of you.
Oh. Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Take it easy. Easy, easy, easy.
How much money do you need?
- Wait, what?
- To go.
How much do you want?
You, uh... You tell me.
It's your house. [chuckles]
[sighs] What war did you fight in?
Uh, the... the only war.
The... The Great War.
[stammers] World War One or Two?
- There's a second one?
- So, the first.
And you just returned.
Now, it must be then, what?
1918, nineteen-nine...
It's 1920. Why don't you know that? Huh?
[chuckles]
[machine whirs]
When was the last time you left
this house? Huh?
[breathes shakily]
What month, day is it?
It's, uh... It's October 9th.
I have not been to this day.
What do you mean? You're here right now.
What about the watch?
The watch that you gave Britta. [sighs]
Did you make that?
Is that why you're here?
- You want to know how it's made?
- Well...
- You're a craftsman?
- I mean, I could be.
No. You don't make things.
You just want them.
[grunts]
Here. I buy these at Sydel's.
The one on Wacker.
- [Harper chuckles]
- Now you can leave.
Ah, now why do I feel like
you're buying me off cheap, huh?
Come on.
[soft rock music playing]
[grunting]
[exhales sharply] You take it easy now.
Where you from, huh?
Who are you?
So, you will want it now.
What?
Maybe it's for the better.
I can...
I can find a time to make my own.
You'll see, we can only pass through here.
Until then, the house has its own ways.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- I'm just talking.
- I'm dealing with it.
- Leave him. Let him go. Just...
["Operator (That's Not the Way It Feels)"
playing]
[pants]
- [grunts]
- [children scream]
[song continues]
Sir. Sir, are you okay?
[pedestrian] Someone call an ambulance!
[onlookers murmuring]
- Oh, my God.
- Someone call an ambulance.
[exhaling, inhaling deeply]
Harper?
Harp... [coughing]
Where'd you get that?
I got it off Charlie. [coughs]
Who's Charlie?
Uh, he's a pilot. He's from England.
He flew Bristols, b-but who knows.
[coughs] He sold it to me.
It keeps my chest clear. [coughs]
- Well, doesn't sound like it's helping.
- [coughing]
You know what you need?
- [coughing] I'm fine.
- Lie down on the floor.
- Come here. Come.
- It's my nerves.
I'm auditioning for the Balaban tomorrow.
Radium? This doesn't make it any better.
- You need to get some rest.
- [sighs]
[coughing]
[clearing throat]
Come to my house. You can get ready there.
- [scoffs] Your house? [chuckles]
- Yeah.
- You have a wife now too?
- Not yet.
My lieutenant, it's his brother's place.
He travels all over.
He needs someone
to look after it while he's gone.
And he trusts you with it?
He's got a lot of nice things.
Doesn't mind having a doughboy
guarding them for him.
You've done all of this since last week?
[inhales sharply]
- [coughing, wheezes]
- Lie down, lie down.
- [coughs, breathes heavily]
- Let me get you your breath back.
Come on.
Just wait.
No, you have to keep looking up.
- Yeah, it's fine. [sighs] Why do we...
- Look, there!
[gasps]
- How did you...
- I didn't. It just happened.
[breathes heavily]
Make it change again.
I can't. It just... does it on its own.
I don't know why.
Wait, what is this?
Come on, Harp. How'd you do that?
It's... [sighs]
Inside here… things become something else.
Sometimes they're older,
sometimes they're newer,
sometimes they're just, uh... different.
Stuff I've never even seen before.
It can happen to anything.
Carpets, lamps, whatever.
What?
- Your lieutenant's brother…
- Mmm.
- …what does he do?
- I don't know.
He must be an importer.
Probably where he got all this stuff.
If this place were mine,
I wouldn't leave it to anyone.
Nobody just let you walk in here.
- Well, we're not leaving now.
- [chuckles]
Come on, I want to show you this.
Harp, tell me whose house this is.
Oh, fine. No, you know what, you're right.
We should go. Come on.
Okay.
Think of sometime else. Like, any time.
- Uh... Why?
- Please, just do it.
Just... Just think of a time.
- Like a memory?
- No, like a day, a year.
- Whenever. Go on. Pick one.
- Uh, a thousand years from now.
Well, no, not that far ahead.
Nothing will still be standing by then.
- I don't understand...
- 'Cause you're not listening.
Think of a day, years from now.
Think of what the world could be.
What day do you wanna see?
I wanna go as far from now as possible.
Give me your hand.
- ["Passin' Me By" playing]
- [dancer, laughing] How did you do this?
How did you do this?
- [Harper] I don't know. Just did.
- [laughing]
- Look at that.
- [chuckles]
- We shouldn't be here.
- Why?
It's no different than looking
in someone's window.
Yes, but everything else
is supposed to be here, not us.
Hasn't it always felt like that?
[chuckles]
How did you do this?
Maybe this is who
I was always supposed to be.
[chuckles]
So, you just pick a date
and you walk through the door?
Yeah. It's what's worked so far.
Why can't you go further than today?
I don't know. I just can't.
Wha... Have you tried?
What happens if you try?
I always go back to the first day
I walked in.
- I... I don't know.
- But why's today the last day?
- I don't know.
- Well, what if...
What if the world ends tomorrow
and then we all go back to the beginning?
I mean, does it matter?
Isn't this enough? Look.
[chuckles]
I don't know what this is.
You wanna go back?
No. Not at all.
Maybe... [sighs] Maybe not ever.
We can stay here then. Hmm?
You know my letters?
The guys at Teenie's,
they told me that they gave them to you.
[chuckles] Yeah,
instead of the pay that they owe me.
Why didn't you write me back?
- I didn't know what to say.
- You could've said anything.
I would've wanted
to hear anything from you.
I... [inhales deeply]
I hope you brought cash.
You still owe me silk stockings.
Let's go.
- [laughs] Oh, no.
- I can never tell the difference.
Why doesn't that one have
a little fox head on it?
It doesn't need one.
It's fancy enough already.
- Oh, I see. That's what it is.
- Yes. [chuckles]
Hey.
Where you been?
Oh, just poking around.
I tried to find you,
but I opened the door, nothing happened.
- Oh.
- [Leo inhales deeply]
I was just outside.
Really? Well, it worked for me.
Leo, this is Klara.
Klara from when you were kids?
Yes, that's me.
Mmm.
- I'm gonna put these upstairs.
- Okay, sure, sure.
[smacks lips, exhales sharply]
You showed her?
She needed a place to stay.
- Oh, she's staying here too?
- If she needs to, yes.
I didn't know we were doing that.
Why don't we grab our buckets
and start charging people?
Well, you know what,
she's not "people." All right?
Doesn't matter. I didn't agree to it.
Oh, really, Leo? You know what?
I don't care what you think.
Whoa. When did this start?
We found this place together. It's ours.
Well,
you can't go anywhere with it.
Not without me.
You couldn't even get your mask on
without me.
Where do you think you're going?
[Klara] So, where to next, Captain?
[chuckles] Well, look at you.
- [Klara chuckles]
- Uh…
- I know where. Come on, yeah.
- [chuckles]
Are you coming?
You two go ahead.
Someone better stay, watch the place.
Come on, the best view in the house
is right outside those doors.
Come on, Harp, open your door.
[people cheering, whistling]
["Hard-core Punk" playing]
Hey!
What do you think?
I don't think I could make
any money off this crowd.
I can't believe this is the same place.
You know, the ceilings,
the floors, it's all the same.
I would have thought they could
come up with something new.
- Nobody seems to mind.
- [chuckles]
You want another drink?
Yeah, buy me another.
So can you come back to the same day?
Over and over if you wanted?
Yeah, maybe. I don't see why not.
Hey, what are you guys having?
- Uh... Right.
- Whiskey neat.
- Okay. From the well okay?
- Yeah.
- Those are pretty.
- Sorry, what?
Your earrings, I like them.
Where'd you get them?
Uh, I don't know.
My ex gave them to me the first time
we went out instead of flowers.
At least you got
something decent out of it.
- Thank you.
- You went shopping today.
How did you know?
[chuckles] Do you ever get to dance?
Not while I'm working.
Oh, that's too bad.
What was that all about?
You like her.
I was trying to keep her around for you.
She's not the one I want.
- [song ends]
- [crowd cheers]
["You're Not Gonna Get It" playing]
You sure about that?
Come on. Just one.
- No, I can't.
- Just a quick one. Come on. Let's go.
[chuckling]
- Come on, dance with me.
- Oh, no. Not now.
[sighs] Fine.
[smacks lips] I'm going
to find the powder room,
but when I'm back, you be ready.
They don't call it that anymore.
It's just a toilet.
Fine. Just the toilet. I'll be right back.
[punk rock music playing]
- Hey!
- [chuckles]
You really like the sound of this, huh?
[chuckles]
I always thought I couldn't dance.
But it was just, uh, the wrong music.
- [chuckles]
- Yeah.
Well, we'll see how you feel tomorrow.
Yeah, well, I won't be feeling it alone.
Ah. Oh, is this what the girls
in Paris were like?
- Huh?
- When you went with Harp.
[chuckles] He must've had a French girl.
- Uh, he only talked about you.
- [chuckles]
Well, what happened over there?
He's different.
Different how?
He takes up space more.
Just doesn't know what to do with it yet.
- Maybe he got taller.
- [grunts]
[breathes heavily] Uh... I c... can't say.
I never knew him before.
Hmm. But you were with him.
I... I don't think he became
someone he wasn't already.
Maybe you just didn't know him
as well as you thought you did.
We never made it to Paris,
if that's what he told you.
Oh, there you are.
I've been looking for you.
[Klara] Mmm.
Uh, let's go.
What's under my coat?
Oh, uh... That's for later.
Let's go.
What about Leo?
I don't think he's planning
on coming home with us. Come on.
- [clicking]
- [Klara] Know how to work that thing?
[Harper] I'm getting there. [chuckles]
How'd you swipe it?
[inhales deeply] I paid for it.
You don't have to steal
when you have money.
[Klara] Sure.
- Oh, no, Harper, I'm gonna put it back up.
- No.
- It's gonna get this shit all over it.
- No, leave it down.
There. You can wash it out.
- [clears throat]
- There.
- This isn't how I do my act.
- No, it'll look better. You ready?
Yeah. Yeah.
Come on.
Let's see.
- All right, get going.
- [exhales deeply]
- [speaks French]
- No, no, not like that.
Like Teenie's. Just be you. No French.
Why? Does it remind you too much of Paris?
Well, yeah, maybe it does.
Ready?
I know you didn't make it there.
Leo said so.
He doesn't know where I've been.
Now, the camera's rolling.
Are you gonna start or not?
[smacks lips] No, I'm not.
Turn... Turn it off.
[clicking]
Tell me where you got this.
I know it wasn't in Paris.
[smacks lips] I, uh...
I took it off someone who died.
He didn't have anyone to give it to,
and I did.
Okay, fine. Just don't lie to me.
[sighs]
So what happens when you sleep here?
Does... You wake up still the same?
- I think so.
- [chuckles]
You know, when... when I found this place…
you were the only one I wanted
to show it to.
Harper. [sighs] Shit,
- I'm getting this all over the place.
- No, sheets don't matter.
- Let's turn the camera back on…
- Take it easy.
- …and do it again.
- Just come sit back down.
- No, I'm ready.
- Just get back over here.
- Get back here!
- Harper, no!
- Come here. Just...
- Harper, what's wrong with you?
- Harper, no!
- Come over here.
Just get back over here! You always do!
[clears throat]
What do you mean "always"?
- I didn't...
- Harper!
Have we done this before?
- Done what?
- [breathes shakily]
Have we come back to today, to tonight?
To all of this?
[breathes shakily] How many times?
What does it matter? It doesn't matter.
How do you do this?
I walk out the back door,
and I... I come and find you.
[chuckles] We go out,
then we... we come home.
And we always just end up here.
Why don't I remember?
Because it's not your house.
Klara, wait. Wait. [stammers] It's late.
- Please. Please just stay, please!
- Get off me.
[breathes heavily] You can come back
as many times as you want.
I'll always know, Harper,
because I know you.
You watched me. I watched you.
You weren't much back then.
Now all of this,
it makes you look even smaller.
[grunts, gasps]
[whimpers] Harper! [breathes heavily]
No, no, no! No, no, no. No!
- [grunts]
- Get off me! No. [grunts]
[Harper shouts]
[Klara sobs, whimpers]
One, two, three, down. [grunts]
[panting]
Ready.
One, two, three. [grunts, panting]
[Leo grunts, pants]
Look, we're both still on our feet, huh?
[grunts, sighs]
Saw you out there. Knew you'd make it.
How'd you see anything?
There was smoke everywhere.
It's... It's Leo, right?
[grunts]
He was with your company?
Yeah. Yeah.
[Leo] They'll want your account
to send to his family.
Figure out something to say.
You might want to leave that with him.
That's his mask, right?
I told you I'd be right behind you.
["Ballad of the Absent Mare" playing]
[song continues]
[sighs]
Do you want something? It's last call.
- Same as last time.
- And that is…
Whiskey neat.
Those earrings are pretty.
Yeah, you like 'em?
You let me hold 'em,
I can tell you where they're from.
And if I'm wrong, this is yours.
If you're trying to steal them,
they're not worth anything.
I'll give them back. Come on.
[chuckles]
Let's see. All right, all right.
Well, not too old.
- Two, maybe three years.
- Hmm.
A man bought them for you.
But they're not nice enough for you two
to have been together long.
So, maybe a gag gift on a first date.
Nope, I picked them out for myself.
They're from the dollar store.
You can keep 'em.
I wasn't wrong.
I guess we'll never know.
[bottles clattering]