["Let the River Run" playing]
[alarm clock ringing]
[Charlie grunts]
Aw, look at you.
[Sylvia chuckles]
I am so proud of you, baby.
- You are gonna knock it out of the park.
- Mmm. Thanks, boo.
[exclaims]
[Charlie] Hey. Doesn't Mom look good?
Okay. [chuckles]
I am so proud of you, babe.
- You are gonna knock it out of the park.
- Aw. Thank you, baby.
Two hands, Simon! Two hands.
Thank you. Sorry, didn't mean...
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Oh, hi, hi, hi.
- Oh, hi.
- Okay. Bye, guys. Bye.
- Have a good day.
Bye, sweetie. [kisses]
- Dang, LA Law! You look good!
- Mmm.
- Give me a turn. Give me a t...
Yeah. [chuckles]
[both squeal]
- I'm really nervous. Is that silly?
- No! This is a really big deal.
I'm, like... I can't wait
to just have coworkers again, you know?
Like, inside jokes.
- Yeah, like, going to lunch.
- Like camaraderie, you know?
- Watercooler talk.
- Yeah. Mmm.
- Not having only me to talk to.
- No! No, but you know what I mean.
- Yeah. Uh-huh.
- This is the moment I've been dreaming of.
- Okay. [chuckles]
- Hi. Angie, Angie!
- [Angie] Mmm.
- So sorry. Um, just quickly.
- I won't be at pickup today…
- Mmm.
…so my mother-in-law is gonna pick up
Maeve today. Yes. I'm actually going...
- I'm going back to work today, so...
- Okay. Thanks, Sylvia.
Yeah. Thanks.
Yeah, you told... I mean, now she knows.
- She didn't know. I've been so busy…
- Yeah, yeah. She needs...
- You had to tell her. Right.
- …and sh... I... Clearly.
- What should we go do now?
- I gotta go to work.
- Shit.
- [Sylvia] Yeah.
[bell rings]
["She Works Hard for the Money" playing]
I'm just saying I have concerns.
- Like what?
- Hey, no knock on Sylvia.
She's a dynamo.
But she's gonna be working
as an associate.
Those people are in their 20s.
Sylvia has more energy than anyone I know.
She will be fine.
She doesn't have twentysomething energy.
None of us do anymore.
- Oh, don't be ridiculous.
- [sighs]
Daniels, get in here.
- How late were you here last night?
- Uh, until 2:00.
- So you left early?
- I kept working from home.
- Are you on Adderall?
- No.
- Yes.
- Never admit that to the State Board.
- See?
- Yeah. I see.
- What are you still doing here?
- Sorry.
Great kid.
Sylvia will be fine.
If you say so.
[hip-hop music playing]
What are you doing?
You'll see soon enough, Omar.
That's not really an answer.
I'm making a new beer.
The fuck do you think I'm doing?
I have been working nonstop, gentlemen.
And I present a blackberry sour
with the complexity of an IPA.
Most people don't try this kind of thing
'cause honestly,
usually this tastes pretty fucking weird,
but I think I figured it out.
Enjoy.
- [both] Mmm.
- Oh, this is good as fuck. Goddamn.
- [Will] Right?
- That's the shit right there.
- Right.
- How fast can you scale this up?
- I can in a few weeks.
How many barrels?
Best part. Twenty-four bottles per month.
- What? That's it?
- Okay. Twenty-four? Uh.
Yes. It is not easy to produce,
and the ingredients are not cheap.
But think of this.
We market it as a limited edition beer.
It will sell out
instantaneously every time.
People will clamor for it.
There'll be legends about it.
Will, how much are the ingredients?
- This bottle cost $60 to produce.
- [whistles]
What the fuck are you talking about?
That's $60 a beer. Stop drinking it.
- That's $60 a beer.
- Mmm.
- What's in it, diamonds?
- [Omar] Whoa. Come on, guys.
You can't drink diamonds.
It'll cut up your guts.
Okay, how much are you trying
to sell this shit for, Will?
We sell it
for five or six dollars a bottle.
- [mutters]
- [stammering] You're killing me.
People will write about it.
We will win awards.
This will bring prestige to the bar.
[chuckling] Prestige? I don't...
I'm looking for money, man.
[Will] We'll make money eventually.
Think of this as, like, spending money
on advertising, you know?
Dude, I got it. I got it.
We'll make the beer, and then
we'll sell it for a $100 a bottle.
- I'm not mad at that.
- [Will] No!
- Come on. No.
- You may never know.
It's like a luxury item.
-You made a fucking sick ass beer,
-Right.
and the customers are gonna like it.
Put luxury prices on it.
Think about it. It's like Cristal, dawg.
It's our Cristal, player.
No, that takes something cool,
and it makes it a gimmick.
Like one of those fucking
Salt Bae cheeseburgers or some shit.
Okay. Dude, this is what we'll do.
We'll try it for a month. If the customers
don't like it, we do my way.
We can try my way?
- For a month, dawg.
- I'm down.
Thank you. Yes! You won't regret this.
People are gonna lose their fucking shit
over this stuff, okay?
Dude, you killed it with this shit, man.
- For real.
- Thank you.
You, like, been grinding
for a long time for us, man.
I... I just wanna tell you,
as the investor of this place,
you should take a day off
'cause this is wild.
- Really?
- Yeah, bro.
- Seriously. In celebration.
- [Will] Okay. Thank you. Great.
- I have a barley shipment coming later.
- I've got that, man.
- Seriously, thanks.
- [Will] Okay.
- [Andy] Good stuff, Will.
- Thank you.
- [Reggie] Appreciate you.
- [Andy] Good work, bro.
- It was really good.
- Can I try it?
It is too expensive for you to try.
[chuckles] You funny as fuck, dawg.
So, the merger and acquisition group
is on the south end of the 11th floor.
Mm-hmm.
We have the best art
because Friedkin collects.
- [Sylvia] Oh, gorgeous.
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Uh, the associates
are gonna be down that way,
and all the partners have the offices
with windows.
Copy.
You'll mostly be working for Stern,
but any partner who puts you on anything,
- you just say yes. Okay.
- Mm-hmm. Copy.
- Oh.
- Oh! Oh, it's... It's, uh... It's Kirk.
- Yeah. He...
- Is it Kirk? Hi. Kirk, hi!
- Hi, Kirk!
- [colleague] Oh.
- It's Sylvia. Charlie's wife.
- Okay.
- Charlie Greeves's wife.
- [mouths] On the phone.
It's my first day. [chuckles] Hi!
- Okay, no. Don't talk to Kirk Friedkin.
- Oh, but I know him.
No, you don't. Okay?
- No, but I do.
- No, you don't. No, no. Just, no.
So right here
are where all the associates sit.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, everyone.
- Everyone, this is our new associate…
- [Sylvia chuckles]
…Sylvia Greeves.
- Oh, hi. Hi. Hi.
- [employees] Hi.
Wait, you're an associate?
Yes. I've-I've been out of the game
for a little bit.
[employees chuckle]
Go about your business, kids. [chuckles]
- Okay. Uh, you are actually right in here.
- Oh. Good.
That's your office. Yeah. Mm-hmm.
- So, this is your new home away from home.
- Oh.
Let me know
if you have any questions, okay?
- Thank you. Okay.
- Okay. Of course.
- [phone beeps]
- [squeaks]
- [knock on door]
- Hi.
Hey. I'm Josh Stern, junior partner
on the Starr Kibble and Suet Sweets M&A.
- Sylvia Greeves. Yes.
- I'm excited to have you on the team.
Nice to meet you. Live close by?
Did you... Oh.
So let's start here. Just get up to speed,
and Levinson can fill you in
on any questions you have over lunch.
- Great. Thank you.
- All right.
- Yeah. I'll have this back to you pronto.
- Yeah.
[clears throat]
[sighs]
There we go. Okay.
- Hi. Thanks.
- Hey.
Hi. Sylvia. Nice to meet you.
Oh, thank you.
Hi. Sylvia. Oh, thank you. Oh.
Okay. What is it?
So he sends me this text that's like,
"How are you?"
- What's wrong with that?
- [laughing]
It's weird. I mean, don't put it on me
to tell you about my whole week
- when I only met you once.
- Oh, come on.
You have a million friends in common.
It's not like he's sending you a dick pic.
He just wants to say hi.
Adam, it sounds like
you wanna say hi to Britney.
- [Adam chuckles] Oh.
- I know.
For the record, Britney,
I like you but as a friend.
- With benefits. [laughs]
- Aw. [laughs]
I'm feeling some kind of chemistry, and I
don't know what's going on. [chuckles]
Okay. So, uh, Adam, where would you
like to take Britney on a first date?
- [gasps] To the beach, 'cause it's free.
- [chuckles]
- [laughing]
- On a time machine to date number three.
Three is the lucky number.
Dude, in law school,
- Adam asked out our torts professor.
- Dude.
- And how did that work out for him?
- Same way it always does, wipe out.
- [chuckles]
- [laughs] Okay. That was funny.
I bet Adam masturbates in the bathroom.
What?
What did you just say?
- I was just riffing with you guys. Just...
- I... I don't do that.
- Yeah. I know th... I know that.
- Who are you?
I'm Sylvia.
- Is she a temp?
- No, I'm a associate.
I was just part of the group, and I...
I just joined. I met you this morning.
Why would you say I masturbate
in the bathroom? You don't even know me.
Yeah. It's, uh... It's, like,
an expression in Australia.
"Masturbate in the bathroom,"
means, like, you know...
It's, like, you have money, you know?
And you're... you've... you're...
like, into...
You're laid-back. And just...
[in Australian accent] I've never
heard that. I don't think that's true.
No, no, i... Uh... Oh, g'day. [chuckles]
Um, you didn't hear that?
- No.
- It's true.
- Yeah, yeah. It's true.
- Can you use it in a sentence?
- Yeah, yeah. It's, like, um,
"I... You know, I was...
I masturbated in the bathroom,
and he-he gave me back my money."
Okay.
[cell phone ringing]
- Hi, babe.
- [Charlie] Hey, babe.
Hey. How you doing?
Uh, g-good. How are you?
More importantly,
how are they treating you?
Good.
- Uh, yeah, they threw me in the deep end…
- Mm-hmm.
…but it's nothing I can't handle.
I just forgot how much work work is.
- Do you like the other associates?
- Pretty much. Um, I don't know.
Young people are so sensitive these days.
Like, we were all joking around,
and I think I offended this guy.
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
That's the point. I mean,
what does it matter what I said, right?
I could've said, "You have kind eyes,"
and I would've been canceled, so…
Yeah, he sounds like a handful.
Oh, it's fine.
I have to go. I have a lot of work.
It's nice having to say it.
- Thank you.
- Yep. Bye. Love you.
[sighs]
[associates chattering]
[yawns]
Can we, uh... Can we go home now?
Oh, uh, the partners leave now,
but the associates stay a little later.
Oh.
You can totally go home if you have
to take care of your kids though.
Oh, no. No, I'm good.
I'm... I'm in the zone.
I'm just grinding through, and I'll grab
some granola bars for dinner.
There are some in the back
that have protein.
Oh.
She was right. It's, um...
It's not an expression.
The other Aussie girl, she was right.
- Yeah, no shit.
- Yeah.
- [partner] Thank you.
- Yeah, of course.
[yawns]
[copier whirring]
Oh!
- [Levinson] Hey, you okay?
- Yeah. I just...
Stretching a little bit.
I'm so stiff from the chair.
Oh, okay. Yeah, no, I get it. Um, okay.
- Yeah. You good?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- You sure you're okay? Cool.
- Okay. Yeah, thank you.
Thanks. [yawns]
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck. Fuck!
God, no! [groans]
Oh, my God.
I really thought I fixed it. Ugh.
[line ringing]
- [Will] What up?
- Hey. Hey, I, uh, uh...
I'm at the office.
Would you mind coming here?
I've just messed up so bad. [sighs]
'Kay, 'kay, 'kay. [stammers]
- Careful, careful, careful.
- Okay. I'm doing it.
- Just concentrate.
- Just...
Your vibe is making this hard, okay?
Just chill out.
- I'm going in.
- [Sylvia] Okay.
- That's the wrong color.
- Hmm.
It's the color of his shirt.
- I...
- It looks worse.
- I don't know what to tell you.
- He look...
You gave me fucking Wite-Out.
- He just looks like he's doing coke.
- Does look like he's doing coke.
- [Sylvia] Ugh.
- Looks like he did too much coke,
- got a nosebleed, fell, cut his face open.
- Okay.
Look, I'm gonna smear it together.
Red and white will make pink.
- The color of this Caucasian man's skin.
- Okay. All right. Okay.
Here we go.
- Ooh, that is... Okay, that's worse.
- Worse. Just stop it, just stop it.
I don't know what the fuck you want
from me. This is your fault.
Who falls asleep standing up?
- What are you, a fucking camel?
- I'm exhausted!
Take nap! Drink a macchiato! There's
gotta be a Keurig in this motherfucker.
Too much coffee makes me tired.
- Coffee does not make you tired.
- It does!
You always say it makes you tired.
That's not true!
- It is for me.
- Well,
I don't know what to tell you.
This is bad.
- You dragged me into this shit!
- I'm gonna get fired.
I'm gonna lose a job I've had for one day.
[chuckles]
Okay. I know how to fix this,
but you're not gonna like it.
- What? How are you gonna do it?
- Audrey.
Audrey? She's a useless hipster.
She's an art "consultant."
We need a maverick. A wild man. A genius.
- We need someone who can fix it.
- She knows a lot of people, okay?
She can fix this.
- Do you want her help or not?
- Yes. Are you guys talking?
- Yeah. You know. Re-Rebuilding bridges.
- Oh. Oh.
- You fucking?
- No! Do you want me to...
- Do you want her help or not?
- Sure. Sure. Okay, fine. Yes, sure.
[sighs] Good Lord.
- This is a nice neighborhood.
- Yeah.
- Must be a good school district.
- [scoffs] Don't be a snob.
There's a guy that sells lobster rolls
out of his apartment over there.
- Oh. Why?
- They're good. There's a waiting list.
Oh. Well, now I want one.
See? If you ever find yourself
in a Liam Neeson Taken scenario,
- come here.
- [car horn honking]
Oh, my. Audrey has a Porsche now?
Since we got divorced,
her life just gets better and better.
She looks like Daniel Craig.
The villain in a Fast and Furious movie.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How's it going?
- Wow.
- It's great.
- You look incredible.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much, Audrey.
- You're such a lifesaver. Thank you.
- Sylvia. Aw. Yeah, of course. [sighs]
So, what kind of art restorer
works at midnight?
Well, Gregory is super talented.
He just hasn't broken through yet,
so he restores paintings.
And even then, only as a favor.
Um, guess what I'm saying is
he can be a bit prickly.
Oh, duly noted.
Also, he goes by Lord Rotero.
- Oh, of course he does.
- [doorbell buzzes]
- [Lord Rotero] Yeah.
- [Audrey] Hi, it's me.
You know, given Lord Rotero's disposition,
maybe Sylvia
should stay out here and chill?
- Yes.
- Yeah. Maybe just chill out here.
What are you talking about?
This is my thing.
Look, I don't know how to say this
in a way that's not insulting.
I'm worried you're not cool enough.
You're gonna fuck this up.
And somebody with the name Lord Rotero
is considered cool?
- Oh, yes. S-Super cool. Very cool.
- Yes. Very.
- You know that I'm cool.
- Right now, you just...
- You don't look that cool.
- I'm cool.
- Okay, you're cool.
- You know what? I fit in anywhere.
- You're right. Super cool.
- He's gonna love me.
Do you wanna put the top
on your Porsche up?
- Why would I do that?
- Good question, you know.
[Will] Wow. Oh, this is fucking cool.
- Don't touch anything. Set it there.
- Wow. Amazing. Yeah.
Awesome. Wow.
[Audrey] Lord Rotero. Hello!
- [groans] You look good.
- Oh.
[speaks indistinctly] All right,
let's see what we dealing with.
- [Lord Rotero sighs] Wow.
- [Audrey] Mmm.
My expectations were low, but this
is a real piece of corporate crap.
- Hmm.
- Only thing I like about it is the damage.
- I did the Wite-Out. So, yeah, thanks.
- Mmm. [chuckles]
So, uh, do you think you can help us?
[inhales sharply] Yeah. I know
the exact vibe of this type of thing.
When I was starting out,
I painted a mural in a lobby
of this fancy accounting firm
on the millionth floor in Century City.
[chuckles] Made me physically ill.
[Audrey] Of course it did. Your body
was rejecting the corporate poison.
I totally feel you.
My business partners are always pushing
this fucking corporate agenda
and it sucks. So, yeah, man. I'm with you.
- My man.
[Rotero] My man.
- How much time do you think you'll need?
- About five hours.
- [mouthing words] Five hours.
- One hour to paint the man's face.
Then four hours to take the humanity
out of him, so he looks like a lawyer.
[all laughing]
[Rotero] Now that I'm looking at this,
I'm thinking, uh,
maybe I don't copy it exactly.
Maybe I make something
that's commenting on this painting.
An original Lord Rotero? [gasps]
Oh, my God. Yes! Yes!
I'm thinking maybe I'll recreate it
but have his hands holding cash
or put him in a MAGA hat.
That's fucking dope.
Maybe his teeth are bullets.
- Koalas.
- Well, I think that that-that sounds great
to hang in a gallery,
all due respect, but this, we just really
wanna replicate the painting. That's it.
This could be kicking it up a notch.
I saw this Kusama retrospective in Tokyo.
We could do an infinity room
with LED lights,
but just zoom in
right on this motherfucker's f...
- Face! My man.
- Yes, my man.
- I have a great lighting source...
- No! Guys!
- Yeah? Okay.
- Guys! Please, this is serious!
We just gotta make
his face look like his face!
I-I-I don't wanna lose my job.
That's why we're here.
Please just make his face
look like his face again. That's it.
She a narc.
I think you both should just wait outside.
- Should we take it?
- Leave the painting. Just go outside.
I'm sorry. Audrey's smile just set me off.
She's just so condescending.
Yeah,
her smile is what made that go wrong.
Is this gonna be okay?
- What am I gonna do?
- I don't know if it'll be okay.
You did everything in your power
to make that not okay.
You weren't much help!
I wanted a Lord Rotero original.
That's shit's worth fucking cash, yo!
I'm not cool. I'm sorry.
- You're right.
- You're not.
Not in this specific context,
but in some other contexts,
- you know, I am considered pretty cool.
- Hmm.
Okay. I settled him down,
and he's gonna do it.
- What did you do?
- It doesn't matter.
Wait, how did you do that?
- I didn't fuck him. Jesus.
- Hey, I wasn't suggesting you did it.
If you did, that's your prerogative.
Thank you.
By the way, can you tell Reggie
that I'm sorry
- but I won't make it to the party tonight?
- What party?
- Oh, shit. You don't know, do you?
[sighs] My brother can be
such an asshole sometimes.
Stepbrother. Ew. What party?
[hip-hop music playing]
What the fuck is going on here, man?
We're starting a hard kombucha line
called Daa Booch, probably.
- Still workshopping that.
- "We"?
- Reggie and I are.
- Cool.
I do not understand
why the fuck you would do something
like this without telling me, man.
Why wouldn't you cut me into this?
Hard kombucha's not your area
of expertise.
It is nobody's area of expertise
because it's stupid.
Gut health for people
who like to get fucked up?
- Those are two different crowds, okay?
- True.
Also, I have a degree
in fermentation science.
If this is anyone's area, it's mine.
Yo, Will, what's up? You look good.
- Oh, great. Omar's here. Fantastic.
- Of course I'm here.
Wouldn't be very professional of me
to miss my own launch party. [chuckles]
- You brought him in?
- [Omar] Hey.
What can I say? I love all fermentation.
- Omar. Omar. Omar.
- [Omar] Unlike some people.
Specifically you.
- Take a walk.
- Yep.
Look, I am very sorry
you found out this way, okay? I am.
This is shitty. But I promise you, dude,
it's just business, okay?
- It ain't nothing personal.
- It feels very personal.
Okay. Well, it's not, Will.
However, if it was,
maybe it's because you shit on every
opportunity that comes our way, okay?
You're only excited
about some fucking limited edition beer
that no one's gonna care
about except for beer snobs.
You said you liked it.
Of course I did! You're an artist.
That's not the point.
We'd lose $40 a bottle, Will.
That's fucking insane. I don't know
what you're trying to do anymore.
I'm just trying to make good beer.
Unlike Reggie, who's trying to turn
this place into a fucking EDM Hooters.
Reggie's not that bad, bruh.
[Reggie] The devil wears Boochy, baby.
[all cheering]
Okay. Okay.
He is the worst, but that little shit
knows how to make money,
and that's all this is about.
It's just money, okay?
- Hey, babe. We need more cold Booch.
- Hey, baby. Okay.
- We'll get Booch. We'll get you some.
- [Katie] Okay.
Katie?
[gasps] Hi!
What in... What are you doing here?
- Uh, um…
- Are you guys together?
I mean, I don't know. I guess ask him.
I don't know either.
It just feels really good.
- It feels so good.
- So fucking good.
How did this happen?
- Pheromones. [chuckles]
- [chuckles] Good one.
- I'm having sex again.
- Okay. Okay. I get it.
You wanna try Daa Booch?
What the fuck are you doing here?
She's my pal. I told you that.
You don't listen.
Yeah, and I needed a job,
since I'm no longer babysitting.
- And you broke up with me on my birthday.
- Oh, that's messed up.
- [Katie] Wow.
- Kids miss you. They really do.
Yeah,
we should do a... We'll do a FaceTime.
Yeah! I miss them!
[sighs] So cute.
What is happening right now?
[stammers] I can't believe
they would do this to me.
And… [stammers] …in my own bar?
- I can't believe they would do this to us.
- What do you mean "us"?
I mean your business partners not telling
you about a new project.
My best friend started
a new relationship without telling me.
Not the same thing.
Yeah. I'm sorry. You're right.
You're right.
That sucks. I'm sorry. I get it.
- Don't worry. I took care of it.
- What do you mean?
It's taken care of.
What's that?
[fireman] Everyone out right now!
Pronto! Pronto!
- What did you do?
- [alarm wailing]
There was a gas leak.
- You called in a fucking gas leak?
- I'm a good citizen. What can I say?
- Holy fuck.
- [Sylvia chuckles]
- You're a good friend.
- I... Yes. Yes, I am.
Let's go now! Gas leak!
This whole place could explode!
- [Will] Oh, no.
- [Sylvia] No.
[exhales deeply]
So, yeah.
A lot of those ideas
we were talking about were
pretty derivative takes on capitalism.
So, um, I just did what you wanted,
with one tiny tweak.
The tweak being
you put a dick on his nose?
- You see it?
- I do.
Where are the balls?
Mmm.
[groans]
- G'day.
- [inhales sharply] G'day.
All right. Stern, why don't you
give us an update on Dobson?
Uh, yes. Okay.
Uh, first of all, we need to make sure
that we are all on the same page
about the arbitration provision
in section 7.5 H.
Uh, specifically whether,
in the event of a disagreement
about whether an amendment to
the company disclosure is, uh, required.
Any dispute will be governed
by an arbitrator
with eight or, uh, ten years of experience
in complex merger transactions.
And we've, uh…
- [mouthing] Sorry.
- …heard from the due diligence team…
Hey. Uh, Jessica from HR
is looking for you.
- Oh, uh, what about?
- Uh-oh.
Hey, have you seen
the dick-face painting? [chuckles]
[associates chuckling] Did you see that?
Oh, no. What? That's huge.
Oh, hi. Hi.
- [chuckles] You wanted to see me?
- [Jessica] Mm-hmm.
Everything's been going so well.
Everyone's been so welcoming and...
Did we talk about my children's lizard
having almost exactly
the same name as you?
Jessipa. [chuckles]
Um, Sylvia,
do you have any idea what happened
to the portrait of Mr. Friedkin
that was hanging outside the copy room?
Ooh. That's a lovely painting,
by the way. Gorgeous.
It's lovely colors, and the composition...
So, do you have any idea
what happened to it?
No. What happened to it?
[chuckles] Well…
Just very weird prank, I have to say.
I...
It's...
That's impossible. That-That can't be me.
It's literally you.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I just... I c... [sighs]
I was... I was so tired, and I just fell
into the painting, and it just crashed.
And then I went to this place to try
to fix it, and they couldn't help me.
And then I was... I was desperately
trying to bring it back in,
and I've just been so tired, you know?
Like, the work is so much harder
at my age. And I'm just, like...
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I totally screwed up, and I just...
- I'm so sorry.
- I get it. [chuckles] You know?
Sylvia, I... I get it. [sighs]
It can be really intimidating
around here, you know?
I remember, when I first started,
I felt the same way,
and I'm actually a mom too, so...
- You are?
- Yeah. I'm...
- I mean, it was unintentional, Jessica.
- Yeah.
It really was. It was the last thing
I was trying to do.
- I am horrified.
- It's all right. You know what?
- Water under the bridge. Okay?
- Okay.
- Let's hug it out. Okay?
- Yes! Oh.
- Sylvia. Thanks for coming in.
- Oh, my goodness. I am so fond of you.
- You've been terrific. Thank you so much.
- Aw. All right.
- Whew. Phew! [chuckles]
- [Jessica chuckles]
- Leave it open?
- You can leave it open.
- Okay.
- That's all right. Thank you.
- What are you doing here?
- Hey, you.
Uh, just working on that contract
for Levinson. You know how he is.
No. You were fired. Y-You have to go.
I... But we just had that conversation
where you were, like...
What? I can't be fired.
I've only been here for a day. I...
I've been waiting for this for 13 years.
I mean, it can't be over that quickly.
[chuckles]
- [Jessica] I don't know what to tell you.
- Well, just tell me that I can stay.
Or don't tell me anything
and just continue on to the kitchen
or wherever you were going. [chuckles]
Please, please, please, Jessica.
Please let me stay.
I'm gonna stay. I'll stay.
- Listen.
- I'm gonna stay.
Sylvia, it's not up to me, okay?
But you know what?
Feel free to take it up with Kirk.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
[sighs] Don't worry about it.
Okay. That's what I thought.
- All right. Well, it won't take me long.
- Great.
- You're gonna stay there the whole time?
- I am.
- [sighs] I see what you're doing.
- Hmm?
You're moving slowly. It's not funny.
[scoffs]
This is so childish.
[sighs]
[sighs] Proud of yourself?
- [Sylvia grunts]
- You know...
Just leave, please.
Okay. Okay. You know what?
I'm gonna have to call security.
Um… [clears throat] …Jesus Christ.
["You Gotta Be" playing]