Well, the race is on to save a young,
British Asian man, Hassan Ahmed, who has been kidnapped by members of a far right group calling themselves the Sons of Albion.
- The kidnappers have made no demands…
- Jesus.
…and it appears the
authorities are no closer… - Shit. - …to discovering his whereabouts.
- So bleak.
- Yeah.
I mean, we're behind the scenes, and
we know nothing. [BREATHES DEEPLY]
Well, we know the bastards
are gonna kill him.
- Yeah, because they haven't made...
- Made any demands, yeah.
how and, indeed,
why he was targeted beyond his ethnic background.
Do you think Lamb
knows what's going on?
Well, I'm sure he could
find out if he wanted to.
I'm not sure he cares.
You know, Lamb's
password is "password."
- "Password"?
- Mm-hmm.
- How do you know?
- Ho told me.
- And what did that cost you?
- Nothing. [CHUCKLES]
He just wanted to tell someone,
didn't he? To prove how clever he is.
[TV CONTINUES, INDISTINCT]
How much do you think the
Park's gonna be telling Lamb?
I mean, we could find out.
He's bound to be copied in
on updates for live ops.
[LOUISA] Mmm.
But... probably shouldn't.
Um, do you want another drink?
Yeah, maybe.
Or... [INHALES DEEPLY] I don't
know. Maybe back to the office.
[MIN] Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Okay. Well,
I mean, it's better than getting pissed here, isn't it?
- Not helping, are we?
- Exactly. No.
- Yeah.
- Last order at the bar, guys.
Okay, thanks. Another drink?
Okay, but something
quick. Shots.
[LAUGHING, CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY] - [LOUISA] Oh, my God. I don't know... - Can you hurry up?
- Can I just do it?
- Here.
- 'Cause it's really painful to watch.
- Go on.
- All right. Are you ready?
- Yeah.
- Want to see my technique in action?
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Okay. [EXHALES]
- [LOUISA LAUGHS]
- Ow. Arse.
- You have to turn the handle at the same...
- Shh!
How have you still not learned
how to open the fricking door?
- But that was smooth.
- Uh-huh.
- That was smooth as you like.
- According to who?
What? Me. That was cool. Cool
as a cucumber. All right, shush.
- Try and be quiet.
- No, you sh...
[MIN] Try, if you can.
[LOUISA CHUCKLING] I can't see.
[MIN] Right, turn that w...
- Let me get the light.
- [BOTH LAUGHING]
[THUDDING]
Sorry. Uh, am I
not doing it right?
- I haven't... It's been a while.
- Did you hear that?
Hear what?
I don't know. A noise.
Like a mouse?
Do we have mice?
Yeah. Yeah, we've
got lots of mice.
Or something that does mouse
droppings around the place.
- Shut up.
- Ho.
[BOTH LAUGH]
- [SCRAPING, BANGING]
- [MIN] Okay, I heard that.
[WHISPERING] I think it was Lamb's
office. Sounded like Lamb's office.
[LOUISA] I don't know.
There's no lights on.
[WHISPERING] Wait. Are
you sure we wanna do this?
[WHISPERING] What else
should we be doing?
Well, I mean, I'd rather be
doing what we were just doing.
- [SCOFFS] God.
- All right. Of course. Priorities.
- [THUDDING]
- [LOUISA GASPS] [MIN EXHALES SHARPLY, WHISPERS] No.
- [NORMAL] Corkboard?
- [THUDS] No, there were two noises.
Well, maybe it bounced.
[THUDDING]
Okay.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Fuck it.
[SIGHS] So, what...
what... what now?
Do you wanna go back to my
place or we go back to yours?
[LOUISA SCOFFS]
[CHUCKLES] Let's
do one more sweep.
[MIN SHOUTS, GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- [BONE CRUNCHES]
- [MIN GROANING] [LOUISA] Min? Min!
[DOOR OPENS]
- Min.
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING] - Min, you all right? - Yeah. Yeah.
- Min?
- The gun, the gun.
[GROANS]
- You okay?
- Fine. I'm fine.
- No pulse. I think you broke his neck.
- [PANTING] He broke his own fucking neck.
Oh, my God.
- [GROANS]
- Oh, my God.
- Fuck.
- What the fuck?
[MIN GROANS]
[HOSPITAL ANNOUNCER] Dr. Lawrence,
come to surgical three.
Non-emergency.
Dr. Lawrence, please.
Dr. Lawrence, come to
surgical three. Non-emergency.
[DOOR OPENS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Can I help you, sir?
Think you must be lost, sir.
They'll help you at reception
with whatever you're after.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [PERSON GRUNTS]
[CLATTERING, SCUFFLING]
[PERSON GURGLES]
- [CLATTERING, SCUFFLING STOP]
- [FOOTSTEPS] A shoe in a bag?
- [CHUCKLES] I'm embarrassed for you.
- [MOP CLATTERS] [RIVER] Wait, wait, wait.
- He's got my phone and my pass.
- [SIGHS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- Take all the time you need.
- Yeah.
[CHATTERING]
Sorry. Um, Sidonie Baker,
do you where she's, um...
Lamb. La...
Lamb, I can't just leave
without knowing how she is.
She's still on the table.
What do you mean? Is
she gonna make it?
[JACKSON] Why the fuck did
you ride in the ambulance?
I thought she was dying.
I'm not just gonna fucking
leave her there, am I?
- Would you?
- Yes.
It was a dumb dick move.
Once you called it in, your ID was flashing lights and sounding whistles from here to Regent's Park.
That's why that Dog
was waiting for you.
Wait, how did you
know I was here?
'Cause once you went walkabout, - I got Ho to monitor the Park's alerts. - Why?
In case you did something
as stupid as you did.
[CAR DOOR SLAMS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[SIGHS]
Okay.
They, uh... They
say she might live.
Oh, thank Christ.
[CHUCKLES]
No thanks to you.
[NEWS ANCHOR] No
indication as yet that the authorities know where Hassan is being held.
- [NEWSCAST CONTINUES, INDISTINCT]
- [WOOD CRACKING] - [VEHICLE PASSES] - [PANTING]
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
- [COUGHS]
- [WOOD SNAPS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [PEOPLE CHATTERING, INDISTINCT]
- [FOOTSTEPS] - [COUGHS] - [TOM BRADBY] Police are now saying the threat to Leeds University student Hassan is grave and imminent.
His liaison officers remain
with Hassan's parents, but it has been some hours since anyone has been seen entering or, indeed, leaving the house.
- [CELL PHONE BUZZING]
- We can go to a live press briefing - being given by West Yorkshire Police. - Yeah?
Cartwright's gone.
I think it was Lamb.
- [DIANA] Find them.
- [LINE CLICKS] [POLICE SPOKESPERSON ON TV] Hassan Ahmed was here after he left this comedy club, The Last Laugh, at approximately 11...
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[RIVER] Slough House?
Why have you brought
me back here?
[SIGHS] Because you're my agent, and you were there when another of my agents was shot, so I'm doing your debrief.
What the hell were you
two doing at Hobden's?
He's got something on his
laptop that the Park want.
I think he's connected to
th... to the kidnappers.
Sid thought this too?
Well, she followed
me following Hobden.
She told me she'd been put
in Slough House to watch me.
Was that before or after
she got shot in the head?
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Who was it?
Who was what?
Who shot her, you pillock?
I don't know. I
couldn't see his face.
He had a balaclava
on and tactical gear.
So, a pro?
Yeah. But, uh... Well, kind of.
[SCOFFS] For fuck's
sake, Cartwright.
- [RIVER] I...
- God.
Can you let me think for one
minute? Would that be fine?
I don't know. It was
strange. It was like he... he he wanted me to think that he was one of the Dogs.
But it just... It
wasn't quite right.
And he didn't speak
the whole time.
Like he was worried I
might recognize his voice.
God.
[SIGHS]
There's your answer,
Cartwright. Jed fucking Moody.
If you had issues with him,
I could have spoken to HR.
No, we didn't know it was him.
- He jumped out.
- I'm not sure that counts as a defense.
He had a gun.
Better. He used it earlier.
- Shot Sid Baker with it.
- What, he killed Sid? Why?
No. She's... She's
fine. She's alive.
Mmm. She was 20 minutes ago.
But wait. Why... Why the fuck did
he shoot her? Where were they?
We were at Robert Hobden's. Sid
followed me. I never asked her to.
[LOUISA] What was
Moody doing there?
[RIVER] I don't know why he was
there. He broke in dressed like this.
- What was he doing here?
- Well, we didn't get a chance to ask.
But he'd... He'd
been in your office.
Your corkboard was off the wall.
[JACKSON] Can you account
for your movements?
- Well, we were over the road. And...
- In... In the pub.
[GROANS] Fuck me.
If this is nicer than going
back to your place, I pity you.
[GRUNTS] Where's,
uh... Where's the gun?
- [LOUISA] It's over there.
- [SNIFFLES, EXHALES] He looked like using it?
[STAMMERS] Look, let's
get this straight.
This is not a court of law.
Did he look like using it?
[MIN] He didn't
point it exactly, no.
Yeah, well, you might want to
reconsider your position on that.
- I didn't mean to kill him.
- Of course you didn't.
If you meant to kill
him, he'd still be alive.
Hmm. What's this?
[GRUNTS] Dirty bastard.
What, was he gonna
bug your office?
Uh, it'd be an odd move after
shooting one of my joes.
No, he was cleaning up.
Prior to getting out.
Well the prostitutes of Paraguay, or whichever non-extradition destination he was headed for, have had a lucky escape.
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTING]
Two mobiles.
Jed, Jed, Jed.
Eh, I'm surprised you had
enough friends to carry one.
[GROANS]
- [CELL PHONE BEEPING]
- This one's barely used.
Just one incoming call.
You should ring it.
Thank fuck you're here.
I would never have
thought of that.
[BEEPING]
[LINE RINGS]
[DIANA] Moody?
I'm afraid he can't come
to the phone right now.
Jackson.
We need to talk.
Come on.
- Yes?
- I need to see him.
It's very late, sir.
- I know that. Is he here?
- Who shall I say, sir?
Hobden. It's Robert Hobden.
Whoa. Just... Just save us
all a lot of back and forth.
Just tell him, if he's
not receiving guests now, he will need to make himself available in the morning, 'cause there will be cameras out front and tabloids trying to get in the back.
[CHATTERING, LAUGHING]
Wait here.
- [CHATTERING, LAUGHING CONTINUE]
- [EXHALES SHARPLY] Robert Hobden, as I live and breathe and shag like a lord.
Good to see you, old chum.
Timing's a little off.
But when a friend drops
by, my door is always open, and my wine is waiting to be uncorked.
I've got this, Seb. Give
us a moment, would you?
What the fuck are you doing
here, you stupid fucking twat?
[SIGHS] I have been
trying to contact you.
I've been avoiding your calls. Take
the hint. You're fucking toxic.
- Did anyone see you arrive?
- I don't know.
- What kind of prick answer is that?
- It's the only prick answer I've got.
- What happened?
- [SIGHS] Someone tried to kill me tonight.
Well, a lot of fanatics about.
- You're not the most popular...
- It wasn't a fanatic. It was a spook.
- A spook?
- Mmm.
MI5 sent a man, masked man, to my
flat, with a gun, to get my laptop.
Fucking hell! I don't
know where anything is.
I hardly ever come in here.
Why would MI5 want
your computer?
Because I have intel about the
kidnapping. The Muslim boy.
Why should I care
about the kidnapping?
I've already made enough of a tit
of myself, claiming it was ISIS.
Because your entire career has
been playing the nationalist card.
And if that boy dies, the closest
you'll get to Downing Street is looking down on it from an open-top bus.
You alone?
Don't know why they had
to clean up the canals.
There was a time you
could find an oil drum or a corpse to use as a target.
What do you think
you're playing at?
Well, that's fucking choice,
considering I lent you an agent for what you said was a run-of-the-mill op, who now has a bullet in her head.
"What do you think you're
playing at?" is my line, with a few fucking fucks thrown in.
I'm sorry, but the brief was not
for her to be on Hobden 24/7.
No, the brief was to
be on Cartwright 24/7.
Which makes me think she
was your agent all along, and you were just asking for show.
- Where was she when she was...
- She was shot outside Hobden's.
Intentionally or otherwise, by Jed
Moody, another one of your recruits.
So, if I may be so bold, what the living fuck do you think you're playing at?
Check the rule book, Lamb.
You run Slough
House, and God knows no one wants to take that away from you, but I am Second Desk, head of ops, which means directing personnel.
All personnel. Yours
or anybody else's.
[PASSES GAS, GRUNTS]
Better out than in.
Oh, God, you're vile.
[SNIFFS, GROANS]
Actually, maybe not.
So, say you're right and
this is none of my business, what do I do about the body on my staircase?
- Moody?
- Yeah.
He's dead?
It's hard to tell,
given his IQ, but yes.
- Jesus.
- Yeah.
But if you wanted
to subcontract, you could've done better than Jed Moody.
Even when he was good,
he wasn't any good.
The guy's a fucking
fridge magnet.
- Who took him down?
- W... [LAUGHS]
Here's the funny part. He
forgot to tie his shoelaces.
[LAUGHING] He f... He
fell down the stairs.
Yes. When you're in
front of Limitations, you might want to leave out the bit about that being funny.
Oh, Limitations.
So, do we call in the Dogs?
Hell, it's a death, Diana.
I could call the
police. I should.
I've got a mobile phone on me.
Yeah, I could use that.
Yeah, I found it
on Moody's body.
The odd thing is, the only
number in it is yours.
Yeah, you've made your point.
It's after 02:00, Diana.
And my team is smaller
than it was yesterday.
You've got till I finish this
fag before I start making calls.
Okay.
I was talking to my brother
at the Frontline Club.
And I mentioned we were
developing operations to neutralize the nationalists.
You are fucking kidding me.
Sons of Albion have links to groups
all under Simmonds's umbrella.
I can use this to
roll them all up.
So, you set up some
half-arsed scheme involving a neofascist group kidnapping a Muslim kid and threatening to chop his head off on YouTube?
Except it's not going to happen
'cause one of the group is yours.
- Close?
- Half-arsed?
One dead and one in
intensive care because what?
You... You... You think Hobden's
got a piece of the puzzle?
When I went to the bar
at the Frontline Club, I saw Hobden in the booth behind us.
Bad tradecraft on my
part, no... no question.
Uh, you thought he might have
overheard you or recorded it?
That's why you needed
to know what he had.
[SCOFFS]
[CHATTERING]
Do you have any proof?
No, but MI5 must think I do. That's
why they tried to kill me tonight.
And you come here, leaving a
trail of mad, shitty footprints.
- I don't want to be caught up in this.
- You're already caught up in this.
You have to warn them
and get them out!
And say what?
Tell them that th-this whole setup,
this supposed execution, is a fake.
That the Sons of Albion, who've never been more than a bunch of moronic street thugs, have been set up by the intelligence services.
By an agent provocateur.
And I'm to, what, announce
this in the House?
Or maybe on the Today program?
Peter, we've known each other for
years. Don't try and fob me off.
We are not friends, Robert.
You've always treated me fairly
in print, and I respect that.
But let's face it, you're
a fucking has-been, and it's no longer appropriate to be associated with you.
So take it somewhere else.
Maybe to your pals in the
British Patriotic Party.
[SCOFFS] What? They
won't believe me.
Well, I can't warn these Sons of
Whatever. I don't know the fuckers.
But you know people
who know people.
You have to warn them.
You have to get the word
out. A spy's in their midst.
A rescue will be staged,
and they will all be killed.
I'm a respected and
much-loved national figure.
I don't have any of the contacts
you're talking about, you mad bastard.
[SPOUSE] Peter, you're needed!
The second I go upstairs, you get the fuck out of here, or I'll have Seb drag you out.
I have the photo of
you at the rally.
Darling, Nahim and Ursula
are going to go very soon.
Already? And skipping cheese,
are they? I'll see about that.
Let's open some port
and tempt them to stay.
Would your friend
care to join us?
Rob and I have been discussing some very official secret hush-hush, darling.
No one's supposed
to know he's here.
You wait here, bud.
I'll settle things upstairs
and be back in a jiffy.
[SIGHS]
I can't help but notice you
seem, you know, pretty relaxed for someone who set up a false flag operation to behead an innocent kid in what, uh, four hours.
They're not gonna do it.
Their core messaging
suggests they very much are.
Our agent told them they didn't
actually need a beheading.
They just had to show that
they could do it if pushed.
That's a hell of a gamble.
I wouldn't fancy your odds.
You underestimate me.
The boy was chosen with care.
The kid. Who is he?
He's Mahmud Gul's
nephew. Gul is...
I know who Mahmud
fucking Gul is.
He's number two in Pakistan's
military intelligence.
And... And this gets you what?
We will rescue his nephew, and if that gets us even 10% more cooperation with the Pakistanis, it will be worth it.
If this goes tits up... and Christ
knows it hasn't gone right yet you... you've assassinated his nephew!
- Our man is...
- Oh, "your man."
This isn't a sanctioned
service op, Diana.
This is off the books!
This is pirate shit! Now
you've got Hobden in the wind!
You gotta roll this up!
- It can still work.
- It...
- This can neutralize the far right.
- [STAMMERS] It can't.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
PLAYING ON TV]
[HASSAN SNORING ON MONITOR]
[SIGHS]
How the fuck is he sleepin'?
I know I couldn't sleep
with what he thinks is about to happen. I know that.
He won't have slept
since we grabbed him.
He must be exhausted.
You wanna go down and sing
him a lullaby, do you?
[ZEPPO CHUCKLES]
[SNORING CONTINUES]
Fuck's sake.
[SIGHS] I'll mute it.
Can still see the lights.
[TV PLAYING, INDISTINCT]
[IMITATING SNORING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SNIFFLES]
[IMITATING SNORING CONTINUES]
[OBJECT SCRAPING]
[GRUNTS, PANTS]
[STRAINING]
[WOOD SNAPS, CLATTERS]
- Little fucker!
- Bastard!
Come on then.
- Get down there.
- [PANTING] Help! Somebody help me!
[GRUNTS] Somebody
help me, please!
- [LARRY] Grab his legs!
- [MOE] No, no.
- Somebody help me! Oh, no, no!
- [LARRY] Get him down from there!
- [SCREAMS] Help me! Help me! Help!
- [MOE] Get the fucker out of here.
Just humor me and
explore the flip side.
If those Sons of Nonsense get
wind of what you're up to, that kid is as good as dead, and your man too.
You've gotta call him and
tell him his cover's blown.
Not possible. He wanted
them to go dark. No phones.
[STAMMERS] Send
in the Dogs early.
If we bring it forward,
we need to let him know so he can secure Hassan and get out himself.
- Yeah. Well, lots of luck with that one.
- You're gonna help me.
Ugh. Oh, no, I'm not. And
nor are any of my people.
They brought the boy to London.
They're holding him in a
house this side of the river.
All I'm asking you to do is
literally knock on the door.
Our man will answer, and...
- What's the signal?
- Your face is the signal.
My face?
Oh, you're a legend in
the service, Jackson.
He'll recognize your face and
know something's about to go down.
He'll secure Hassan, and Dogs
will be right behind you.
They'll go in and
do the dirty work.
I've got other things I
could do tonight, Diana.
[SNIFFLES] I've got a
really massive shit brewin'.
I could sit and read a
book and birth that beauty.
[SIGHS]
Was Moody alone when he died?
We're all alone in the end,
don't you think, Diana?
In those final moments?
If he did have company, that company might come under intense scrutiny.
Oh, by all means,
call in the Dogs.
And when they're finished
tearing you apart, maybe they'll have enough strength to pick at the rest of this.
Either way, I couldn't
give a monkey's.
Even if it was Standish?
Y... You're tossin' darts.
Standish wasn't there.
She's at home asleep.
I'm not talking about tonight.
I'm talking about the
night Charles Partner died.
Catherine Standish came very
close to a treason charge.
That file could be
reopened, reassessed.
Didn't fly then.
It won't fly now.
A lot of other things
might come out.
That is not a can of
worms you want to open.
Do I look keen?
Like it or not, Slough
House is part of this now.
You'll all get turned over.
Standish will find
out some things it would be better for her not to know.
I'll go knock on
the door for you.
But in return, I want
the Standish file.
And you've been using Slough
House as your personal toy box, which pisses me off.
- Are we clear?
- Crystal.
Oh, there's more.
Moody disappears.
Baker, a victim of street crime.
Anyone with me
tonight is fireproof.
Oh.
And you are in my debt
until you're in a care home.
God, you really care
about them, don't you?
Mmm.
Nah. I think they're a
bunch of fucking losers.
But they're my losers.
For what it's worth,
I'm sorry about Baker.
I'll have that
marked on her chart.
You know, the one that clips
to the bottom of her bed that tells you when her catheter needs changin'.
- [CHATTERING]
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING] I apologize for the threat, but I do need you to listen to me.
Don't you see?
They want everyone to forget a-about body parts on the tube.
Madmen with swords, hacking
people to bits on bridges.
But instead, we'll have footage of our brave spooks rescuin' some brown-skinned boy and paintin' the right as a bunch of murdering bastards.
[ICE CLATTERING]
Do you want them to
get away with it?
This will stop you
from taking your party and your country further to the right.
Oh, that ground
will be poisoned, and there'll be a swing to happy-clappy, rainbow Britain.
[CHUCKLES]
Where the rights of the minority drown out the rights of the true-born majority, and you'll have to go along with it.
And that will pain you. And I
know that you're with me on this.
- [WATER RUNNING]
- [POTS CLATTERING] Now I don't want to have to use that photo to make you do this.
I want you to do this willingly.
- [GRUNTS]
- [GROANS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Listen to me, fucko.
That photo doesn't exist.
If it did, anyone who was in it would make sure all copies and negatives were destroyed.
But say it did exist and
you somehow had a copy.
I can brush it off quicker
than you can cream your piles.
"It's photoshopped."
It's a wave, not a Nazi salute.
It was fancy dress. Poor
taste, but not a crime.
I was young and
drunk and stupid, and this is not the man I know myself to be.
"Here's ten grand to
an anti-fascist group."
Now get the fuck out of my house before I punch you so hard, I break my fist.
[GRUNTS]
Seb.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
You want me to follow him?
Warn him off a return visit?
No, but I'll need you
to make some calls.
- [TAPE RIPPING]
- Fuck! That was close.
He is a horrible,
slippery little prick.
Yeah. Well, he's not
goin' anywhere now, so if either of you wanna doze off.
Nah. I'm pretty wired now.
No. I'm stayin' awake, because I
don't trust this little bastard.
[MOE] Easy. All in good
time. All in good time.
Where's fucking laughing boy?
Don't know. Probably upstairs,
havin' a bubble bath.
All right, let's
have some fun then.
Might as well make
some money off you two.
Who's in?
- [ZEPPO] I'm all for a game of cards.
- Yeah, all right.
[LARRY] Um, let's get rid
of some of these bottles.
- Don't be falling asleep in there.
- [MOE] Yeah, go on.
[ZEPPO] Mmm. [CHUCKLES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[PANTING]
What happened to the gun?
All right. Come on, pillocks.
Keep an eye on the
place, eh, Jed?
- Has anyone else got a car here?
- I have.
- You in a fit state to drive?
- I can drive.
I hold my drink better than Min.
All right. Cartwright,
you're with me.
You two fuckbirds follow.
[RIVER] Where we going?
[JACKSON] Roupell Street.
South of the river.
- Why?
- To assist with the rescue of Hassan Ahmed.
[REPORTER] Speaking
this morning, the Prime Minister described the kidnappers as pure evil.
[REPORTER 2] Government is
doing plenty of tough talking...
[REPORTER 3] The kidnappers
are claiming to be from a group called the Sons of Albion.
[REPORTER 4] ... despicable
and ghastly acts.
[REPORTER 5] The fear is that another
British citizen is going to die...
[REPORTER 6] The British
government now finds itself fighting international terrorism on its home turf.
[REPORTER 7] ... as
extremely worrying and added the investigation continues...
[REPORTER 8] The deadline set
by the men holding Hassan Ahmed is now less than four hours away.
[CELL PHONE BUZZES]
Proceed. Lamb will
knock. You clean up.
Go!
- It was money, wasn't it?
- [JACKSON] What?
"What?" Come on. In that
envelope you took off Moody.
It's your flight fund, in case
you need to make a run for it.
Flight fund? Why, I haven't
heard that for a long time.
- Where'd you get that? Your grandfather?
- How much?
[SIGHS] Fifteen hundred, a passport and a key to a box.
- Switzerland?
- Fuck you, Switzerland.
Bank in a two-donkey French town
four hours' drive from Paris.
Why am I telling you all this?
Probably so you'd have
an excuse to kill me.
That's probably it.
- [TYPING]
- [PHONES RINGING]
[CHATTERING]
Home Office, ma'am. Barrowby.
Tell him I'm operational.
I'll call him back when I can.
Yes, ma'am.
Do you, uh, think he
can breathe in there?
Get a move on.
[LARRY] He hasn't moved in ages.
That's 'cause he's
tied to a chair.
You can breathe, can't you?
Don't piss about. Nod.
I know you can hear me.
- [WHIMPERS]
- See? He's fine.
[HASSAN WHIMPERING]
- Fifteen.
- [CLICKING TONGUE] [SIGHS] Call.
Fifteen.
Where have you been?
Hugging a pillow and crying?
Hey, what were you
doing up there?
Just thinking.
[MOE] Thought I
heard a dull clang.
Want me to deal you in?
Playing for real money though.
You may not have
the stones for that.
I'll raise another 30.
What regiment were you in?
- What?
- In the army.
You know, when you were
out killing towelheads.
[MOE] Marines.
Asked about the regiment...
Marines don't have regiments.
It's battalion units
known as commandos.
Stop makin' a twat of yourself.
Well?
[ZEPPO EXHALES HEAVILY]
All in.
[LARRY FLAPS LIPS]
Bollocks to it.
[MOE] Ooh, looks like you two
are finally growing a dick.
One between you.
You haven't used one of
these though, have you?
Put it down.
- [HASSAN SNIFFLING]
- [CURLY] No.
It feels good in my hand.
[HASSAN WHIMPERING]
[CURLY] All it'd take
is one swing, I reckon.
Cut right through.
Put it down before you
fuck everything up.
Hold on.
So, killing him now
would fuck everything up?
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
That's odd.
I mean, what are you
talkin' about, mate?
I thought we were strikin' a
blow for Britain at sunrise.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
Look.
At the end of this, I
report to Simmonds, yeah?
Now, I can tell him you're a good
soldier. You get a pat on the back.
Or I can tell him
you're a twat liability and have his boys break your spine.
Up to you.
[CURLY EXHALES DEEPLY]
[SCOFFS]
[ZEPPO EXHALES, MUTTERS]
You little prick.
- Full house, dickheads.
- [ZEPPO] Ah, bollocks.
- [MOE] Hey!
- [LARRY, ZEPPO] No!
[RIVER] Seems pretty quiet.
What'd you expect?
Balloons tied to the door?
Whoa. Why are you takin' a gun if
you just have to knock on the door?
Because this whole
op is fucked up.
Taverner's playin' London rules,
but I'm the one in joe country, so I'll play Moscow rules. Thank you.
[GRUNTS]
[CAT MEOWS]
[CLICKING TONGUE]
Hey.
What are you doin'?
Stroking a cat.
[KNOCKING]
Shit!
Go around the back!
[RIVER] Lamb?
Lamb?
[JACKSON] Kitchen.
- [DOOR OPENS]
- Oh, fuck.