Diane sent a listing that looks promising.
Should we go check it out?
I can't today.
Or we could go tomorrow,
or on the weekend if you like?
You know what?
I'm really swamped at work, so, uh,
why don't you, uh, ask Will?
Hey. I am sorry that I told him
I was fired before I told you.
I am sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
I made a mistake. I'm sorry, baby.
I'm sorry!
How many times do I have to say it?
Okay, if you yell,
it doesn't count as an apology.
[whispers]
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Okay.
How long is this gonna go on for?
I don't know. I don't have a crystal ball.
So, I'll see you at home for dinner?
Maybe. Maybe not.
Actually, no. I-I-I told Frances
I would help her with her homework,
so I'll be back no later than 9:00.
- Okay.
[Sylvia] Okay.
["Bad Habit" playing]
Well, this is easily 200 billable hours.
I am hungry.
We should probably spend some
six minute increments having dinner.
Vanessa, what will it be? Surf or turf?
Um, I don't know. Since Dupont's
paying for it, what if we did both?
Ooh, surf and turf.
Charlie, I assume you'll be
finishing your work at home?
You know what? I am gonna stay
and push through with you guys tonight.
I miss eating steak with a plastic fork.
- Uh, special occasion, anyone?
- Ooh?
Come on. We get Charlie tonight?
- [chuckling]
- You never stay late.
Normally you finish your work at home
like someone who loves his family.
Well, not tonight.
Oh, yeah!
Preach. Preach, brother.
- [laughs]
- Late-night Charlie. I love it.
You know what? I don't even care
that she lost her job. Shit happens.
The problem is that
she didn't tell you first.
A guy shouldn't learn something like that
from his photo library.
Mmm. Rookie mistake.
Whenever Doug travels for work,
I check my photos every 15 minutes.
- Really?
- Mmm. Can't be too careful.
- Ugh. You know what? Screw it.
- [Stewart, Vanessa laughing]
- Late-night Charlie. All right, guys.
- Mmm. Mmm.
I gotta go meet a... Let's say "friend."
- Excuse me.
- Ooh.
[Vanessa] Look at you.
You are an animal, huh?
Okay. That's it for my holiday gift wine.
- You got anything around here?
- You know what?
I have a bottle of display Scotch.
- Okay. Now we're talking.
- Okay. Yes. Ooh. Very nice.
- May I?
- Mm-hmm.
Do Frank. Do Frank.
What's your name?
- He doesn't know anyone's name.
- No.
[both laughing]
Oh.
Albert has Scotch in his office.
He never touches it.
- That is so Albert.
- [chuckles]
Should we steal it?
- [gasps] You're so bad.
- Yeah?
- You're so bad. Let's go.
- Let's do it. Late-night Charlie.
[singsongy] Ta-da.
[Charlie] Oh. Ooh.
[speaks indistinctly]
- So bad.
- [breathing heavily]
Albert's cool.
Go, go, go, go, go.
["Run-Around" playing]
Oh! That's really good.
This is where it gets...
No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm the deejay now.
- Okay. All right.
- I'm the deejay now. Okay?
- ["Red Red Wine" playing]
- Ah.
[chuckles]
[Charlie] Yeah!
- [Vanessa laughing]
- [chuckling] Yeah. Ah.
- [Vanessa sighs] Ah.
- Ah. [grunts]
[breathing heavily] Oh, my God. Yeah.
- Yeah. Oh. Yeah. [panting]
- [Charlie panting]
- I should prob... I should go. Yeah.
- I, um, me too. [clears throat]
- I should go. I should go.
- Yes.
[breathing heavily]
[music stops]
You were dirty dancing? What-What is that?
Sort of, like, dancing from the movie.
[stutters] Wha...
You mean the movie Dirty Dancing?
I'm just saying it was inappropriate,
and I regret it.
- Well, show me what you did.
- That's okay.
No, no. [stutters] I actually,
I would like to know what happened.
Take me there.
I was a little drunk.
I don't really remember.
What? You were drunk at work?
Ye... We had a little to drink at work.
Stewart was there.
What? Was he dirty dancing too?
What do you mean?
No, he had left by-by that time.
I would like to see exactly what you did.
[stutters]
Would you like me to put the song,
"I've Had the Time of My Life" on?
Would that help you remember?
It actually wasn't that song.
What song was it?
"Red Red Wine."
- UB40?
- Yep.
- UB-serious? Oh, my God. [gags]
- [sighs deeply]
I just got full body chills
from embarrassment for you. Wow.
We also dry humped
for eight to ten seconds.
- What?
- I...
- Oh, my... [gasps] Did you kiss her?
- No.
- Do you love her?
Were you guys harboring secret feelings
for one another?
Absolutely not. I-I have no feelings
for Vanessa. She's so boring.
That doesn't make me feel any better.
She's got four kids.
She's like a fertility factory. She's
probably pregnant with your twins already.
Absolutely not.
I was nowhere even near ejaculation.
Ew! Don't say that word.
That's disgus... Stop talking.
So, you just had, like, a quick dry hump?
What? That's so tacky.
I-I think maybe I was acting out
because of all the time
you've been spending with Will.
Oh. Oh, it's my fault?
That's so manipulative.
I'm-I'm not trying to excuse my behavior.
I just want you to know
how I've been feeling. I am so sor...
Absolutely not! Stay back there.
Sorry. Yes, of course. Sorry. I'll just...
Vanessa. She's so dull and humorless.
Ugh. She's like wallpaper.
Is it okay if I come and sleep here?
[Charlie] Okay. Zip, zip. [clears throat]
- Hi.
- Morning.
- [Maeve] Morning, Mommy.
- [Simon] Hi.
- [Sylvia] Morning. Morning.
- Kids are fed and dressed,
and their hair is brushed.
I'm gonna drop them off.
I'm also gonna pick them up.
Oh, I made you poached eggs.
They're in the kitchen.
If they're cold, I'm happy to make you,
uh, new ones.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- [door knocks]
- [Charlie] Ah.
Thank you, sir.
- This is, uh, oat milk latte.
- Hmm.
If it's cold, I can...
I can order you another one.
- I'm good.
- Good. What are you gonna do today?
[inhales sharply]
Uh, I think whatever I want.
Good. Yeah, great.
- [Sylvia] Bye, guys.
- Bye.
Why is Mommy looking at you like that?
Did you do something bad?
[chuckles] No. Okay. Okay.
Chop-chop. Let's go.
- Let's go. All right. Good, good.
- [Simon] She's still doing it.
[Reggie] Dude, are you fucking crazy?
I'm not crazy at all.
That kombucha
business would not exist without me.
You are only able to get investors
because of what I built in this bar.
- I'm entitled to a piece of that business.
- You sound fucking insane right now.
Why is this insane? We talked about it
in San Diego. You were open to it.
Yeah. That was before you blew
the Johnny 66 deal, ass.
I fucked up that deal for moral reasons.
That had nothing to do
with my business acumen, which is vast.
I have been described as
a regular Warren Buffett!
- Oh, it's "Buffett". But go off...
- You shut the fuck up.
Okay? And if I remember correctly,
that deal was tanking
until I stepped in and saved it.
Well, let me ask you this, how much do you
think you deserve in this situation?
Good question.
Because I do not wanna get so brutally
fucked over by you two gentlemen, 51%.
Oh, my God.
You're fucking out of your mind.
Fifty-two percent.
- Oh, my God.
- What... Y...
You have no leverage,
and this is not a negotiation.
- You're just asking for money.
- Fifty-three percent.
No, dude.
I don't negotiate with terrorists.
Fifty-four percent.
- Omar gets it.
- Will, this is not happening.
We built the entire groundwork
of Daa Booch without you.
You stood on the shoulders of giants.
I'm sorry.
Are you "giants" in this situation?
I sure am giants.
I put up with your shit
for so fucking long.
I want you to look me in the eye
so you can hear
that this is not fucking happening!
You want some leverage?
I'll show you my fucking leverage.
I'm gonna squirt leverage
in your fucking face. I'm going on strike!
- [Reggie] Fuck you, bro.
- Oh, you're going on strike?
You're going on strike on your business?
Oh, I sure as fuck am. Let's see how well
this place runs without me around, huh?
I will return when
I am cut into Daa Booch.
And by the way, my first order of business
as majority shareholder,
I'm changing that fucking name.
[Reggie] Dick.
Oh, he'll be back.
In one, two, three,
four...
Oh, shit.
Omar, can you take care of
the tank room while he's gone?
- That does not inspire confidence.
- [Andy sighs]
I mean, she's so accomplished.
Look at all the boards she's on.
Oh, my God. Who gives a shit
what boards she's on?
She looks like a crazy person.
She looks like Amy Coney Barrett.
You mean, one of the most powerful women
in America?
Yes. But I think you get my point.
I mean, how does she have time
to do all this? She has four kids.
She's partner,
and she literally has a newborn.
And it's really cute too.
It's not even a weird looking baby.
Yeah. She probably never sees it.
She probably never sees any of them.
They're gonna grow up resenting her.
Mark my words.
They're just gonna grow up
and wanna be her.
I mean, could he have picked
a worse person?
She's partner in the firm,
she has four kids.
She's very blonde, she's very tall.
Okay, yeah. Let's do it your way.
Wow, I mean, she is beautiful,
- she's accomplished.
- [chuckles]
[stutters] I think the-the right thing
to do is to give your husband to her.
She's basic as hell! She's fucking boring.
Yeah. She's not even actually that cute.
And who dry humps? Take your fucking pants
off and do it right.
She's a quitter. She's a quitter.
What am I gonna do about Charlie?
He needs to pay for this.
Uh, jewelry?
[sighs] Yeah?
Is dry humping worth jewelry?
Sounds like purse-level.
Syl, are you okay?
Do you want me to come over?
No, no, no. I'm okay. I'm okay.
[knocks]
I gotta go. Someone's at the door.
Thanks, babe.
Oh. [chuckles]
Hey. You okay?
Yeah. I'm fine. Just... paper cut.
What are you doing here?
I took the day off work. Honestly,
I just need someone to complain to.
- Oh, well, you've come to the right place.
- Thought so.
So, you think they'll give you
a cut-in on the Daa Booch?
I do think they'll cut me into da
Daa Booch, and they'll give me da money,
and I can, uh, da retire.
- Really? [chuckles]
- To da islands. [chuckling]
Why do you think that?
Whose side are you on here?
I don't know. I'm really just trying
to slice this meat. [grunts]
I think they will see how much
the business needs me to function properly
and they will project that onto Daa Booch,
and they, you know,
they-they'll be begging me
to be a part of it.
I honestly don't know why
you find this relaxing.
Cooking dinner is, like,
the biggest chore of my day.
Oh, it's so relaxing.
There's one where you clean up
a little mouse's apartment. Also amazing.
Oh, hey, Will.
- Hey!
- What are you guys up to?
Can you not see that
we are virtually creating a meal
with a pair of
disembodied Caucasian hands?
- [Sylvia chuckles]
- Oh. Oh, right. I see.
Hey, where are the kids?
- Huh?
- The kids.
They're in the garden. Yeah.
They each brought a friend home,
and they're waiting for you
to take them out for pizza.
- Pizza? Great. Okay. Good.
- [yelps]
Um, can I get you guys anything?
Yeah, I'll take a pepperoni.
Will, what do you want?
Oh, I'll take some mushroom pizza
if you're buying pizza. Yeah.
And I'd love a bottle of rosé, please.
Like, a Whispering Angel or whatever.
If you happen to walk past an IPA.
It doesn't have to be local,
but if it is, I would, uh,
I would take that as well.
Okay, sure. Okay. Okay.
- [Sylvia] Thanks.
- [Charlie] All right.
Hey, kids! Pizza!
- Flip, flip, flip!
- Flip that meatball! Flip it! Flip it!
- Ah! Oh! Hey! Flip!
- Oh, there you go. Hey! Hey!
- [Maeve] Piz-Pizza!
- [children chattering]
Can Jack sleep over?
Yeah, sure.
Why not? Friday night, yeah? Oh!
If Jack sleeps over, the other kids
are gonna wanna sleep over...
Gemma, Shelby, you guys wanna sleep over?
[children cheering]
- Yay!
- [children chattering]
- Okay! Let's go! Pizza time!
- Okay. You tell their parents, yeah?
Minivan keys are on the hook!
- Yep. Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Fun house. [chuckles]
- Oh, yeah. Friday night.
- [Will groans] Whoo.
- [people shouting, clamoring]
I really wish you had
a security camera in your backyard,
I'd be famous right now.
Yeah, as a stupid person.
- Is there any other kind of famous person?
- [laughs]
Um, the, uh, four little ones are in bed.
[sighs] I'm not sure that Shelby's
gonna make it through the night
because she's five, and she's never
slept over at anyone's house before.
[inhales sharply] So, uh, I think I'll
probably, uh... [yawns] ...hit the hay.
Um, in case I get woken up at 2:00 a.m.
Oh, should I, uh, should I get going?
I didn't realize it was bedtime
'cause it's 09:23, but, um...
Oh, no, you should just stay the night.
Yeah? Is that cool?
- Cool.
- I don't wanna impose or anything, but...
No, I mean, your nails have to dry anyway.
- My nails do have to dry.
- Yeah.
I would hate to ruin them,
I worked pretty hard.
Sure, okay. Um, hey, Sylvia, are you...
[mouthing words] ...coming?
[Sylvia, Will laughing] Oh! Oh!
[Charlie] Okay.
I'll grab the air mattress then.
I'm not clicking on that, but I will click
on the Brandy Melville mega-haul.
- [Will] Oh!
- [Sylvia groans]
Oh, my God. I know that girl.
I actually like that shirt.
I would wear that.
- I've been looking for that.
- [Will] It's actually cute.
- It comes in green as well...
- [air mattress pump whirring]
Oh, my God. Can you wait until after
we've watched this Brandy haul to do that?
[air mattress pump stops]
[Will] She seems pretty self-centered.
[Sylvia] Yeah.
I don't... I'm not loving her.
[Will] I can... I go shopping too,
I don't post it
on YouTube every fucking time.
Click on that. "Why NASA doesn't want you
to know the earth is flat."
Yeah, my dad's all about that.
Yeah, he has some
pretty convincing arguments.
- Mm-hmm. He posts about it too.
- Yeah.
[Will chewing]
Sounds like you're jerking off
your arms over there.
Ew. Leave a woman to her creams.
Thank you so much for inviting me
to this slumber party.
I'm in such a better mood than
I would've been if I was alone all day.
Aw. Yeah, that's the thing
about never being alone.
You just never have time to feel anything.
- That sounds amazing.
- Good.
Do you ever think about
leaving Lucky Penny, like, for real?
It just seems like you and those guys,
you really do not see eye to eye.
Yeah. You know, as much as
I hate the business side of it,
I just like making beer too much.
I don't know what else I would do.
- Doritosaurus. Doritosaurus.
- Doritosaurus. [growls, chuckles]
I don't know why you wanna move.
This house is awesome.
[groans] It's way too small
for the five of us.
You've got a garage back there
you're not even using.
It's gross back there.
It's like a meth lab.
Most meth labs I've been to
have been impeccably clean.
Well, ours is disgusting.
We bought this house, and we just...
[stutters] ...never touched it again.
You could turn it into an ADU,
like an additional dwelling unit.
Uh, you know,
like a little guesthouse kinda thing.
We don't want guests.
We just want another bedroom
and another bathroom.
That's exactly what
you could put back there.
I don't know.
That sounds like a big project.
Not a bigger project than moving,
you know? It would add square footage.
It would add
to the resale value of your home,
which is very responsible
of you as an adult.
Well, I would not even know where to begin
to get something like that off the ground.
- I would. I could help you.
- Really?
Yeah. I, um, converted our garage
into a little office for Audrey that, uh,
she later went on to have sex
with Adolf Eichmann's great-grandson in.
[chuckles] Wow. You did that yourself?
I did. Over the course of a bunch of
weekends, but yeah. It wasn't a big deal.
Wow, look at you.
You're, like, a secret man.
Why's it a secret that I'm a man?
Because you wear ladies' hats,
and you have a purse.
And you're wearing some very pretty nail
polish, and we're having a slumber party.
- Yeah, that makes sense.
- [chuckles]
- When you cheated on Audrey, did you...
- I did not cheat,
uh, I hooked up with a rando.
Please, some respect.
- [groans] Pardon me.
- Yeah.
- Uh, when you hooked up with a rando...
- Thank you.
...did... did Audrey drive you to do that?
Like, did she drop me off
at the rando's condo in Laguna Hill?
Yeah. Did she take you there?
- That's so nice.
- Oh, you mean,
like, figuratively speaking? [chuckles]
No. Did she treat you in a way
that made you wanna act out?
You know, at the time,
I would've said yes.
Uh... [chuckles] ...but I was just
justifying bad behavior, you know?
Um, as much as we fought,
it was a shitty thing to do,
and I wouldn't do that again.
Do you think it ended your marriage?
No. Definitely not.
Our marriage was doomed way before that.
If we actually...
If we had a better marriage,
we could've worked through that, you know?
[inhales deeply, sighs]
Why do you have all these questions?
[breathes deeply] Uh,
I, uh... I am thinking of writing a novel.
- Really?
- Mmm.
Let me be the first to tell you
it sounds genuinely awful.
[both chuckle]
It's called Before Adolf.
- Yes. Oh, good. Perfect. "R" for Rando.
- [laughing]
- Whoa. Gummies are starting to hit.
- Hey. Those gummies be hittin', yo.
- I'm gonna need some fries.
- [knocking]
I had that same thought 20 minutes ago.
- What?
- You can thank me later!
Ring-a-ding-ding.
- Morning.
- [clears throat]
Hi.
[Maeve] I like your picture.
- [Charlie] Good morning.
- How'd you sleep?
Ah, pretty well. Uh, Maeve and Shelby came
into our room a couple of times,
but, you know...
[yawns] ...I'm still alive.
Uh, did you and Will have a nice night?
Yeah. Actually,
Will had a really interesting idea.
What if he converted the garage
into a guest room?
[chuckles]
What? What's so funny? I could design it.
Wait, you're serious? Wha...
What do we need a guesthouse for?
Aren't we trying to move?
Well, it could be useful
until we find a new place.
It doesn't have to be for guests.
- It's just extra square footage.
- Wait, how will that even help us?
It's not like we can move one of
the kids into the garage.
- I could use it as an office.
- An office for what?
Uh...
Yes, it sounds like a good plan.
Thank you.
- Morning.
[laughs] I smell coffee.
- Coffee?
- Yeah, thank you. Charles?
- [Charlie] Yes?
- I have a lawyerly question for you.
I'm in a fight with my business partners.
See, they started, like,
a side business without me,
and I should very much be a part of it.
What do I do?
Um, well, the first thing you need to do
is negotiate with them separately.
That way, you can divide and conquer.
Ooh, I like that.
- He's good.
- Mmm.
You wanna hang out this afternoon
and chop it up about the ADU?
Charlie loves the idea.
- Really? You saw the light?
- Yep. Yeah.
Love it. Well, adieu. Get it?
- ADU?
- Oh, ADU.
- [chuckling] I do. I do.
- I do. Hey, you do get it.
Is Will wearing my clothes?
Would you prefer he wore mine?
[Sylvia]
Hey, Will, you wanna get pancakes?
Look, I don't feel comfortable talking
about business without Reggie here.
Who got you your first job as a barback?
- All right, you did.
- Look, Reggie might know about money,
and I will give him that,
and he is good at that.
But he knows nothing about
actually starting a liquor company,
and I know about that. I can actually...
I can get you guys more cash
if you cut me into this shit, okay?
Okay. Look, I'll talk to Reggie.
We'll set something up for tomorrow.
We can figure something out. Cool?
- Very cool. Thank you. Yes.
- We good? Okay. I love that.
Now, more importantly, I know we just ate,
but that unagi truck is open today,
and I'm on the wait-list. So what's up?
I can't. I told Sylvia I'd go meet her.
[chuckling] How is she?
What does that mean?
Uh, what are you... I mean...
Nah, it's all good. Never mind.
What do you mean, "never mind"?
You said it like...
[stammers] You clearly said it
with meaning.
- It's nothing.
- What... It's something.
- It's not.
- [stammers] It is clearly something.
- What the fuck is going on?
- Okay, look, I can't tell you.
This is intel from Katie.
Sylvia told her in confidence,
and I can't air my baby's shit out.
That is what it is.
- It's too late! You've already told me.
- I have not told you.
- You've betrayed your baby!
- I haven't.
- Your baby's been betrayed. Tell me.
- She hasn't.
I'm your baby.
Okay. [chuckles] All right, I'ma tell you.
So the other night,
Charlie was working late with some girl.
- He got drunk and...
- Oh, my God. Charlie cheated on Sylvia?
No, they dry humped.
- What?
- They dry humped.
They dry humped?
Dry humped.
Was there kissing?
- Dry humped.
- Touch his dick?
Dry humped.
Did he cream his jeans?
No, because that would be wet.
This was dry. Just dry hump.
- That is so weird.
- [chuckles] I know, right?
- That is...
- It's fucked up.
Me and Katie have
gone deep on it, bro. It's really strange.
It is very strange.
- It's really strange.
- What a weird thing to do.
Is that even cheating?
I mean, it's not, like, cheating,
but it's not not cheating.
[stammers] I would not like my partner
out there dry humping motherfuckers.
- It kinda feels worse.
- 'Cause it's weirder.
It is.
And it would make sense from Charlie,
because he's, like, this handsome guy,
and he's super nice. No one's like that.
It's true. He seems like the deprivation
of wetness would kinda get him off.
- Weirdo.
- The dryness is part of the allure.
Friction.
- Wow. I wonder why Sylvia didn't tell me.
- Yeah.
What do you mean?
It's fucking embarrassing.
- True.
- Didn't think he had it in him,
to be honest with you, but...
He didn't have it in him.
- He was dry humping. It was dry.
- [chuckling]
Yo.
- Hi. How did it go with Andy?
- Hello.
It was good. It was good to talk to him.
Good, good. Glad to hear.
Yeah. How you doing?
- Good.
- Yeah? You okay?
Why?
Um, Andy, uh... [chuckles]
I mean, he mentioned to me
what happened with Charlie.
Oh. [stammers] That's nothing.
- Really?
- [stammers] Yeah. I, uh...
You know, it just...
It happened one time. It's not
gonna happen again, and we're fine.
- Do you wanna talk about it at all?
- No, I'm good.
All right.
So, I was thinking
that this would be great for me
if we could turn it into an office space.
All right. What, uh...
What exactly are you looking for?
[sighs] Um, you know,
like over-stuffed sofas,
cashmere blankets, things like that.
Okay. So, like a she shed?
No, like an elevated office space.
You want, like,
little chandeliers everywhere,
maybe a small fridge with rosé in it,
- magazine racks with Us Weekly, Cosmo?
- Ooh.
That sounds amazing.
That's a basic-bitch she shed.
Hate to break it to you.
- Wow. Nice.
- Yes.
Bigger than I thought.
Yeah. So? I mean,
obviously needs some work,
but it's got some potential, right?
This will make a great taco trove.
Okay.
- Hmm. That's strange.
- What?
These posts aren't fastened
to the foundation in any real way.
Oh. That doesn't sound very good.
This whole thing is actually just
being held up by these four things,
and they're really not
attached to anything.
- Huh.
- It's okay. We can...
We can reinforce them.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. It'll be fine.
- Okay.
- It'll be fine.
- [metallic clattering]
- Do you hear that?
Uh, uh, yeah.
- [chittering]
- [screams]
- [screaming] Oh! Oh, my God!
- Ah! Fuck! Help! Help! Fuck!
Oh, my God! Shit! Oh, my God! [screaming]
[Will screams] Get out!
Get the fuck outta here!
[screams] He's on the door! I can't!
[screams]
- [both screaming]
- [shed crumbling]
Oh, shit. Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
- That's... That's a structural problem.
- Oh, no.
- That's not good. Are you okay?
- Oh, my God.
- I'm okay. Oh, fuck, are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- Look at my house!
- What happened?
You won't fucking believe
what happened, man.
- A raccoon jumped on me...
- Oh, my God.
- ...I knocked into the poles...
- Then the thing fell down.
- ...and it fell.
- A racc... What?
I don't think this was permitted properly.
- [Sylvia] ...an earthquake.
- This is not what I expected.
- That makes one of us.
- [Sylvia] Me either.
- No, but we... we can figure it out.
- It'll be okay.
Can you... Can you figure this out? Really?
- Yes!
- I, 100%, cannot fix this.
Really? It doesn't seem like
you can figure this out.
- I can't.
- It's okay. We have this under control.
Honestly? Because destroying our house
is not the best way of dealing
with being upset.
You don't get to tell me
how to deal with my feelings.
[inhales deeply] Can we please talk
about this alone?
I'm gonna go.
Come on. You don't have to go.
You know, your husband said
he wanted to talk to you alone. It's fine.
[Sylvia] The ADU was your idea.
Now that you've destroyed my garage,
you gotta help me fix it.
[Will] I'll come back and I'll...
I'll help another time.
But in the meantime, uh,
deal with your shit.
Excuse me. That was a small argument
that happens over the course
of a long marriage. It's fine.
But I guess that's something
you might not understand.
It does not seem fine.
[sighs]
[Sylvia] Oh, my God. [sighs]
Well, this looks good.
Babe, I'm sorry.
I know.
You know what happened
between Vanessa and me
was in no way, shape or form your fault.
[sighs] Thank you.
And you know that
this has nothing to do with Vanessa.
And you know that that doesn't
make me feel any better, right?
I do, I do, and I'm sorry.
I just...
What?
[sighs] It's nothing.
Just tell me, babe, please. What?
I don't like feeling like the
second-most important man in your life.
- You mean, after Simon? [chuckles]
- [chuckles]
- Okay, the third-most important...
- Hey.
...man in your life.
[Sylivia] I just...
I think since Maeve's gone back
to school full-time,
I just feel, um, a little bit of a mess.
And for some reason, it's easier to talk
to Will about it than to talk to you.
That doesn't make me feel great.
I know. I wanna tell you everything first.
You're my husband, but I don't know.
For some reason, it's just hard.
Why? I love you so much.
- You can tell me anything.
- I know.
Because it's embarrassing being a mess
in front of you,
and Will's a much bigger mess than I am,
or at least an equal mess. I don't know.
- Okay. Yeah, I... Yeah, I...
- Does that make any sense?
I get it. Kind of.
Thank you.
[sighs]
And next time you, like,
dry hump with someone,
would you mind doing it with someone just,
like, slightly less accomplished?
Mmm, like Judge Sotomayor?
No, that's the wrong direction.
- [chuckles] I promise. I promise.
- [chuckles]
So...
- [Sylvia] What are we going to do?
- I don't know. [chuckles]
What's the deal with the new listing?
When can we see the house?
"This weekend," she said.
Yeah, I'm sure it'll be the one.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
[chitters]
- Oh, my God. This guy again.
- Aw.
- This guy, huh? Oh, it's not cute.
- Aw. Oh, it's cute.
It's cute. [strains]
It's cute, and I got ya.
- You're cute.
- Aw. You're cute.
- [chuckles] Hmm? Hey?
- [chuckles]
Okay, what's this?
That is a list of names for our
hard kombucha company that I approve of.
- Kombucha Cha-Cha?
- Kombu Cha-Cha Cha.
Oh, like the legendary Afro-Cuban dance.
Exactly. If you don't like that,
there's plenty more on the list.
- [chuckles] I kinda like Boochy Call.
- [Reggie] What? No, dude.
Daa Booch is the perfect fucking name.
We're not changing anything.
Come on.
You're the one who called me over here
and said we were gonna
talk things through.
Also, who the fuck is this guy?
- No one.
- Yeah, he's just a guy.
- He's just a guy?
- [Andy] Mmm.
Is this an intervention?
Is this guy an "interventionalist"?
No, he's not that.
This guy drinks more than I do.
You don't wanna know the shit
this motherfucker gets up to.
Also, I'm not going to rehab
unless it's that place in Malibu.
That place actually looks really...
It's right on the water, right?
This isn't about drinking, Will.
This is just business.
So it's not an intervention?
Nah, dude.
Clark, he's just here to listen.
Is he a fucking professional listener?
What is happening right now?
Will, you have done an incredible job
getting Lucky Penny up and running.
We think that maybe
it's time you take a step away.
Why are we talking
about Lucky Penny right now?
Bro, this shit ain't working, okay?
You gotta go.
- Are you guys trying to force me out?
- Yes.
No, he can't be forced out. He has to
voluntarily decide to do this on his own.
Why is he correcting you?
Is this guy a fucking lawyer?
Yes, I am a lawyer.
Ah, bro, you didn't have to
disclose that information.
Yes, I do.
Will, look.
You know I love you, all right?
But we disagree about everything, bro.
We disagree about
what fucking beers to make.
We disagree about who to partner with.
It's ridiculous.
I'm sorry I didn't want to partner
with a geriatric sexual predator.
No, fuck Johnny Rev, okay?
It's about more than that.
Like I said, it's everything, bro.
You cannot take this bar away from me.
This place is my life.
I built it from nothing.
Nobody's trying to take
the bar away from you.
Besides, we legally can't do that.
- Yeah, we legally can't do that.
- See?
Like, it's not that surprising
coming from him because he sucks.
I genuinely expected more from you, man.
How could you do this to me?
- No, Will...
- Where you going, dawg?
I am not going anywhere,
'cause this is my bar.
That is my beer.
You are never getting rid of me.
That went a lot better than I thought.
What did you think would happen, Omar?
I don't know, physical stuff.
Karate, knife play. You know, like a show.
Have you ever had Johnny Blue?
No.
My motto, "Work hard, play hard."
There's nothing in there.
Yeah... [stutters] ...I
can fucking see that.
Or we could just drink one of these.
No, no. Just get the fuck out.
Get out, get out.
["Work Hard, Play Hard" playing]
[mumbles indistinctly]