[door opens]
- [Jason groaning]
- [footsteps approaching]
[grunting]
[breathes shakily]
- Where are they?
- Wha... I came looking for my family.
Just... Just like you.
Oh, yeah?
[Jason groaning]
Hey.
- [screams]
- I was there when you got this.
You're the one who
did this to me.
[sniffling]
To all of us.
At the bare minimum, I'm as smart
as you, so don't fuck with me.
Where are they?
[breathing heavily] Okay.
I'm... I'm sorry. I'm so s...
Fuck you. I don't want
your fucking apology.
Tell me where they are!
Oh, fuck. I don't know.
[groaning]
Oh, fuck.
Where are they?
Daniela found out.
- [groans]
- Of course she did.
She's the one who pushed
me down the stairs.
And I... [breathes shakily] I don't
know where she is now. I swear.
- So you're fucking useless to me?
- I'm sorry.
[groaning]
[phone chimes]
[chiming continues]
[sighs]
[phone buzzes]
Mom.
Let's turn them off, okay?
[Daniela sighs]
When I came back, I thought
I'd only have him to deal with.
I should've known
there would be more.
So where do we go?
I really don't know.
Credit cards can be tracked.
No one really
takes cash anymore.
And even if I had an idea, I
can't be the one to choose.
Why?
'Cause any place he would
think of, they could too.
I have an idea.
[Charlie] Uh, that's
the one. That's the one.
[door unlocks]
[security alarm blaring]
- [keypad beeping]
- [alarm stops] And you just happen to know the security code?
James's family spends their
summers... most weekends here.
- I visited a couple of times.
- Couple of times?
I think he's been here more
than a couple of times.
[sighs]
How's your room?
I should have protected her.
[inhales deeply] Charlie...
I should've protected
both of you.
None of this is your fault.
You know that, right?
Are they really all my dad?
[breathes deeply]
Yes and no.
[sighs] So what do we do?
We figure it out...
once we get some sleep.
[sighs]
[Jason] Hey.
Do you wanna be alone?
[inhales deeply]
I can't imagine the
things that you've seen, all the things you had to do to get back to us.
I want it...
to just be as simple
as you're home, we go back to the way we were...
but they're all home too.
[inhales deeply, sighs]
[whispers] I don't
know where to start.
[grunts]
Guess just like after Max.
Somehow we just have to start.
[gasps]
None of you have been through
what I've been through.
You haven't earned it.
You know, we... we can't all
have them obviously, so...
the question is, who
gets stuck alone?
What if we tried joint custody?
[computer chimes]
[bird calling in distance]
[inhales sharply]
- [water lapping]
- [bird twittering]
[sighs]
At first, I liked the
way he made me feel.
It was like we had
gone back to the start.
But he wasn't my husband.
He lived with us, slept with me.
That's all I wanna
say right now.
I'm sorry.
[exhales heavily]
I loved our life, but there were times that I thought, "What if?"
Not a constant
thing, but sometimes.
This other Jason, he is, to some degree, me.
So my what-ifs are also in him.
They led him to this world.
None of it's your fault.
You know, I met a version of
you that never married me.
[chuckles] Yeah?
What did I do?
You're an artist.
I met you at the opening
for your newest show.
You lived in a really
cool loft, and...
you had a lot of friends.
No kids?
No.
Was I happy?
She wondered the same about you.
[exhales sharply]
No hotel charges, no
airline tickets, no Airbnb, no rental cars, but he buys fucking gas at Schaumburg.
And they take $500
out of the ATM.
Where'd he go?
Come on. You should be
able to work this out.
Wherever he would
go, you would know.
So you don't make the decision
because it's too predictable.
I know Daniela too well.
They'll let Charlie do it.
Oh, fuck.
Is there any chance you haven't
powered your phones down?
[bangs on table]
[sighs]
Where's my phone?
[breathes heavily]
[breathes shakily]
Where's my phone? The one that you
took from me under the train tracks.
[exhales heavily]
Where is my phone?
Where is it?
Listen, cut me loose.
I'll help you find it.
Why don't I just cut you?
[grunts] No. Look.
[groans]
[Jason] Gotcha.
Sorry...
[sighs]
[Daniela] We should
check on Charlie.
Daniela?
[sighs]
Uh, last night, I
found a message board with hundreds of Jasons who'd made it back.
What were they saying?
As damaged as some of them have
become, they all love their family.
They want you back.
One of them had an idea.
[chuckles]
Kind of a lottery system, where apparently one of us gets to stay in this world with you and Charlie.
Everyone else leaves.
Well, whoever had that
idea just lost the lottery.
Another suggested
shared custody.
Wow.
Holidays will be a nightmare.
[chuckles]
Hey.
So what happened to you?
What happened to me?
Yeah.
After you kidnapped me and played out a sick dad fantasy with my son and raped my wife?
[Jason groans]
I'll tell you what happened.
Your Daniela is dead.
What?
How?
Well, it was my fault.
Actually...
it was your fault.
Because I didn't know the kind of
people that you were involved with.
[sighs]
Dawn killed her because
she was trying to help me.
Oh, and Leighton
had Ryan killed.
And then there's Amanda, who you abandoned.
She helped me escape in the
box, and she was very confused and disoriented and scared.
And as you know, they're
not the kind of feelings you're supposed to have when you open the door.
The sixth door that we
opened was a big forest.
We just stepped outside
just to have a look.
And...
there had been a fire, I
guess. It was very black.
Blackened, you know?
And so when a wind came, it just
started knocking trees down.
This branch fell and...
well, one hit me on the head, but a
really big one just came and went...
[imitates zipping]
right through her.
Pinned her to the ground.
And there was just nothing
that I could do about it...
except just sit there and
wait for it to all be over.
[sighs]
That took two days.
[exhales heavily]
[sniffles]
Is... Is that hers?
Amanda's?
She would've done
anything for you.
One hundred percent. Anything.
Do you want to see what
other damage you've caused?
[sighs]
- Yeah, and it just goes on.
- [laptop lid snaps shut]
[breathes shakily]
I just thought...
What did you think?
It doesn't matter.
Look at me.
I would really like to know.
I thought...
[sobs, sniffs]
I thought that...
you would love... love my life.
[scoffs, chuckles]
[sighs]
- [phone chimes]
- [clicks tongue] [Jason] What else?
[Charlie groans]
Brooke and Drew are dating.
Oh, I'm sorry, pal.
Smells good in here.
Yeah, I found some slightly expired
pancake mix and a can of condensed milk.
Okay. I like our chances
with expired pancakes.
[Charlie chuckles]
What'd I miss?
Well, I am catching up on current
events at the Dessen household.
Speaking of which, what happened to that show that you were trying to land?
Don Good at Artspace got it.
We are batting 1,000 here.
Any good news?
You got me a car
for my birthday.
- Yes, I heard.
- Excellent Blackhawks tickets.
New skateboards.
- [Daniela] Ice cream with nuts.
- What?
[groans] Yeah, you almost
killed me. [chuckles]
Nah, but seriously, you didn't
know how to use an EpiPen.
He wouldn't have known
about your allergy.
- [Charlie] Yeah.
- [Jason] Huh.
[Charlie] Or Max. He missed
our time by the tree.
[sniffs] Well, he's a dick.
[Charlie chuckles]
Coffee?
- I'd love some.
- [Jason] Yeah? Same?
The thing about these
is they make you think, "Why would you ever want a fresh pancake?"
[Daniela, Jason laughing]
- Okay. Why are you doing this to me?
- It was perfect.
- [Jason] Thank you.
- [Daniela] Thank you for breakfast.
You're welcome. But
what's the plan?
Don't really know yet. Just that
we have to leave here tomorrow.
Why?
Well, we're currently
home invaders and thieves.
- Did you take something?
- [chuckles] I just love how your mind just went straight to me.
Well, you did kind of
thieve my best friend's car.
She kind of let me borrow it.
Doesn't seem like there's really a plan
to give it back to her anytime soon.
[Jason] Well, we might need it.
So, where will we go?
We're working on it.
[doorbell ringing]
[door opens, creaks]
Hello?
Daniela?
Charlie?
Hello?
[thudding]
[Jason grunts]
Hello?
[thudding]
[Jason breathing heavily]
[Blair] Jason?
I know this seems very strange, but for Daniela's sake, I need you to do something for me.
What?
Can you track your
car's location?
Can you? Can you track
your car's location?
Yes.
Have you?
No. It didn't occur
to me to track.
- All right. Give me your phone.
- That would be a solid "fuck off."
- Blair, just give me your phone. [groans]
- [groans] [Jason] I'm not gonna hurt you.
[breathing heavily, sniffs]
Just give me your fucking phone.
Blair, give it to me!
Okay.
[screaming]
- [Blair grunts]
- [Jason groaning]
[both grunting]
- Sit down. Now!
- Yeah, fine. Yeah.
[groaning]
[groans, gasps]
- Now...
- [Jason groans] what the actual fuck is going on?
[Daniela] Where are they?
The other realities.
Imagine you're a fish,
swimming in a lake.
And to you, that lake
is your entire universe.
Then one day, someone reaches in and pulls you out of the water, and you realize that what you thought was your entire world is just one lake.
Then you see another
lake and trees and the sky above.
And it suddenly hits
you that you are...
We all are part of a
more mysterious reality than we could ever possibly understand.
So, they're just all around us and we can't see them?
[Jason] They're right here.
So close, just microns away.
And if our consciousness
were more fluid, we could literally reach out and touch 'em.
[wine pouring]
[Jason sighs]
Were there any worlds...
where you were tempted to stay?
Out there in the
box, I almost...
almost lost hope of
finding my way home.
There was one world where
I thought I could be happy.
But you came home.
Do you regret it?
Not one bit.
["Sparks" playing]
[sighing]
[TV playing indistinctly]
[Jason, Charlie chuckling]
- [Jason] Ask another question.
- [Charlie chuckles]
[knocking]
[Jason] Hey. Come in.
We're just chatting.
[Charlie chuckles]
Okay, now this just feels
suspiciously like a tuck-in.
Aw. What, you too old
for a tuck-in, huh?
- Huh? [chuckles]
- [chuckles] [Daniela] Thank you for bringing us here, Charlie.
Considering this is pretty scary,
you're handling it with real bravery.
I'm very proud of you, pal.
Night, kiddo.
[Charlie] Good night.
All right.
[song continues]
Do you remember
when we first met?
Mm-hmm.
Could have been anyone...
but it was you.
And out of all of them, again it was you.
I went on the message board.
I told them we made a choice.
I don't want a lottery.
I choose you.
[water runs, stops]
[panting]
- [person shouts]
- [gasps]
[panting]
[bird calling]
[breathing heavily]
- [person grunts]
- [Jason] Oh, shit.
[grunting, groaning]
[groans]
[groaning, gasping] Help me.
Who did this to you?
One... One of us. [grunts]
How many are here?
Am I gonna die? I
don't wanna die.
[Jason] How many?
Get Charlie. [sobs]
Where's Charlie? [groans]
[Jason] Hey!
- [gunshot]
- [grunts] Oh, fuck.
[breathing heavily] Plea...
[panting]
- Was that a gunshot?
- [Jason] Shh!
Get Charlie. Meet me back
downstairs. Hurry! Hurry!
[Jason] Hey.
Drop it.
I said drop it.
Listen...
Just stop. Stop.
[sniffs]
[breathing heavily]
Are they upstairs?
[Jason] Yeah.
Okay. Take off all your clothes.
Now. I'm not gonna
tell you again. Just...
Come on.
Everything.
Do you have a safe word?
Yeah.
Give it to me.
How many have you killed?
I don't know. [mumbles]
Safe word.
- [shotgun cocks]
- [Jason gasps] Okay. I'll tell you.
It's...
[both grunting, groaning]
- [gunshot]
- [Jason groans]
[gunshot]
[groans]
[breathing heavily]
[Daniela gasps]
Daniela, take
Charlie and go. Go!
[breathing heavily]
Not without you.
I'm not gonna stop you.
It's not why I'm here.
[breathing shakily]
I'm the one who built the box.
I'm the one responsible
for all of this mess.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry to all of you.
- [grunts]
- [Jason] Charlie!
Fuck.
How did you find us?
Blair had a tracking
app on her phone.
How did the others find you?
One of them put this
device on the Honda, and I didn't realize it until the others started showing up.
They followed me.
- [gunshot]
- [Daniela gasps] - [groaning in distance] - What the fuck?
You have to leave.
[breathing shakily]
It's outside.
Please. I am trying to help you.
All right. Well,
show us where it is.
Okay.
[car door shuts]
[Jason] Jason.
This belongs to you.
- [gunshots]
- [Jason] Go. Go!
[Jason] Daniela! Charlie!
- [shouting]
- [Jason] Get down!
- [Daniela screams]
- [gunshots] - [gunshots] - [groaning]
[panting]
Are you good? You okay?
[groans]
I don't think
anyone followed us.
What do we do? There's
nowhere for us to go.
Guys, I think he
left us something.
[object clicks]
[Jason] Uh, how many are there?
I don't know. Forty?
[Charlie] There's
a bag here too.
He brought Max.
[breathing shakily]
[gasps]
[Charlie] And there's this here.
[Jason] When I went into the
box, I was filled with regret.
And then one day, I
walked into a world and I found a family that had been created through a choice that I had been too scared to make.
I was burning with envy.
At first, I thought it was
all about you, Daniela.
And while some of it was, I realized what I really wanted, what I tried to steal, were the choices that you made, Jason.
Mostly the choice to
allow space in your life for someone else's needs and dreams.
I think there's a
part of us... me...
that's been afraid to risk love.
And my whole life, I've
let that fear control me.
But somehow you broke free of it and gifted yourself a full, messy and beautiful life.
There's no apology sufficient
for what I've done.
This world is no longer
safe for any of you.
And I hope you can find a new home,
and I'm sure you will, because...
well, you've all been through
things I can't imagine, and they've shaped you into an even more perfect puzzle that can only fit one another.
[Charlie] You're sure
this is the only way?
If we stay, we have
to live in fear.
She's right.
Wait.
[alternate Jasons]
Look. There they are.
Hey. Hey, look. Daniela.
Shit. That's him.
Where's he going?
They're here.
We didn't come to stop you.
We figured that your only chance at a
normal life was to leave this world.
[Jasons] Yeah.
He's right. Uh-huh.
We came to say goodbye.
I'm sorry.
I just want you and
Charlie to be safe.
[Jasons] Yeah.
And you...
take care of them.
[Jasons] Yeah.
No, no! No! Why... Why
should he get them?
It's not about him.
It's about what she wants, and what's best for our son.
[sighs, sniffs]
Let 'em through.
No.
Let 'em through!
Move!
[Jasons murmuring]
[Jasons] Charlie. Charlie.
[sniffing]
Daniela.
[Daniela breathing heavily]
["Roost" playing]
[song continues]
Do you know me?
No...
but I've been looking for you.
[song fades]
["If You Want To Sing
Out, Sing Out" playing]