[engine starts]
[van door opens]
[van door closes]
[Lauren] Do you
like women, Jimmy?
What do you think?
I love 'em.
Yeah?
[clears throat]
What do you like about them?
Everything.
I got sisters.
[sighs]
Women are more…
kind.
I can chill with a woman in a
way I never could with a dude.
I can just be.
But what do you like about them?
I like this.
I'm not saying anything's
gonna happen, but…
possibility's there.
What don't you like about women?
Nothing.
What do you think Larry Hall
doesn't like about women?
How the fuck do I know?
So, what good are you to me?
You show me you can find
common ground with this man,
or you are wasting my time.
[sighs]
[Brian, muffled] You said
you dreamed of killing women?
You said you dreamed
of killing women.
[normal voice] Larry.
What? I dre... Oh, uh,
it's not like that.
No, I... I don't dream
of killing women.
I just have a lot of
dreams from killing them.
You know. And, uh, G-Gary says that
he has a lot of dreams about falling.
Uh-huh. Who's Gary?
My twin.
Mm-hmm.
[chuckles] G-Gary
also once told me
that he has a lot of
dreams about drowning.
But not killing women, right?
That's more your thing.
And tell me what these
dreams are like, Larry.
The dreams are like...
It's like, um…
[breathes heavily]
I'm kinda looking down on
myself, like I'm not in my body.
Do you remember what your
body is doing, Larry?
I can't tell you exactly.
I only remember that
it's something bad.
[Brian] Mm-hmm. Where
women are being killed?
Sometimes.
Yeah.
[Brian sniffs]
Do any of the women
look like her?
[chuckles]
She in any of your dreams?
I wanna go home now.
[Brian] Okay, is she, Larry?
Hmm?
I wanna go home, Chris.
Larry, just look
at the photo here.
- [stammers] I wanna go home.
- Okay, but is she...
- I wanna go home.
- Okay, I'll take you home.
- I'll take you home.
- [Larry] Okay.
- [Chris] Larry, it's okay.
- It's okay.
Can I talk to you outside?
It's okay. We're good.
We got him in there
talking about his dreams.
That's all they are.
We don't have anything.
- Because you didn't let me get it.
- [Chris] Larry talks big. That's it.
He did the same thing with
us in the Reitler case.
Well, if your high-end detective skills
can't be trusted, whose can, right?
- Don't fucking talk to me like that.
- I agree. Your tone's not helping.
Detective Miller, I appreciate
your passion here. I do.
But we do have our guy
in the Reitler case.
And it's as open and shut
as I've seen in ten years.
Why not go back to Illinois, build
your case for the Roach girl,
then come back to Indiana
where she was found
and take another run at Hall?
None of us would object to that.
We'll respect your sandbox,
and you respect ours.
[indistinct chatter]
Fuck your sandbox.
I don't know.
It was the way he said,
"Come back to Indiana
where she was found."
[Lauren] Made you think what?
Made me think they could steal
the case right out from under me.
- On what grounds?
- Thanks.
[gasps]
Well, Jessica Roach was
abducted in Illinois.
Probably killed there
too. That's inconclusive.
She was found, though, in Perrysville,
Indiana, and that is conclusive.
So, they can claim jurisdiction.
Yeah.
Except…
No, no, no, no. You
say it. Your moment.
Our suspect crossed state lines
to kill her, so, you know…
Federal.
Yeah.
Well, most US attorneys,
they don't try murder cases.
When they do, they've been known
to get their asses handed to them.
But, but, but Hulin just brought
in an assassin, Edmund Beaumont.
He used to be state's. Tried
a ton of capital crimes.
Hulin likes you?
Seems to.
Put a bug in her
ear about Beaumont.
If Hulin agrees to bring us in,
and she puts Beaumont on it…
Brian, you got a shot at
slamming the door on this guy.
Mark will lead the interview.
If Hall throat-kills women, I
don't want Lauren in the room.
Might spook him.
I have a guy I'd like
to use for the poly.
Mark could do the poly.
When are you cleared to part us?
[Mark] I'm in court all week.
Then let's do the 15th?
It's a lot of time for
things to go wrong.
Marion or Wabash could claim jurisdiction
at any time. Hall could get a lawyer.
Jackrabbit, take
off, kill again.
You brought this to us. This
is how we're gonna do it.
[chuckles]
What are you smiling about?
I think you already
picked me for the job.
Yeah?
Yeah, I'm not sure there
ever was anybody else.
I got black belts in
karate and tae kwon do,
and I'm… charming.
And you're so bashful about it.
- You think it'll endear you to Hall?
- Possibly.
Maybe he'll wanna hang
out with the cool guy.
[chuckles]
Here's your competition, Jimmy.
Won a boxing championship
while serving with the
Rangers during Desert Storm.
So, I think he can
handle himself.
Personable,
non-threatening demeanor,
and he doesn't have an
ego that announces itself
half an hour before he
enters a fucking room.
- So, pick him.
- Beaumont wants to.
You are full of yourself, and you
are full of shit. That's all he sees.
- Yeah, that's all you tell him.
- 'Cause that's pretty much all I see.
Wh-Why'd your parents divorce?
Uh... [chuckles]
They had too much fire and
passion, but they loved us,
- and they wondered what we...
- Bullshit.
Look, I didn't get along
with my stepfather, okay,
but I could care less
if my parents were...
Bullshit!
Don't fucking waste my time.
Oh, are you...
You're leaving now?
All right, come on. My
mother fucked around.
I think.
My old man was always
drinking, never home.
And he might have
been on the take,
so it was like growing
up in an earthquake.
We didn't have any
choice in any of it.
They just did what they did,
and we had to… take it.
That house was a
fucking horror show.
Must have been lonely.
It was what it was.
If you end up in with Hall,
I want you to remember
who you were at eight.
Tap into it. Feel it.
Wear it like skin.
I don't like that skin.
Hall doesn't like his either.
Where are you with the file?
I…
Yeah, I've been looking at the
Jessica Roach killing again,
and I… I have a question.
How'd she die? It's blacked out.
She was strangled.
But how?
- He used his hands, or rope? What?
- You tell me if you talk to him.
But you know.
I know.
Larry, thanks for coming down.
- Hey.
- Brought along a colleague.
This is Agent
Ellenberg from the FBI.
Glad to meet you, Mr. Hall.
I'm Larry. Just call me Larry.
Oh, well, call me Mark.
Mark.
Do you need anything?
Water? Soda?
Mmm, water would be nice, yeah.
Want a water? Yeah, um...
Yeah, let me get that.
Wanna have a seat?
[Mark clears throat]
[Larry groans]
Wha-What-What is this?
Uh, waiver of rights.
It just says you're okay,
uh, talking with me,
answering a few questions.
Do you mind if I look
over it for a bit?
Oh, sure. Sure.
[Larry breathing deeply]
Mmm… [sighs]
Uh, this is consent
for the polygraph.
I ca... I can't take that.
Why not?
Because I don't
believe I'll pass.
[whistles]
[Mark] Mmm, why
do you think that?
- [door opens]
- It would...
- Here you go.
- [Larry] Thank you.
[Brian clears throat]
Could you just do...
Would you mind leaving? I ju...
Your energy makes me feel itchy.
Sure thing, Larry.
[sighs]
[Larry] You know, I am sorry.
I'm just so tired right now.
I'm afraid to sleep.
[stutters] I have
nightmares all the time,
and I… and I get
depressed, like, bad.
[Mark] Have you seen
anyone about that?
Yeah, I went to a
counselor once, but it...
He was young.
And he wasn't very helpful.
Yeah.
Well, uh, besides the nightmares,
what else depresses you?
I'm... I'm very lonely.
That's hard.
Yeah, it is hard. Like,
I wa... I wake up alone.
I g-go to work alone.
I go to bed alone.
Some other guys,
they have women.
They go to movies. They
eat pizza together.
And you wish you had that?
A woman who loved you.
[breathes shakily] Yes.
But you don't feel that's possible?
You don't think women like you?
N-No. No.
So… [sighs]
Wh-what do you do with the
urge… to be with a woman?
Always push it down.
It's gotta be hard.
And it's probably what
causes the nightmares.
You know, you push it down, it climbs
right back up into your dreams.
Yeah, th-that's why I do such awful
things in my nightmares, it...
That's all that they are, though.
It's just dreams, you know.
She wasn't in your dreams,
Larry. She was in your reality.
I thou... I thought she
was. I thought she was.
No.
Can I touch her?
[Mark] Sure.
Tell me how you met her.
She was riding her bike,
and, uh, I drove up and
I stopped to talk to her.
She was so very nice, you
know. Very nice at first.
[Mark] And then she wasn't?
[Larry] No, she was always nice.
It's just that she...
She got sad, real sad.
[Mark] Well, when was this?
[Larry] When she was... When
she was sad, she was in m...
Uh... When she was in my van.
And then, uh,
later in the field…
The field in Georgetown?
Yeah, it wa... in
Perrysville, Indiana.
Oh, right, um… Do you
remember where exactly?
I do remember where it was exactly. It
was just past mile marker 16 on 1125.
Normally, I wouldn't remember
that. I might not remember it, but…
I… [sighs] …didn't
have time to bury her,
so I had to drive
past a few more times.
Tried to find an opportunity,
but I never found it.
It didn't happen.
I mean, normally I
bury all of them.
Them?
The girls.
How many have there been?
It's... There...
[sighs] It's, uh, a few.
You know, I... [sighs] I'm...
I just do things.
I'm not... I'm not in control.
It's like that girl in
Marion. The college girl.
Now, you know her name, Larry.
Tricia Reitler, yes.
You know, the Marion Police
arrested another man in that case.
He didn't do it.
Oh.
There was one in Wisconsin,
near one of the reenactments,
and some in Indiana.
I can't remember
which ones I hurt.
It's just... I'm so
tired all the time.
I'm always tired, you
know, and... and sad.
[inhales deeply]
And what I don't like
is this guy in Marion
trying to take
credit for my act.
He didn't fold the clothes.
He didn't fold the
clothes, did he?
- No.
Because he didn't break the zipper,
and he didn't feel bad about it.
And that's why I
folded the clothes.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
I need a, uh, confession
form and a computer.
I'll set you up in
the bullpen. [sighs]
What... What's... What's
this about the clothes?
Tricia Reitler's clothes were found
in a park about 10 miles from campus.
That, and a bloody earring
was ripped from her ear,
her blood was on her jeans,
and her zipper was broken where her
jeans had been taken off of her.
- She fought him.
- None of this is public information.
- We need a warrant on his home.
- [Lauren] On it.
And on his vehicles.
You're a county
sheriff's investigator.
I'm Chief Investigator.
And you just reeled
in a serial killer.
Well, we haven't done
shit yet. Let's close him.
You're all set.
- [Brian] We got it?
- [Mark] Yeah.
He just asked if he
should contact a lawyer.
[scoffs] Almost there.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Okay.
- Gotta go.
- [Mark] Yeah.
[Brian] Mark.
[Mark] Okay, okay. I got it.
- Go. Yeah.
- Print it?
[printer whirring]
Fucking thing.
This... This is what I did?
I-I-I didn't do this.
I didn't.
[Brian] Yeah, but
you did, Larry.
You did.
[gasps]
[inhales deeply]
No wonder why I
can't sleep at night.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Larry…
it'll be all right.
[cries]
N-Nothing's... Nothing's ever
gonna be all right again.
Forget how I'm
doing. How you doing?
I'm, you know…
[chuckles] …whatever.
I don't know, Dad. How are you?
[stammers]
[scoffs] I'm weak.
My left side
is-is-is... [stammers]
I forget my keys, a lot.
You know, shit like that.
Wh-Wh-What are you gonna do?
It is what it is.
Sammy taking care of you?
[blows raspberry] Too much.
I can't take a piss without
her asking me what color it is.
I said, "It's yellow."
"Yeah, but dark or light?"
[chuckles]
Yeah, you.
Well, good for her, you
old prick. Listen to her.
Yeah, yeah.
S-Seriously, how
you doing in there?
[guard] Jimmy, time's up.
Dad, I gotta roll.
Talk soon, okay?
[stammers] Yeah, yeah,
yeah, sure. Stay safe.
You too. [sighs]
[sighs]
What?
You could've told him
you went blind in one eye for
a couple of days last week.
Who wants to hear that?
Or you got trouble walking
or talking some days.
- Just s... You know, will you stop it?
- What?
- Ju... Just stop!
Just, just, just…
Just, you know...
What?
Stop.
[sighs]
Me and my son, we have a shorthand. We
say things without having to say them.
- You don't say anything at all.
- That's what I just said.
[chuckling]
Yeah, have some more wine.
Take your purple pill.
[scoffs]
[FBI agents chattering]
[FBI agent 1] Hey, Jason!
Thanks, we're moving
on. Close it up.
[Lauren] Seen these yet?
As nasty as the house?
One of 'em is.
Uh-huh.
What about the other one?
First ERT guy said, to his expert
nose, it smells like three things.
Chemical cleanser, Armor
All, and denatured alcohol.
The one thing in the world
Larry Hall keeps clean.
Right?
[door opens]
So, no more dentist?
Hall was a janitor.
Worked nights on the same
three office buildings.
Company said no janitor they ever
had cleaned half as good as Larry.
That's why you never found
his victims' DNA in his van.
Bingo. What's the other salient fact
that made Hall such a competent killer?
He grew up digging graves?
Starting to ace the quizzes now.
What about his twin?
Gary?
You read about fetofetal
transfusion syndrome?
Yeah, I didn't
know what it meant.
It happens in the womb
when one twin imbibes more of the
placenta blood than the other.
Essentially, Gary drank
crucial parts of Larry
before they were born.
Holy shit.
So, Gary got the looks and the
brains and some athletic ability,
and Larry got… being Larry.
They get along?
Gary is Larry's
biggest defender.
My brother's not well.
He's weird as shit,
but he's harmless.
Gary, I'm gonna need you
to take two steps back.
Your brother confessed
to two murders.
[scoffs]
He's just... He's so desperate,
you know? For attention.
When we were kids, he'd try out
lies just to lie, all right?
He... He lies just
to get a reaction.
He ever mix the truth
in with those lies?
See if anybody catches it?
We're just regular
people here. Okay?
We don't kill people. We don't
know people who kill people.
How'd you get him to tell
that story you wanted to hear?
All I wanted to
hear was the truth.
[chuckles] All you wanted to do was to
close your... your fucking casebook.
So you put an idea in his head because
you knew he'd say what you wanted him to,
because he's impressionable.
Well, that cuts both
ways, motherfucker.
I'm gonna check on my mother.
[door opens, closes]
[sighs deeply]
If you can't tamp down your natural
alpha male qualities completely,
and I doubt you can, be
a Gary to Larry Hall.
Make him feel like
you're his brother.
Always looking out for
him, never judging.
All right.
Well…
We've got a plane to catch.
- What?
- [Lauren knocks]
Audition's over.
You got the role.
Jimmy.
Now.
[door closes]
- Hey, hey.
- Marshal, how you doing?
Doing well.
How you doing?
Here.
You gotta put them back on
when we get to Springfield,
but, uh, until then, you good.
You got mad testes,
dog. [chuckles]
Come on, you can change inside.
Change?
[officer] So you're in street clothes,
'cause you're not going in as a transfer.
Only the warden and
the chief shrink know
you're anything other
than a scumbag arms dealer
who got sentenced
to Springfield time.
You scared?
[scoffs]
I'll get over it.
Don't.
Comfortable people get cocky,
and cocky people fuck up.
Prefer you didn't fuck up.
[TV reporter] This recent arrest
hopefully will put an end to the fears…
Yeah, I'll get him
to blab in the car.
Well, it's a long
drive, flat country.
Who knows how many he'll cop to?
'Cause they don't
give a shit, Pat.
They think they're dealing
with some harmless weirdo,
who likes confessing
to shit he didn't do.
Yeah, I'll... I'll call
you if I hear anything.
We've apprehended a suspect in the
abduction and murder of Jessica Roach.
But through the diligence of
the officers you see behind me…
Fuck me.
…we believe Larry DeWayne
Hall may be responsible
for the deaths of as many
as four more young women.
[reporter] Are you saying
you captured a serial killer?
No one likes Rob Roy more
than Braveheart. No one.
- [agent] That's what I keep telling him.
- It is more historically accurate.
Says who, Liam Neeson? [laughs]
Edward the Longshanks did not die
on the same day as William Wallace,
and the Battle of Stirling
didn't take place...
God, it doesn't matter.
Yeah. One's a great movie,
the other stars Jessica Lange.
[Lauren] Hey, Jim, I need
you over here for a bit.
Sure. Give me a minute.
No minute. Come on.
You wanna be out of
prison yesterday, right?
And the feeling's only gotten worse
since we dangled this carrot, correct?
Like a clock tick, tick,
ticking away. Right?
Don't let the clock rule you.
Don't approach Hall too early, or
he'll know we sent you for him.
- I hear you.
- Besides the warden and Dr. Zicherman,
I'm your only other safety line.
When I visit you treat
me like your girlfriend.
Slip me tongue, grab
my ass, whatever.
- Grab your ass?
- Yes. Cop a feel. Do what it takes.
Should we practice now?
Hey, cool guy, keep
dicking around here.
It's just your fucking life.
If shit hits the fan, you get
to Zicherman or Warden Price,
and have them call me ASAP.
And, Jimmy, do not get any time
added to your sentence, understand?
If you get time tacked to your
sentence, it supersedes our deal.
It will be beyond our control.
You'll be stuck doing
Springfield time.
What if I have to defend myself?
Don't maim anyone.
And don't get caught.
Hey, Jim.
Take care of yourself.
I thought you were
coming with us.
I'll see you in a month or so.
[lock clicks]
[officer] Yeah, I heard
him making noise in there.
Go and check him out.
[Brian] Going right.
You two need any more
pictures with him?
I can hold the camera.
Here we go, Larry.
[chuckles]
[Brian] You really got nothing
to say to me, huh, Larry?
Huh?
Never struck me
as the quiet type.
Seemed like the kinda guy who'd like
a good jaw session to start your day.
Huh?
My mom used to say that I could
just talk paint off a wall.
That changed a little
bit as I got older.
Decided to appear like
the strong, silent type.
Mostly to get laid, but...
I do enjoy having a good chat...
You know, I kept trying to tell
you that they were just dreams.
I kept telling you,
but you kept pushing.
You f... You forced a
fake confession out of me.
Mm-hmm. Is that how you see it?
Hmm? Who put that idea
into your head, Larry?
Now, why does everybody think I need my
ideas to come from someone else, huh?
I'm smart. I've got ideas.
Hmm. I'll bet you do.
I'd like to hear
about a couple of 'em.
Maybe ones that involve girls?
Hmm.
Gary got me a lawyer.
Aha. So it was Gary.
Yeah, but... No, but…
The lawyer said that I wasn't
to say another word to you.
Oh, is that right?
Well, I don't know if that lawyer is
looking out for you, in my opinion.
'Cause you... you twist
what I have to say.
We didn't twist
your words, Larry.
You told us about your dreams.
We documented it, and
you signed a confession.
Which was coerced!
No.
The confession was coe...
♪ We are coming, Father
Abraham 300,000 more ♪
Hey, Larry. Take...
Take it easy.
From Mississippi's
winding stream… ♪
Larry.
♪ We leave our plows and workshops
Our wives and children dear ♪
♪ With hearts so full of
utterance With but a silent tear ♪
Hey. Take it easy, all right?
♪ We are coming, Father
Abraham 300,000 more ♪
♪ From Mississippi's winding stream
And from New England's shore ♪
Okay.
You got kids?
Yeah, I got a son. He's five.
Aw, man, loved five. [chuckles]
It's the perfect age.
They think you're a god.
Yeah, but now, Brittany?
Shit, she's nine, going on "Fuck
you, Daddy. You don't understand."
[officer 1] Shit, I'll take
that over dirty diapers any day.
Yeah. Bigger the kid,
bigger the problem.
Yeah, says the man who hadn't
wiped an ass in a while.
What about you, you got kids?
No.
You got a wife?
- No.
- Girlfriend?
- Nothing serious.
- You a lucky man. Shit. [chuckles]
[officer 2] Lucky man.
Look, man, I can't. I can't
do this. Let's just go back.
No, you can do it.
- [officer 1] Come on, bro.
- [officer 3] Hey, you got this.
What if Beaumont
changes his mind, huh?
Backs out?
Then I'm stuck there.
In five minutes that shift
change is gonna happen.
And that's the only time that
we have to get you in there
without setting off smoke signals from
one end of the complex to the other.
The time to do this is now.
I'm out.
[officers] Fuck.
That's not cool, man.
That asshole can never
walk back out those doors.
You're our way to
guarantee that.
Fucking look at me!
Whatever you decide
to do right now,
Beaumont will never forget it.
I will never forget it.
Final answer?
Fuck it. Let's do it.
- [laughing]
- [officer 1] Yes!
My man.
[officer 2] That's a
good call, Jimmy. Smart.
I, uh... I gotta treat you like
a scumbag again, man. Sorry.
[officer 2 clears throat]
[officer 2] All right, let's go.
[Beaumont] How'd he strike you?
He didn't fill me with an
overwhelming sense of confidence.
Well, that will be
moot in about an hour.
[judge] At trial, Mr. Hall's
entire theory of defense
boiled down to a
simple proposition.
Due to a personality disorder that
makes him susceptible to suggestion
and pathologically
eager to please,
he confessed to a crime
that he did not commit.
When Mr. Hall's
attorney, Mr. DeArmond,
attempted to call an expert witness
in the field of false confession,
Judge Baker refused to
permit Dr. Ofshe's testimony.
Since the verdict hinged on Mr. Hall's
state of mind during his confessions,
Dr. Ofshe's testimony would've gone
to the heart of Mr. Hall's defense.
Further, several aspects
of the confession,
Mr. Hall signing his name in block letters
when he is perfectly capable of cursive,
Mr. Hall signing a statement over
the name Larry DeWayne Daniels,
give further credence to a state
of mind that was suggestible.
Further, the interrogating
officer in his initial confession
was described by fellow officers
as intimidating to Mr. Hall
and resistant to
his initial answers.
Mr. Hall's appeal
is hereby granted.
Counsel, join me in chambers.
- It's getting closer, Mom.
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
[door closes]
[Lauren] What's our clock?
A month.
And she's putting a hearing for
the second appeal on the docket.
Oh, fuck off. Really?
[sighs] Keene's
not moot anymore.
- We need him to step way up.
- I told him to move slowly.
If he blows the
approach to Hall...
Hall spooks. End of story.
But if he moves too slowly,
Hall walks into the free world,
buys himself another van
and a box of zip ties.
- [door closes]
- [footsteps approaching]
Hey, Larry.
We need you in the boiler
room as soon as you finish up.
Looks like they
forgot about you, man.
Sorry about that.
Welcome to Springfield.
Empty your pockets.
All right, clothes
go in there, bud.
Follow me.
[officer] Cough.
[coughs]
Spread 'em.
Here you go.
Follow me.
[pilot ignitor clicks]
- [buzzer sounds]
- [inmates chattering]
[inmate shouting]
Chow's in ten.
Which way?
Just follow the
crazy train, bud.
Hang in there.
First week's the toughest.
[door opens]
How's it coming?
It's pretty fucked up.
[officer] How long to fix?
A machine is like a... It's
like a person, Mr. Burden.
Hygiene matters.
And this boiler, it was
neglected for years.
That neglect has allowed for
filth to spread everywhere.
Every c... crevice is infected,
every valve, every locknut.
So, how long?
[bell ringing]
Want me to bring you
something from the mess?
Yeah, just... just a sandwich.
Will do.
Thank you.
[inmates clamoring]
[inmate] What you mean? Get
the fuck out the way, ese.
["The Sign" playing
on headphones]
[Brian] Hey.
How can you do
homework like that?
I just can.
How?
First time I get less than
straight A's, then it's an issue.
[phone ringing]
Brian Miller.
How do you feel
about today? Good?
Uh, wouldn't be
the word I'd use.
I wanna take another look at all
the cases Hall's a suspect in,
but take a particularly hard
look at Roach and Reitler.
Second guess all my case work?
No, I want you to
work it with me.
- It's a Hail Mary, but...
- It's a waste of time.
You're such a fucking pussy.
A what?
N... Okay.
Work it with me.
Okay, good night, Lauren.
No. Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
I... I have a guy
inside with Hall.
You what?
A guy inside.
A cop?
No, a civilian.
What you're doing isn't police
work. It's fucking desperation.
Good night.
[sighs]
Yeah, can you connect me to
prisoner 8611167, please?
James Keene.
What... What is
that? Chocolate chip?
It's pistachio.
[groans]
Jimmy!
I-I-I don't understand.
You have to have a record of him.
I just talked to him last night.
Well, maybe you've got the
spelling wrong. It's K-E...
Okay. Okay... [stammers]
[stammering] Okay. Say
he was transferred.
Wouldn't you be...
Wait a minute.
I gotta go to court to get it?
He's gone.
What? Gone where?
[officer] That's
good. Lights out!
All right, lockdown.
[buzzer sounds]
[inmate speaking
Spanish, cackling]
[inmates chattering]
[inmate 2 shouting]
[sighs]
[shouting continues]
Thanks, Larry.
Yeah.
[Burden] Night, Larry.
["Mmm Mmm Mmm Mmm" playing]