Who are you?
Look, these people...
these people don't mean anything to me.
I don't know any of these people,
but if they try something and one of you lot let off one of those, and then this plane goes down.
The plane's secure.
Yeah. Right now, it is, yeah.
We don't need any help.
Well, right now you don't, but
what if it all goes wrong again?
- Who the fuck are you?
- You went too early, didn't you?
You was gonna do this
later on in the flight, then that man came rushing into first class and he was worried and panicking and then you gave him a green hat.
The next thing you know,
it was all going off.
That wasn't part of the plan, right?
Go and get his passport.
That can't have been...
That can't have been part of the plan.
Look, if it's all going
wrong in the first hour, imagine what could happen in the next six.
Okay.
He's coming down your side, Eddie.
Hey, oi. What you doing?
Shut up.
- Sam Nelson.
- Yeah.
You think we're stupid...
Sam Nelson?
No, I don't. I don't
think you're stupid.
I think you're very smart.
But...
Look, I think you get what I'm saying.
Take him back to his seat.
Open it.
You wanna see them again, open it.
Is that it?
This is it.
I go, and you follow. Yeah?
No!
Grab him, Eddie!
Strangle him!
Down!
The gun! Kick the gun!
Sit down. Sit the fuck down.
Face forward!
Don't fucking move!
The gun! Where's the gun?
Like I said, I just wanna get home.
I'm gonna say it, yeah?
7 a.m. is way too early to call someone you haven't seen in about, what, five years?
I know, I know. I'm sorry.
I need one favor.
I'm heading into my car
in about 30 seconds...
And listen, there might not be
anything in this, but...
Which is my way of saying,
make it quick.
Thanks.
My girlfriend's ex is on a
plane to London from Dubai.
He messaged her straight after takeoff saying there was an incident on board.
She messaged him back
straightaway, can't get through.
What are you asking me?
Well, to check if it's okay.
Look, there must be someone
you work with who can...
Yeah. It's not a
counterterrorism issue, Daniel.
Well, it might be.
And if it's not, I... You know,
maybe there's someone who...
You know, who knows someone who...
Please, Zahra.
I told her I'd try.
All right. An issue on board?
An incident.
Then he told her how much he loves her.
How he'll... he'll always love her.
Right. And this is definitely
her ex we're talking about?
It's the way he said it.
He wouldn't have said it unless it...
He'd never have said it like
that unless it was serious.
Okay, what's the flight number?
Thanks. Genuinely.
Especially after everything
you and I... You know.
Yeah, yeah, the flight number, Daniel.
KA29. Kilo Alpha Two Nine.
Took off about an hour ago.
All right, got it.
Why... Why are you doing this?
What do you guys want?
Shut up.
Ties.
Ice.
Sorry?
You got any ice on the plane?
Yeah.
Whose idea was it to
start all that shit?
Mine. Mine. It was mine.
Not a good one, mate.
It's not for me.
The guy that's in charge,
what's his name?
Stop chatting, mate.
Sit down.
No one's interested in your bullshit.
Don't make me come up there, mister.
All right, I'm starting
to get angry now. Come on.
I'm coming.
We're even later than yesterday.
And that was a record in itself.
Wait. Velcro.
- They're for P.E.
- Velcro.
- Bobs.
- Alice?
Yeah, hi. Yeah, I'm...
I'm five minutes late.
- Oh, so not ten like yesterday?
- No, five.
Okay, and how long is
five minutes these days?
Simon, if I say five, I mean five.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
Okay, well, I'll just tell
the plane to keep circling till you're ready to come to work, shall I?
Look, Bobby had his
appendix out yesterday, which means he's off school today, which means I need to find alternative childcare.
And that's further away than his school.
All of which means, Simon,
I'm going to be ten minutes late.
- Yeah?
- Fifteen minutes tops.
All right, now.
Tune.
This is your cabin crew speaking.
We ask that you remain in your
seats with your seat belts fastened.
Do only as instructed by those
now in charge of this aircraft.
The events of the past few
minutes will not be tolerated.
Any further resistance
will result in a fatality.
Take this as your final warning.
Right, give me that.
Now fuck off down the front.
Hey. Get something for this.
Checking for you now.
Yeah. One second.
Kingdom 2-9, what are
the timings on that?
Not due till 13:06.
It's still a way out I'm afraid.
Five hours till it hits our airspace.
Can you contact the plane direct?
Well, I can, but anyone can
if the Wi-Fi's on.
For some reason, the Wi-Fi's down.
Or we could try ATC at...
- Where did you say? Dubai?
- Yeah.
Doesn't really fall under
our remit, but there you go.
Bear with me.
Siobhan, can you get me
a number for Dubai ATC?
Control, this is BA9850
requesting clearance for take off.
Eight. You've got an
eight to go on a nine.
Take a second look.
I'm going home.
Happy birthday!
BA9850, you're clear to take off.
Correct.
Talked to the aircraft.
Now everything is fine.
False alarm.
Was that about the Kingdom flight?
Yes. British calling.
What'd you say?
I say everything is okay.
Just false alarm.
No. Not here, my friend.
The boy who cried wolf?
Hey. You spoke to the pilot.
He said it was nothing.
What if he's wrong?
How could he be wrong?
What if he's lying?
Why would he lie?
Maybe someone was making him lie.
Maybe he was threatened.
But his voice.
He was not frightened.
He sounded very calm and relaxed.
That's how they sound.
- Pilots?
- British people. Zero emotion.
Tells us nothing.
You need to get him out of there.
Look, you've got everyone where
you want them except for him.
He doesn't have to be in there anyway.
Everyone knows that pilots just
do the takeoffs and the landings.
The rest is on autopilot.
So?
So he could be taking us anywhere.
What have you got for me, Heidi?
Flight Path Control spoke with Dubai.
They'd already contacted the pilot.
It's confirmed as a false alarm.
Shit.
Isn't that good?
Sorry, sorry, I didn't mean that.
You're just having a bad morning.
I'm having the world's worst
journey, that's what I'm having.
Right. I want it on autopilot.
It is.
Show me.
Yeah, show me though. Explain it.
Okay.
Well, if I press autopilot there, I get a message on my flight screen here that shows you there, if you look, the autopilot AP1 is engaged.
And the program destinations are here.
That's Heathrow, EGLL,
at a bearing of 320 degrees.
How do I know that?
About the degrees?
That it's London.
Well, it's there.
EGLL, that's the code.
Europe, Great Britain, London.
So you don't have to touch anything now?
No. Not until an
hour before Heathrow.
Peace be upon you.
And also upon you.
- You're in charge here, yes?
- Yes.
I work in ATC.
We think there might be a
problem with one of the aircraft that took off this morning.
Planes are not my department.
I get that. I realize that.
The cameras.
Can I see the footage?
Can I ask to see the footage?
You can ask. You can always ask.
Okay.
Thank you.
Take your seat belt off.
Belt off.
Move.
Let go of my arm. Stop it.
You're hurting my arm.
My arm!
Hey! She's doing what you want.
Go on.
Ask her if it was a gun.
Ask if it was a gun.
Sit there.
What's she done?
She stays here.
You all right, pet?
What's happening?
There's a man up there who's
gone over to their side.
He's just betrayed us all to help
himself. That's what's happening.
I don't understand.
First one, sit there. Just here.
Keep your voice down.
She's in a really bad way.
I need to get some
more supplies to her.
- She's fine.
- She's not.
She's... She's bleeding really badly.
If I could just get to
the back of the plane.
No, it's not happening.
Sit.
Hello? Sit down.
Shiver me timbers.
Seriously?
You're just going out
like nothing's happened?
Well, what would he want us to do?
- He'd tell us not to worry.
- You don't know that.
- And to get on with our day.
- You don't know that though.
This is an important day for me, Kai.
If anything changes, we'll call.
Or text.
I'm here. Okay?
I'll leave my phone on.
When has your phone ever been off?
And?
They spoke to the airport,
to Dubai. It's a false alarm.
Are you sure?
All a misunderstanding.
Marsha.
See?
This is the problem.
This is the man I'm dealing with.
- Marsha...
- No, this is what Sam's like.
This is what he will always be like.
The main thing is, whatever we thought was happening on that plane, he's okay.
Sam is okay.
Thank you.
So, Dad's okay?
A gun went off, that's all I heard.
- You heard the gun?
- No, I heard that's what happened.
A gun went off in business,
there was a fight, two guys tried to take them on.
That's what people were saying.
You saw 'em then? These blokes?
Only when they brought me
back here. They were tied up.
That's what they must have meant
by will not be tolerated.
It's why they're doing
this in the first place.
That's what I wanna know.
So, what did you do then?
Come on, you must have done something.
Don't talk to her like that.
Well, think about it. They've
not put her here for no reason.
Turn round.
You. Face forward.
You. Shut up.
Hey, it's gonna be all right, okay?
What the fuck did I just say?
Passengers of KA29 will be in this
area. Mixed in with other flights.
It's all pretty normal.
So you saw nothing suspicious?
Today? No.
Security's tight here.
We're good.
See?
I recognize her.
Neela. That's her name.
Took my daughter to her kid's party.
Neela, yeah.
Last week, she stopped a man
from bringing on a starter pistol.
As in, you know...
a gun to start a race.
Neela's the best.
If there's any kind of
problem, she'll spot it.
Fast-forward again.
That's it? She went home?
Maybe it was the end of her shift.
Maybe. Did anyone check?
You all right?
Seat belt.
Got everything?
Got your water? Got your snack?
Got your reading diary?
Yeah? Right, go on in.
In you go. In, in, in, in.
You said it before.
- Said what before?
- That I had my appendix out.
Did I?
You said that last term.
And you can only have your
appendix out once, let's face it.
So if somebody says that twice...
Something smells dodgy.
Something smells dodgy. Yes.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna hope that my boss isn't
as clever as you. Now go in, please.
You're late. In, in, in.
- Love you. Bye-bye.
- Goodbye, love you!
A table for two at the Plaza.
That is what I want for my birthday.
I want to buy you lobster. Okay?
Okay.
So, let's do it properly.
Starters... All the seafood...
A proper babysitter...
Fatima. I'll call you back.
Abdullah.
It's Natalia. Airport security.
Your friend Neela, you were right, she left early. She said she was sick.
She didn't seem very sick.
Well, that's what she said, apparently.
Okay. Thank you.
My girlfriend's very grateful.
Yeah, no problem.
She's also angry. You know?
Angry that her ex...
her ex made her think that he was
in danger when he obviously wasn't.
Okay. Again, yeah, I get why you might call me about all the counterterrorism stuff, but...
No, this isn't a work call.
Yeah, this is getting a bit strange now.
Well, I just... I just
wanna know what you think.
You think that...
I know it's a...
a weird call to make, I do.
You think that for someone
who's meant to...
who's meant to have moved on, she cares too much about what this guy says and does?
Yeah, so...
So, when I asked you if
this ex really is an ex...
Hey, when you said, you know...
Or when we agreed that it was...
it was over between us, it was over.
We never spoke about it,
you never called me...
You know. That was it.
- Are you still there?
- Yes. Look...
Look, Daniel, if it was me, okay, - and she's worth fighting for... - She is.
Then she can care about
this guy all she wants, 'cause I'm just gonna make sure that she cares about me more.
Commit, Dan, or things move on.
All right, let 'em through.
Yeah, and maybe... maybe don't call me about this kinda thing again, yeah?
Sorry.
It's all right.
Kingdom 2-9, this is Baghdad control, how do you read?
Kingdom 2-9, this is Baghdad
control, how do you read?
Kingdom 2-9, control,
how do you read?
Got a message coming through
in there. Have a listen.
Kingdom 2-9, this is Baghdad control, how do you read?
We need to answer that.
If it's air traffic control,
we need to answer that now.
- Sit down.
- He needs to answer that. Him.
Sit the fuck down!
This... This absolutely needs to happen.
- Is he right? Is he?
- No, he's lying.
How do you know?
- Listen to what I'm saying.
- How do you know?
He wants the ground to
know something's wrong because he thinks this is going to stop, but it's actually going to make it a lot worse.
I won't tell you again, mate.
Sit down.
Kingdom 2-9 on airway Lima 602, please call Baghdad control on 123 decimal 52.
Get her.
You can answer that, can't ya?
They won't speak to her. They'll
need to speak to the captain.
Sit the fuck down!
Can I... Please, mate? Please?
Listen, listen, if they
think something's wrong, they'll scramble the jets, and if they do that...
they'll shoot us down.
Kingdom 2-9.
Urgent. This is Baghdad control.
We need identification.
Baghdad, this is Kingdom 2-9.
We tried five times to identify.
Apologies, Baghdad. We're here.
I'm speaking to the captain?
Is this the captain speaking?
Correct.
- You are the captain?
- Correct.
You are Robin Allen?
Captain is Robin Allen?
He wants the ground to know
that something's wrong because he thinks this is gonna stop. Can you tell him, please?
I must speak to Captain Allen.
He's away from the cockpit.
- Captain is away from the cockpit?
- That is correct.
So, why say you are the captain?
I speak to Robin Allen right now.
For security purposes, now.
What you've gotta do
is get in the cockpit and tell them everything is all right, you hear me?
If you put me in that cockpit,
it's only gonna make matters worse - than they are now. Listen to me... - Just take your hand off the belt.
- I'm not getting out of this seat.
- Just do what he says.
- Can you help? Can you help?
- You cannot make me.
Just grab the belt.
Get back in your seat.
There's no point.
We're all gonna fucking
die unless you go...
I'm not moving. I'm not moving!
Get your hands off me, get off!
Get her, for fuck's sake.
Bring her here.
Fuck. Come here.
Jesus Christ.
- Right, here.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Look. Here, all right?
Now don't make them do this.
All right? Don't make
us make them do this.
All right. I'm going.
All right.
Okay.
Baghdad control,
this is Kingdom 2-9, Captain Robin Allen speaking. Good morning.
Pilot Allen, please confirm
date of birth, security question.
Twenty-second, the second, 1970.
Pilot Allen, please confirm you are
safe and not in need of assistance.
All safe and well, thank you Baghdad.
He went to the toilet.
I... I just nipped out
to the bathroom for a minute.
But where was the copilot?
We've been having
a lot of radio problems so we're not exactly covering ourselves in glory this morning.
Kingdom 2-9.
Please confirm final destination
and heading. Security verified.
Okay, we are squawking 4625 maintaining
a course for London, Heathrow.
Once he's done,
take him back to his seat.
So, you've hijacked a plane,
and no one knows about it.
Down there, not one person
knows a thing about this.
That represents success.
Come on.
Morning.
What happened to five
minutes being five minutes?
Lufthansa, 958, turn right.
Heading 329. Descend and
maintain flight levels 30.
What's going on with this Lufthansa?
Delayed. I looked after your KLM.
Michael covered your Swiss Air.
Thank you, Michael.
You nearly had a live one and all.
That Kingdom at the bottom.
Counterterrorism called.
Suspected incident on board.
All sorted now though.
Pilot said it was a false alarm.
How does that work?
- Sorry?
- A false alarm, how does that work?
Simon got a call, rang Dubai, Dubai
said it was old news. False alarm.
- Simon?
- Why get involved?
- You're in enough trouble as it is.
Kingdom 2-9?
You get a call about an incident?
- Suspected.
- Suspected?
You ring Dubai and
Dubai say what exactly?
- False alarm.
- See?
- So, there were two calls?
- Sorry?
- Here we go.
- Well, you get a call, you call Dubai, Dubai had already had a call earlier. It was already sorted.
And what's wrong with that?
Oh, nothing, absolutely nothi...
I mean, that's really weird,
don't you think?
Somebody on board calls the UK, manages to get a message to us via Counter Terrorism of all people?
But the passenger who's done that,
who's gone to all that trouble, they've also got it wrong?
Maybe they dealt with it.
Then why didn't the
second caller say that too?
If it was all fixed, why didn't the second caller send any more messages?
Well, because for some
reason the Wi-Fi was down.
Oh, because for some
reason the Wi-Fi was down?
Okay. Yeah.
Something smells dodgy.
Hello, this is Senil.
Please leave your number
and I will call you back.
Yeah, no, we have
double-checked with Dubai, - now we're just double-checking with you. - Ask if they can share their screen.
Kingdom 2-9 was not responding.
They would not identify.
We try many times.
- Ask them to share their screens.
- Okay, you need to share your screen now.
Okay. So, that's what
Baghdad are seeing.
That's Kingdom 2-9's flight
path viewed in isolation.
That's normal, to go that way?
Is that the standard route?
Yeah, that's fine, apparently, and that route would have been uploaded before takeoff.
And the other line?
Well, you can see the route there.
But the other line.
Ask him to go closer, please.
Can you zoom in for us, please, Jalal?
Yeah. There.
Behind the plane.
That's a deviation, no?
Michael?
It's a message. That's the plane
trying to tell you something.
Yes, I agree.
I don't get it.
Before 9/11, planes
often veered off course.
Now it's tightly monitored.
If anything, it's a way to
signal there's a problem.
Yes, if you're not able
to signal it verbally.
Are you sure that's not just the
weather blowing it off course?
It's too straight a line.
It's a three degree shift.
It's meant to be at 320 degrees but someone's changed it to 323.
So, something has
happened to Kingdom 2-9...
and someone is calling for help.
Excuse me, I'm...
I'm looking for Neela.
- Is she here?
- They're all upstairs.
Who are you?
We're the cleaners, pal.
Professional cleaners.
They're moving out next week.
You want me to go up and
tell them you're here?
No. Thank you. I will go.
Neela!
That's it, pal.
All the way in the back there.
Neela?
Do me a favor. Step back
into the bathroom for me.
The bathroom's easier to clean.