Turn around. Hands up!
- [GUNSHOT]
- [SCREAMS]
[SCOFFS] Well, well.
Just as I suspected.
Kind of obvious when
you think about it, huh?
[PUERTO RICAN ACCENT] No for
me, boss. I no see that coming.
Anyone with an alibi is always
a suspect, Markowitz.
How do you know these
things, jefe? [CHUCKLES]
[NORMAL VOICE] Wait. I'm the sidekick?
Yes. You're the sidekick.
[CHUCKLES] Thank you so much.
I... I don't know what to say.
You're welcome. [CHUCKLES]
Now, should we go back to the top?
Yeah? Okay.
Well, well.
Just as I suspected.
Kind of obvious when...
Why the accents?
You're Puerto Rican.
Uh... [SPEAKS SPANISH]
Hey. [CHUCKLES] Not bad.
There you go. [CHUCKLES] Okay.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Well, well.
Just as I suspected.
He watched the light fade
from the man's eyes,
the withdrawing of the
life-force from the body
seeming to coincide
with the evacuation of his bowels
into his gabardine slacks.
"... into his gabardine slacks."
Before long...
"Before long... "
- ... the putrid scent of feces...
- "... the putrid scent of feces... "
... hung in the air like...
the ghost of a dead lover.
"... hung in the air like the
ghost of a dead lover."
You getting this, Marty?
You know, you gotta keep up
with the rhythm of the prose.
You know, it's like jazz.
- Uh-huh. Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah?
[MARTY] I got it. I got it. Got it.
"Another day, another dollar,"
as he always said.
"... another dollar... "
He turned on his heel and walked out.
Another day,
- another case closed.
- "Another day... Case closed."
The end.
"The end."
Or is it?
Isn't it?
Just saying that, um,
maybe Dr. Kessler isn't
as dead as he seemed.
- Oh, wow. [CHUCKLES] No way.
- Hmm.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
- [MARTY] I love it.
- Well, there we go.
[MARTY] Ah.
Book nine of the "Some
Like It" series complete.
[STRAINS] Ah. Incredible.
And... [STAMMERS] ship all
of this to the publisher?
I think so, yeah. I think it
reads better as a series.
But it's this last book that's gonna
really get them interested.
- Yeah.
- It's the ultimate page-turner.
Bottom line, though, it's gonna sell.
And at the end of the day, that's
all the publishers care about.
Getting noses in books.
[STRAINING] Ouch.
Whew. My stomach kinda
hurts when I do that.
Yeah, well, you know what? My
head really hurts when I do this.
I just wrote an entire novel.
But this has been going on
for a couple of weeks now.
Well, uh, maybe your
stomach problems are back.
[STAMMERS] It... It feels different.
It sounds weird, but I
can't fart, you know?
Even though it feels like I need to.
And then if I cough, it feels
like I might, you know, poop
- by mistake.
- Okay. Yeah.
That's too much information. Thank you.
[SIGHS]
[EXHALES]
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
- [STRAINS, SIGHS]
- Marty, are you okay?
[SIGHS] I just have a little bit
of discomfort when I move.
Or... Or don't move.
Or breathe.
That doesn't sound so good.
Sit down. I'll get you some water.
No. No, no, no. I...
I can't. We're too busy.
You weren't too busy
to have a heart attack.
You... You scared us once before.
You think I'm gonna let
you do that again? Sit.
[SIGHS, EXHALES SHARPLY]
Hey, uh, listen. I... I know this
probably isn't the, uh, best time,
but I was wondering if I
could get a word with you
about, uh, some financial, uh, stuff.
Oh, B... Uh, Bruce, can...
can you just email
Norman Horowitz about it?
Um... [STAMMERS]
Well, it's kinda urgent.
And I figured it's easier to talk to you
because... [CHUCKLES] you're right here.
What's up, Bruce?
Uh, oh, I-I... I was just, uh...
That's okay. We can talk later.
Problem?
[STAMMERS] No, no.
[CHUCKLES] No problem.
Hmm. It kind of sounds like there is.
[STUTTERS] Come on, Bruce.
You can say anything.
I was having a look at
this year's accounts
on top of this year's
expenses, and, uh...
we have a big problem.
We don't use the word "problem" at AFC.
We use the word "solution."
Yeah, but sometimes you
need to know the problem
in order to find the solution.
Okay, thank you, Cathy.
That'll be enough.
Our problem is that profits are
down and midtown rents are up.
- Yeah. We can't afford the lease here.
- Okay, you know what?
This sounds like something
for Norman Horowitz.
Yeah. I gotta be honest.
It's killing us. Right?
Another six months of this rent,
we go under. Simple as that.
All right, you know what?
All I hear is the word "problem."
But he has a solution.
Okay. Well, lead with
that next time, please.
A contact of mine tipped me off
that the Lea & Perrins factory
in Fair Lawn, New Jersey is empty.
Now, we could move out of here,
rent that place for, like,
under half the price.
It's twice the size, but
we'd have to move quick.
- That place is gonna go fast.
- No. [CHUCKLES]
Forget it, Bruce. We're not
moving to New Jersey.
This is a great opportunity.
You know, when I, uh, encouraged
more feedback from the workforce,
I was expecting suggestions
more along the lines of, uh,
"Could we get some non-dairy
creamer for the coffee cart?"
Not, "Hey, I've got an idea.
Why don't we tank our business
and move to New Jersey?"
But the problem is that we can't...
You don't take AFC out of Manhattan.
It's classy. It's classic.
New Jersey is second-rate. It's cheap.
Do you think that the
pastrami from Katz's Deli
tastes the same in New Jersey?
- Yes.
- I think that it probably would, yeah.
[IMITATES BUZZER]
No, incorrect. It doesn't.
Uh, moving, in itself,
Bruce, is expensive. So...
[IKE] Look, Bruce, business
is all about perception.
If we were to pack up
and move out to some sauce
factory in New Jersey
with our schmekel between our
legs, that sends a message.
It sends a message to our customers
as well as our competition.
And that message is, "Hey,
look at us. We're losers."
Now, you wanna make a suggestion?
Maybe we should try moving to
a place that's more expensive.
That would be smart.
Now, if all of you financial
wizards would excuse me,
I have patients to see.
Thankfully, none of them
are as crazy as Bruce.
[SIGHS, SCOFFS]
Here. Take that.
Listen, I... I don't wanna
cause any trouble, all right?
But this is a serious situation.
You know I care about
this company, Marty.
I was there when your dad put his
sweat and blood into this place.
I feel like I sorta owe it
to him to keep it alive.
[STUTTERS] I don't know.
I... I mean, I hear what you're
saying, Bruce, but... [SIGHS]
I think we gotta listen to the experts.
You know, it's... it's his world.
He knows what he's talking about.
- [SIGHS]
- [INHALES SHARPLY, GROANS]
- It's... Jesus. See a fricking doctor.
- No.
No, no. A doctor's only
gonna make things worse.
It's like taking your car in.
They're gonna find something eventually.
That is it. I'm making the call.
- No.
- You are not crapping out on me, Marty.
I am not springing for a new dress
for a perfectly avoidable funeral.
You have a hernia.
You will need surgery
to repair the tear.
Surgery? Like surgery-surgery?
I'm afraid so, and as soon as possible.
Uh, good news is it's a
straightforward procedure
and nothing to worry about.
Oh, well, I guess that is good news.
So... [STAMMERS] in and out?
You know, like, same day?
Not quite. We get in there pretty deep.
We keep you around to make sure
the sutures don't get infected.
Sutures?
[DOCTOR] You won't feel them.
You'll wake up very comfortable
from the anesthesia.
Anesthesia? What? Hold on.
This doesn't sound so simple.
Uh, um, how long will
I be in the hospital?
I have a lot of responsibilities
I need to take care of.
What sort of responsibilities?
Well, you know, I... [STAMMERS]
My... My constituents.
They're counting on me.
Ah, you're an elected official?
No, I... [SIGHS] I don't think
I used that word correctly.
[STAMMERS] People need
me to be healthy, is all.
Not long at all. Should
only be a few days.
And then, obviously, there
will be a period of recovery.
A period of recovery?
Oh, my God.
All right, well... [SIGHS]
I guess I will, uh...
I have to get my affairs in order.
Mr. Markowitz, I assure you,
it's really pretty routine.
We'll get everything popped
back in, and then off you go.
[EXHALES]
Right. Okay.
I've been thinking, Marty.
That whole thing with Bruce
didn't sit well with me.
The Bruce thing? What... What thing?
[GRUNTS]
A move to Jersey.
- Oh.
- I just don't have time for negativity.
It's toxic.
And it's not good for your anxiety.
- I don't know. I... I just think...
- Oh.
You know what?
We're out of time for today.
- Oh, right.
- Yeah.
Uh... So, uh, with the koi.
They have this ich parasite
problem with their gills currently,
so they're gonna need a... a
little more care than usual.
Uh, can I ask you to put some
formalin drops in the pond
as soon as you get down there
- for the weekend?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
- Ah, great.
Uh, about the feeding schedule.
I... I think the long-release
block should be good
for a few more days,
but you may wanna add
a precise measured pour
of the spirulina algae
as a weekend treat.
Think of it as their
Saturday morning pancakes.
- Hah.
- It's all labeled in the guest house.
And also, I wrote it down.
Got it.
Oh, and, um, if I... If
I don't make it, uh...
can you just, uh, promise
me they'll be taken care of?
Seriously? Come on.
Look, let's not make a
huge deal of this, okay?
It's a hernia. Yeah? It's
like getting your tonsils out.
The girls got their tonsils
out when they were little,
and it was fine.
You know, we watched Jungle Book
and we ate ice cream and Jell-O.
You're gonna be great.
You're in very good hands.
And your fish are in good hands too.
I know how much they mean to you,
so they mean just as much to me.
Aw, I appreciate that.
- [CHUCKLES] Come here.
- [CHUCKLES]
Is that a hernia or are you
just pleased to see me?
- Ah!
- [CHUCKLES]
Come on.
- I love playing around.
- Oh. Ah, all right.
- Okay.
Talk soon.
[MALE NURSE] Finally, we
just need contact details
for your next of kin.
Just a formality, in case of emergency.
Parents? Wife? Children?
Siblings? Could be anyone.
Um... [SIGHS]
Ike Herschkopf.
H-E-R-S-C-H-K-O-P-F.
Great. Good luck.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
You did great, Marty.
[MACHINERY BEEPING]
It's okay. You're in recovery.
Oh.
Okay.
[DOOR OPENS]
Doctor ordered a CBC.
Need to make sure that your
iron levels have come back up
- and check for any possible infections.
- Okay.
- Got any questions, honey?
- Yes. Uh...
Visiting hours are 9:00 to 5:00, right?
That's correct.
[EXHALES]
How you feeling?
Um, you know.
Question.
Uh, does... does someone
have to be approved
before they can come visit?
What... What exactly is the process?
Is... Is it a written consent?
Oral consent? 'Cause I'm happy to...
I'm gonna up your meds, okay?
No, no, no, 'cause I need to
stay awake in case he comes by.
[DOOR OPENS]
- Good morning.
- Oh, good morning.
I just need to run through some of
these insurance details with you.
Is there a chance
that I wouldn't be getting
cell phone reception in here?
I just wanna make sure
I'm not missing any visitors
who try to get ahold of me.
Can I... Can I check your phone?
Um...
- [CELL PHONE BUZZING]
- [GASPS, GROANS]
[INHALES SHARPLY] Ow! [EXHALES]
Okay. Oh.
Hello? Dr. Ike?
No, no. You...
No, you h... you have
the wrong number. Yeah.
Yeah. No. Okay.
[SIGHS]
Mr. Markowitz? You have a visitor.
Oh. I do?
- [SIGHS] Thanks, man.
- You're welcome.
Good afternoon, sir.
My friends and I are
reading to seniors today.
Would... Would you
like me to read to you?
"I seen it over and over.
A guy talkin' to another guy
and it don't make no difference
if he don't hear or understand.
The thing is, they're talkin' or
they're settling still not talking.
It's just bein' with
another guy." [SIGHS]
Why are you here, Terrel?
You don't actually care
about me, do you?
No. You... You're okay. You're cool.
[SCOFFS]
- I'm cool?
- [TERREL] Yeah.
No.
I'm not cool.
Why are you really here?
[SIGHS]
Honestly, I just need some
stuff to put on my college app.
It was either this or band,
and I hate band, so...
Oh, everyone hates band.
Well, at least you're honest.
Don't ever lose that.
Uh, so...
do you want me to keep
reading, sir, or...
You know what? Um, yeah. Why not?
Thanks, Terrel.
Uh... [SIGHS]
"Sure, you could play
horseshoes till it got dark,
but then you got to read books.
Books ain't no good.
A guy needs somebody to be near him.
A guy goes nuts if he ain't got nobody.
Don't make no difference who the
guy is, long as he's with you.
I tell ya, a guy gets too
lonely an' he gets sick."
You can stop there, Terrel.
Thank you.
[STRAINS, GRUNTS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER, LAUGHING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Mr. Markowitz?
Mr. Markowitz.
You can't leave.
- Come back here. Sir.
- [ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
What do you think you're
doing? Mr. Markowitz!
[SIGHS] Fuck.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[LOUD MUSIC PLAYING]
Everybody, duck!
- Don't say it. Don't even think it.
- [CHUCKLES] What?
- I'm not playing golf with you again.
- Why not?
"Why not?" That wasn't golf.
That was more like hockey.
I was afraid for my life.
[IKE] Have you tried the hot tub
yet? You should try the hot tub.
- Even you can't miss that.
- [RICHARD] Ooh, I ought to...
[IKE] Have you seen the sundial?
- [WOMAN] No.
- No? No? Here, look.
Thirty-six feet tall.
And you know, to get it in,
I had to chop down a tree
and install it by crane.
- Amazing.
- Yeah?
- [IKE] Do you know what time it is?
- [WOMAN] No.
[IKE] Cocktail time.
You don't need a sundial
to tell you that.
- [LAUGHS] No, you don't.
- [CHUCKLES]
You most certainly do not.
Um, have you played the giant chess?
[STAMMERS] Go ahead and,
uh, play some giant chess.
Marty, my sweet. Why...
Why are you so dressed up?
It's not a formal party. [CHUCKLES]
I need to talk to you.
[STAMMERS] Oh, yeah. Sure, of course.
Hey, come on. [STAMMERS] Let's...
Oh, Marty, your... your
tush is hanging out.
Here. Here. Okay.
- All right.
- Who's that?
Oh, that's, uh, Chef Pete.
I hired him for the party.
He used to cook for Kevin
Bacon and Kyra Sedgwick.
He's good, but he's no Marty Markowitz.
All right.
What's going on?
For the better part of
the last three decades...
I have dedicated my life to you.
Every weekend, every
holiday, everything.
And you couldn't even
find time in your schedule
over the course of four days
to come... come visit me?
To call me?
To check in on me
during one of the most harrowing
experiences of my life?
Okay, I know they pumped
you full of narcotics, Marty,
and that you're a lightweight, so
I'm assuming it's hitting you hard.
I don't underst... You wanted me
to, what, come by the hospital
with Jell-O and ice
cream, uh, snuggle up
- and watch Jungle Book?
- Why?
Why didn't you come?
I thought we were family.
[SCOFFS]
Are you serious?
Marty, I'm worried that you're serious.
You need to know this.
You need to hear this.
I would do anything for you. Anything.
The second you told me
about your procedure,
I called my contacts at NYU
Langone the very next day.
I told them that we're family.
The hospital bed, the
private room you had.
Who do you think did that? I did that.
I can't believe you didn't think
I would do anything. Wh...
After all these years,
is that how you see me?
[STAMMERS] I was just surprised
that you didn't come and visit.
Why didn't you ask me to come? I...
Do you think I'm that much of a schmuck?
You don't think I'm gonna come and...
Of course. Why didn't you say,
"Ike, it would mean a
lot if you swung by"?
I'm not a mind reader.
- Well, why...
- You say that you've been by my side
for the better part of three decades.
Well, I'd argue the same thing.
When Debbie and your
sister tried to bleed you dry
after your parents died,
who was there, hmm?
What about when AFC wanted
to grow and expand?
Who provided you with that opportunity?
When you had a heart attack,
who scooped you up and held
your hand in the ambulance?
Who saved your life?
Marty...
That's loyalty.
That's love.
I'd do anything for you. You're my guy.
I will always show up for you.
You're absolutely right.
[SOBS]
I'm sorry.
- I'm... I'm... I'm sorry.
- Come here, you maniac.
Come... [CHUCKLES] Come...
Oh. Marty, I love you.
You are my brother.
- You hear me?
- Mm-hmm.
- Are you listening?
- Yeah.
Good.
Now get out of this farkakte outfit
and meet me by the pool, huh?
- All right. All right.
- [KISSES]
- [SIGHS]
- Okay.
Money in the bank. Ready? Jump.
- He's hot. Oh!
- [MAN LAUGHS]
You just made a hundred bucks.
[IKE] ... because your mother
raised you as veal. [CHUCKLES]
Let's go in here, all right?
There's air-conditioning.
There are hundreds of movies,
all Academy Award winners.
- [GRUNTS]
- Mind the boccie balls.
- Hi, tchotchke.
- Hi.
Having a good time? [KISSES]
- Uh-huh.
- Oh, great.
Uh, maybe you could send
the message to your face?
What?
Maybe you can arrange your features
in a configuration that expresses
some form of enjoyment.
- Oh, fuck you, Ike.
- Come on. [SCOFFS, CHUCKLES]
I'm kidding. I'm kid...
You look terrific.
I'm worried. What is
going on with Marty?
What? Nothing. He's fine.
Yeah, well, he's a little loopy
post-surgery, but he's fine.
[BONNIE] No, he doesn't seem fine.
Maybe we should just wrap this
up and just get him some rest.
Wrap this up? What, are you
crazy? Lisa Rinna just got here.
Should we bring him something to eat?
Yeah, sure. I don't know.
If you think so.
But one of us has to host this party.
I know, but I... I don't know.
I think we should just shut this down
and send everybody home. He's not okay.
What are you, the fun police?
[STAMMERS] Well, um, don't be
ridiculous, Bonnie. All right?
I've already got one ridiculous wife.
His name is Marty Markowitz.
You don't have to tell me that.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[MARTY] Stu, get away from that rock.
You always get caught in
that little roundabout.
[SIGHS]
So, did you guys miss me?
Aw. [CHUCKLES]
Well, I missed you too.
That's very nice of you.
Where's Adam? How's his ich?
Stu, where's Adam?
Where...
Where is he?
Adam?
[BREATHES HEAVILY] Adam?
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Where the hell is he? Ada...
[BREATHES HEAVILY] What?
[GASPS]
Oh.
Oh, no. Adam.
Adam. [GASPS]
[SIGHS, SPEAKS HEBREW]
Goddamn fish murderer.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
"Brothers," my ass.
[SIGHS]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Lisa.
Ike Herschkopf.
- Hi. [CHUCKLES]
- Thanks for coming. [CHUCKLES]
- You look gorgeous, as always.
- Thank you.
- You don't mind if we get a picture?
- [MAN] Okay. So, which button is...
- On the top.
- I pressed the wrong one.
- Can I just go find my glasses?
- No. No. You know... It's okay.
Hey, hey! Come. Come here.
Thank you. Thank you.
Come here. Uh, take this picture of us.
- Enjoying yourself?
- I am. I am. Gorgeous.
- I love the house.
- [IKE] Thank you.
- Success.
- Great. [SIGHS]
I wanna show you these cows.
- Oh.
- I got 'em in a gallery in the city.
- Oh, okay.
- They're so fun.
Collect some of these
wet towels, would you?
- Right over here. It's terrific stuff.
- Oh.
Hey. Hey, Marty. You okay?
Are you in pain?
Oh, you... you know.
Yeah.
Can I get you anything?
I've had enough.
What?
I can't do this.
I've tried, Bonnie.
For so long.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[SIGHS, GRUNTING]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[INHALES DEEPLY, GROANS]
You need something?
I left the Ambien in your bathroom.
[SIGHS]
What are you looking at?
Party for the ages, it seems.
The lawn is totally trashed.
Well, eight hours of open bar with
your friends is not a good combo.
- I can't get this...
- Our friends.
Your friends.
Marty's got his work cut out for him.
He'll see to it tomorrow. I got it.
Yeah. I don't think that's a good idea.
He just got out of the hospital.
He's been lying in bed,
bored out of his mind,
desperate to get out there.
[INHALES DEEPLY] He likes it, you know.
It's therapeutic for him.
- [LID POPS]
- Ah.
[BONNIE SIGHS]
I can't help it if his favorite
thing in the world to do
helps us out sometimes.
[CLEARS THROAT] Did you
hear that Jacob went to the...
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
[GRUNTS, SIGHS]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Sleep well, friend.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
[SNIFFLING]
[GRUNTING]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTS]
That's because it is, Claire.
It's an invasion of your privacy.
Here's what we're going
to do. You ready?
- Mm-hmm.
- You ready?
- Yes. [CHUCKLES, SIGHS]
- Okay.
You're going to block your mother
and father on Facebook.
No more wall posts. No more pokes.
- No more tags.
- Really? I...
Yes, really. These are toxic people,
and they need to learn
that if they're going to
take advantage of you,
there are consequences.
Yeah. I mean, you're probably
right. Right? Yeah.
- Thank you, Dr. Herschkopf.
- Oh, don't thank me.
This is my job.
And, um... yeah, unfortunately
we're out of time.
We even went a few minutes over.
But... look.
Call me this week if you wanna
schedule a few more appointments.
This is a big step.
And I think you're going
to need me a few more times
to help guide you through.
Okay. Thank you.
- Good seeing you, as always, Claire.
- Yeah.
Hey, Marty. You're late. It's 11:20.
And, um, just wanna make
sure everything's okay.
You, uh... You stuck in traffic?
We have an appointment.
Hope to see you soon.
[SIGHS]
35th and 7th. And avoid 5th Avenue.
- It's a nightmare.
- [DRIVER] Got it.
I'm very interested in
the lecture circuit.
I love to travel.
I guess, sure. Okay, yeah.
We'll talk about it then.
Great. And, um, we'd love
to take you up on your offer
to visit Stowe next winter.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Sounds terrific.
Well, there is... Yeah.
Dennis, I have to call you back.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- [PEOPLE CHATTERING]
AFC. How may I help you?
[IKE] I'd like to speak
to Marty, please.
Uh, wh... Uh... [STAMMERS]
Marty is... is not available right now,
but I could take a message.
- I need to speak to Marty.
- [CATHY] Yeah.
Sure. I'll have him
give you a ring back.
[RECEIVER CLICKS]
[IKE] Why? My God! Who takes
the bridge at this hour, huh?
At this rate, we'll get there
by the Sabbath. Oh, fuck!
Fuck!
[DRIVER] Thanks.
[LOUD MUSIC PLAYING]
- And I don't wanna throw it out.
- Oh, check it out. Wha... No, no.
- Because I know it's perfectly brand-new.
- [IKE] Hey, Cathy.
It's good to see you.
Can you point me in the
direction of Marty, please?
Forget it. I'll find him myself.
- What's up?
- Hi, Marty.
Good to see you.
What's, um...
What's going on?
- Nothing. Just, uh... Just unpacking.
- I can see that.
I... I got cuts all over my
hands from the cardboard.
- See?
- [INHALES SHARPLY]
- That's gotta hurt.
- Yeah. [CHUCKLES] Yeah, a little bit.
Bruce, can you give us a moment, please?
[SIGHS]
[MARTY] What's, uh...
What's going on?
Well, Marty...
a lot of things are going on.
One being, when did you move?
A few days ago.
But you knew we were...
[CHUCKLES] moving.
We had to.
The city rent was killing us.
I thought we decided we were
not going to leave the city.
Well,
I know that you decided
that you didn't want to.
But I decided that we had to,
to keep the company from going under.
And since it's my company,
I decided...
that...
that that was th-the decision.
So, yeah, he-here we are.
And, uh, it's kinda nice.
Look at the space and,
uh, and the light.
Yeah. No. It's the Venice of America.
Can we speak in your office, please?
About that. Uh...
We no longer have private offices.
Yeah, it's... it's more of
an open concept now.
Oh, Marty.
This is... a shame.
- Why?
- You.
All of this.
You've taken a real step backwards.
You're not thinking clearly, Marty.
I have your best interest at heart.
And it's hurting me to see
you hurt yourself like this.
- Is that so?
- Yes, it's so.
It's very much so.
Do you know that I just spent two
hours on the GW Bridge, okay?
George fucking Washington
himself didn't take that long
to cross the Hudson.
The Delaware.
- What?
- He crossed the Delaware.
That's... That is the famous crossing.
- I know.
- He crossed the Delaware.
He was president, Marty.
He crossed a lot of fucking rivers.
How do you think he got to
Manhattan in the first place, huh?
- What, did he take the PATH train?
- Okay.
Let me tell you something.
This arrangement, it's untenable.
It's untenable!
How do you expect me to help AFC
if I am stuck for two hours
schlepping out here, huh?
[STAMMERS] It's, like,
a waste of money, Marty.
It's a waste of your money.
[INHALES DEEPLY, SIGHS]
Then don't come.
I beg your pardon?
If it's so much of a hassle,
then maybe you shouldn't come.
Marty...
- are you firing me?
- No.
[CHUCKLES] No. No, of course not.
Good. Good, because I...
But Norman Horowitz is.
[PEOPLE APPLAUDING]
- Yes! Yes, Marty. Yes!
- Marty!
- [CHEERING]
- Way to go, Marty.
[CHUCKLES] Marty!
[PEOPLE CHEERING, SHOUTING]
[MOUTHING] Thanks.