[elevator bell dings]
[wind howling]
[Irving echoing] Hello!
Hello!
[Mark] Irving!
- It's me. I'm up here!
- Mark!
[Mark] Yeah!
Hey!
[stammers] What's happening?
Where are we?
[Mark] I have no fucking idea,
but there's a path up the
cliff right down there!
[Irving] Do you
want me to come up?
[Mark] Well, yeah!
[Irving] I'm on...
[groans] I'm on the ice.
I'm on the fucking ice!
[Mark] Maybe get
off of it. Come on!
[Irving] I'm coming!
[groaning, panting]
[ice crackling]
[grunts] I'm...
I'm coming!
Be careful!
[Irving groans, panting]
[Mark] It's very steep!
[grunting, panting]
[grunts]
[pants, sniffs]
- [grunts, sighs]
- [Helly] Irving.
[Irving] Helly!
Where did you come from?
I don't know.
What are we doing out here?
[Mark] Up here!
Follow my voice!
Mark!
[Irving grunting]
[Mark] Up here!
[Irving] Mark.
[Mark] Hey!
Are you okay?
- Did you wake up on the ice too?
- Yeah.
- What about you?
- On the cliff.
- [Dylan screams, grunting]
- [Irving] Oh, my God.
- Is it you?
- [Helly] Of course it's us.
Holy shit!
Out-fucking-side.
Oh, my God. I mean, I knew
there was no actual ceiling,
but this is fucking insane.
Hello?
[electronic Kier hymn playing]
[Mark] What is that?
[music continues]
[music stops]
Good morning, Refiners.
This is Mr. Milchick from work,
and I'm thrilled to welcome you
to your first ever
outdoor retreat and
team-building occurrence.
This ORTBO is in response to your
desire to see the outside world.
With your outies' blessings,
you will spend the next two
calendar days walking the meadows,
thickets, brambles and brooks that make
up the Dieter Eagan National Forest.
Who the fuck is Dieter Eagan?
Dieter Eagan?
Some of you may be quietly
yearning to learn more.
The truth you seek lies
within the fourth appendix.
Kier dictated a fourth appendix
in his final hours of life,
a text of such sanctity that it is
forbidden upon the severed floor.
It's waiting for
you in Scissor Cave,
the very same grotto
where Kier Eagan tamed the four
tempers for the very first time.
And do remember,
"Stray not from Kier's path,
lest you roil nature's wrath."
There will be help
along the way.
Happy fortunes, MDR.
[beeps]
Scissor Cave.
What the fuck is that?
He looks like Mark.
Milchick said there'd
be help along the way.
I wouldn't trust a word out
of that mountebank's mouth.
Not even televisually.
Not like we have a lot of
other options right now, Irv.
[sighs]
Wait.
[Helly] "Chapter one.
I was not born into
this world alone.
The lodgings of my mother's
womb I shared with another,
a twin brother who
was called Dieter."
Kier had a twin?
That's what those things are.
[Irving] Yeah.
"In infancy, he was my bosom friend.
But as we blossomed into boyhood,
he beseeched me to take to the
wood with him to live as paupers.
My love for my twin
unbalancing my judgment,
I acceded, and we ventured
into the wood towards"...
[both] "Woe's Hollow."
[Irving] So, we're to walk
in the brothers' footsteps.
"He always crept like
this at this hour.
- Once concealed by flora, my brother"...
- [Kier] ...flora, my brother
unfastened himself.
The din of his fervor fell strangely
into concert with the music of the wood.
His every thrust found rhythm
- with the trill of the crickets...
- "trill of the crickets"...
- and the moaning of the wind...
- "and the moaning of the wind"...
- and the snowfall's yearly thaw.
- "and the snowfall's yearly thaw."
[Kier] Dieter
became, on that night
- an instrument of nature...
- [Irving] ..."an instrument of nature"...
- and nature played Dieter...
- "and nature played Dieter with elegance.
I had no choice but to listen
as he spilt his
lineage upon the soil."
Now there's a me one.
[sniffs, breathes heavily]
[panting]
You okay?
[sighing] Yeah.
I just wish I knew
where we were going.
[exhales sharply]
[breathing heavily]
[no audible dialogue]
[panting]
[Dylan] Fuck.
What were you and Helly
talking about back there?
[Dylan groans]
When?
I don't trust her.
I think she might be lying
about what her outie saw.
Why would you think that?
Night gardeners. Hmm?
[sighs] It's clear you do not
have an objective perspective
due to your feelings for her.
My feelings for her have nothing
to do with anything, okay...
[Dylan sniffs, sighs]
[Mark] Whoa.
What the fuck?
What is it?
I don't know.
Looks like a seal.
Why does it look so messed up?
I don't know. Maybe this is
what dead things look like.
We should eat it.
Pardon me?
We don't know if there's
food waiting at the hollow.
We don't even know where we are.
They can't let
anything happen to us.
It's an ORTBO.
Outdoor retreat team-building
occurrence. Right, Mark?
We don't know what this is.
- We don't know anything!
- Irving, calm down.
We all know you had a bad experience
the last time you were outside...
Who said I had a bad experience?
Oh, my God.
What did you tell him, dumbass?
Nothing! What the fuck?
Let's just get to the hollow.
[Mr. Milchick] Kier's
twin was always with him.
That's why we provided the
very same for each of you.
Fuck you all. I was right.
Mr. Milchick.
This is the tallest
waterfall on the planet.
You have followed the path of Kier
and Dieter, and reached Woe's Hollow.
You stand upon sacred earth.
We're starving, Mr. Milchick.
Are you?
I thought the waterfall's
grandeur would satiate you.
I'm teasing, of course.
Lumon will always
protect and provide.
Right this way.
Miss Huang has been readying the grill for
which we brought in copious luxury meats.
The fire will be used for
marshmallows and a recital later.
The tents, as you
can see, are MDR blue
and the outhouse is stocked
with four-ply washroom tissue.
Wow.
[Mr. Milchick chuckles]
Wow, indeed, Helly R.
Also, for your comfort
and safety, torches,
which can provide both a
heat and a light source.
Double duty.
It's beautiful.
Pretty cool, right?
Yes, lovely.
[grunts]
[Helly] Irving?
Enter.
[sighs]
- [Helly shivers]
- Hmm.
Made you a snow seal.
[chuckles]
In case you were hungry.
Yeah.
I feel silly for suggesting
we eat that animal.
I suppose it sounded
alarmist and paranoid.
Irrational.
No. It was fine. We
were all a little...
[sighs]
Yeah.
What did you really see during
the overtime contingency?
I told you.
[Irving] It's okay.
It won't change anything.
Irving.
Okay.
[theremin playing]
[Mr. Milchick] "Dieter lay
unwashed in his bedroll,
though the hollow's pool
was primed for bathing.
We ate of the hare we'd caught
and told each other rhyming
jokes till our gullets ached.
But at last, the thought
tickling my mouth emerged.
'We must return to
Father, ' I said.
'But I promise to look after
you in the ether mill.'
When at last a sound came from
him, it was a bewailing whimper.
He believed, I suppose, that
we'd be woodland paupers forever.
I was looking at him
when his eye came out.
It popped from the socket,
driven by a sudden torrent
of pus from his skull.
And he reached up to
grasp at his hair,
which was suddenly moss that tore
easily from his bleeding scalp."
Good heavens.
[Mr. Milchick] "And as the pus
from his eye thickened into sap,
I turned from my gargling brother
and walked to the pool of the hollow,
where I knew the waterfall would
drown out my brother's cries."
That's actually really smart.
"And it was here that I first
encountered the temper Woe,
a gaunt bride, half the
height of a natural woman.
She spoke to me directly
from her eyes and said,
'This is your doing.
You suffered his wantonness.
Now he's no one's brother.
Only chaos's whore.'"
The end.
Perhaps in the morning, we'll
have time for the next chapter...
"Kier and the Thieving Nanny."
- [Helly] Hmm. Creepy.
- Whoa.
Did his brother really die
that way, Mr. Milchick?
The handbook enriches our work
with tales of the founder's life.
Every word is truth.
[Helly sputters]
[laughs] I'm sorry. Sorry.
Helly.
[laughing continues] What?
- [Mr. Milchick] Helly R.?
- You guys... [laughs]
He melted, right? [sniffles]
He turned into the forest
because he masturbated.
[both laughing]
I mean, seriously, that's actually
the dumbest thing I've ever heard.
- [Mark laughing]
- [Dylan chuckles]
Right? He jerked off in
front of his brother...
and he got punished for it.
[Mark laughing] Wha...
You can't say that.
- [Helly] He just said it. [laughs]
- [Mark] Wha... [laughs] He did.
[stammers] I... It's... It's...
You know, we often laugh at
what we don't understand.
The team I thought I knew would
have processed more thoughtfully.
Miss Huang.
The marshmallows, please.
Throw them in the fire.
- [gasps] Mr. Milchick, come on.
- [Helly scoffs]
Now, Miss Huang.
- [Helly, laughing] Oh, my...
- [Mark gasps]
Why?
Marshmallows are for
team players, Dylan.
They don't just hand them out.
What?
Good night.
Wow.
- [Mark] Oh, my God.
- [Helly laughs]
Hey, what do you think
his dick turned into?
[laughing]
[Dylan chuckles]
It isn't funny.
- Oh, I don't know. It's pretty funny.
- [Helly laughs]
- [Irving] Well, it's not.
- Okay.
And stop making
goo-goo eyes at her.
- [laughs] I'm not.
- [laughs] Stop.
- "Goo-goo eyes"?
- [Helly laughs]
Just tell us, Helly.
[scoffs] What?
[Mark] Come on. Tell us.
[Helly laughing] Tell us what?
Just tell us about him.
Who?
The night gardener.
Oh, Irv, come on.
Did he have a flashlight? Hmm?
What was he wearing?
What is your deal
right now, dude?
What color was his shirt?
Did he have on a vest?
- A luminescent vest? Tell us...
- Okay.
- Exactly what he was wear...
- Irving. Th-That's enough.
- Enough?
- Yeah.
Using your pupils
to make love to her
while your outie's wife
rots away somewhere.
Hey, shut up.
Yeah. Fuck you, Irv.
Oh, so it's three
against one now, huh?
It's okay.
We all know Irving's upset because
he can't ever see Burt again.
And he's really lonely.
[Mark] Hey, Irv.
[Irving] Fuck you all.
[material rustling]
Uh, probably a carrot.
What?
Dieter's penis.
[Helly scoffs]
Yeah, or some other
root vegetable.
[sighs]
That was mean of me...
to say that to Irving.
[sighs]
I mean... [sighs] ...he
kind of deserved it.
And I can make goo-goo
eyes at anyone I want.
Are you okay?
Sorry if I'm
distracting you from...
From what?
From looking for your wife.
Hey, it's okay.
I know we'll find her, and
you've already helped so much.
I have?
[Mark] Yeah.
Okay.
[kissing]
[moaning, breathing heavily]
Mr. Milchick!
[Irving] Mr. Milchick!
Miss Huang!
Mr. Milchick!
[Helly breathing heavily]
Miss Huang!
[heavy breathing continues]
[grunting]
[Helly, Mark moaning]
Mr. Milchick!
[groaning]
[groans]
[panting]
[grunting, groaning]
I didn't like who I
was on the outside.
I was ashamed.
Who were you?
I don't care who
you are out there.
I care who you are with me.
That's all.
Okay?
[Mark gasps, breathes shakily]
Are you okay?
[breathes shakily, grunts]
What happened?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
[scuttling]
[typing]
[typing intensifies]
[hisses]
[gasps, breathing shakily]
[panting]
Helly?
Hey, where's Helly?
I don't know. Irv never came back
last night, and he's not in his tent.
What?
Mr. Milchick?
Helly!
Mr. Milchick!
[Mr. Milchick] Mark.
Mark. Dylan, what's happened?
Helly and Irv are missing.
What the fuck is going on?
Hey, kid.
Irving.
[Irving] What are
you doing down here?
Hmm?
What are you doing down here?
[Irving] I slept outside.
I almost froze to death.
What you said to me last night,
it was cruel.
Helly was never cruel.
I'm right here.
So if you're not her...
then who are you?
Who would have the power to send
their outie to the severed floor?
Hmm?
I'm sorry.
- [grunts]
- [groans] No! Irving!
[Helly breathes sharply]
Mr. Milchick!
- [Helly] No. No!
- [Irving grunting] Come on.
- [Helly] No!
- [Irving straining]
- Irving. Stop. Irving, no.
- Mr. Milchick!
- Please, stop.
- [Irving groans]
Help!
- [Irving] Mr. Milchick!
- [Helly] No!
[Mr. Milchick] Irving?
[Irving] Mr. Milchick!
[Mr. Milchick] Irving!
Mr. Milchick!
- Come!
- [Helly] Mark!
[Irving] Mr. Milchick!
Mr. Milchick!
- [Helly] Mark!
- [Mark] Helly!
- Turn her back, Mr. Milchick!
- [Helly] Help!
What are you doing, man?
- Turn her back!
- Irv, what the fuck?
- [Helly screams]
- She's an outie!
[Helly screams]
- Hey! Irving, stop it!
- Hey! Irv, cut it out!
- Stop!
- She's been an outie the whole time,
ever since she came back!
- Irving, you stop now!
- [Mark] Stop it!
- [Mr. Milchick] Irving, stop this!
- [shrieks]
She's a fucking mole!
What are you doing?
- [Mr. Milchick] Irving!
- I'm gonna kill her, Mr. Milchick!
- [Helly screaming]
- [Irving shouts]
[Mr. Milchick] Irving!
Irving! Irving!
[Mr. Milchick] Stop! Stop this!
- [groans] She's not Helly!
- [Helly gasps, panting]
She's an Eagan!
Turn her back,
Mr. Milchick! Turn her back!
Goddamn it, Seth, do it!
Yes! Do it, Seth!
[Mark] Hey!
[screams]
It's Milchick. Remove
the Glasgow block now.
[groaning]
[screams]
Now!
[elevator dings]
[Irving grunts]
[Helly gasping, coughing]
- [Helly whimpers, gasps]
- I'm sorry.
- I'm s... so sorry, Helly.
- [Helly coughs]
[breathing heavily]
What's happening? [gasps]
[pants]
Helly!
[breathing shakily, coughing]
I'm sorry, Helly.
[Mark sniffs]
[Helly breathes shakily]
Irving B., stand.
You have threatened collegial
murder in the pond of Woe's Hollow.
For this, there can be no penalty but
immediate and permanent dismissal.
There shall be no formal
valediction, catered or otherwise.
Your outie will be
notified forthwith.
Irv! I'm sorry!
I should have listened!
It's okay. It's all okay.
Just remember, hang in there.
Please refrain from
any further speech,
as you are no longer authorized to
consort with any severed employee,
nor they with you.
Leave him alone!
Turn around!
[Dylan] Leave him alone!
[panting]
Walk into the forest.
Your workspace will be cleared
and any personal
items discarded.
Your file, including any and
all professional interactions
and personal relations,
will be purged and destroyed.
It will be as if you, Irving B.,
never even existed
nor drew a single
breath upon this Earth.
May Kier's mercy follow
you into the eternal dark.
Now.