[splashing]
- [breathing sharply]
- [clock ticking]
[breathing heavily]
[Helly] Father.
[Jame] A momentous day.
[Helly] Yes.
Won't you eat?
[Jame] I'll watch.
[sips]
[whines]
We're seeing to Mr. Bailiff.
I wish you'd take them raw.
[Mr. Milchick] Unveil.
Eustice Huang.
Today marks the end
of your Wintertide Fellowship.
Congratulations.
Your bed will be moved
from your parents' home to the Gunnel Eagan Empathy Center in Svalbard, where you will work to steward global reforms.
[Miss Huang] I thought
I'd be finishing the quarter.
Empathy awaits, fellow Huang.
You may resume your duties for the day.
A shuttle will pick you up at dusk.
But first...
lay the game on the table.
The handbook requires that you mark
this betterment with a material sacrifice.
I have chosen your ring toss game
as a proper totem.
[Miss Huang grunts]
Again.
[music playing on TV]
Asher picked up the kids.
[Dylan] Outstanding.
I kissed your innie.
Beg pardon?
I saw your innie again at Lumon.
And right before I left, we ended up kissing for about a minute.
[exhales sharply] What?
I'm sorry.
Uh, how?
What the fuck? Like...
It... It didn't f...
It didn't what?
It didn't... It didn't mean anything?
I wasn't going to say that.
Wow.
Yeah.
[Gretchen] You've been adrift.
You know that.
This is so many
fucking dimensions of fucked.
He just...
He reminds me of how you used to be.
- [Dylan] Okay.
- Dylan?
Um, I'm gonna go to work and earn
a paycheck to feed our children.
- [stammers] Will you st...
- And I'm gonna r-respectfully request that you don't follow me there and use my own body to fucking cheat on me.
- Don't leave.
- You know what?
Since I would have no way of
knowing if that's happening or not...
I don't know. Maybe I just go quit.
Maybe I go in and I quit
and I just end his existence.
How about that?
[door closes]
[Radar whines]
Burt.
[inhales deeply]
"They may be also connected to several recent disappearances or deaths.
Goodman... [grunts]
may have participated as a low-level Lumon enforcer or goon."
[chuckles] "Lumon goon." That stings.
We never used words like that.
[stammers] With Lumon it's very...
[clicks tongue] ...specific language.
That was before. I...
I know now that I was wrong.
I-I know you're not with them.
Would you go for a ride with me?
Burt, I'm... I'm sorry. I...
[whispering] Go for a ride with me.
[Drummond] Yes?
- [Dr. Mauer] It's nine o'clock.
- And?
The numbers aren't moving.
[phone rings]
[Drummond] The numbers aren't moving.
[Mr. Milchick]
He may just be running late.
The final quota was promised today.
Get him here now.
[breathing heavily]
Hello?
Mark?
[breathes heavily]
- [Devon] Do you know where you are?
- I'm fine.
[Devon] All right. Where are you?
Smelly fucking car.
That's nice.
And how about me?
Am I me or a copy machine?
Tragically, you're you.
[coughing]
This is a mistake.
[Devon] I'm sorry. The wind was whistling over the hole in the back of your skull, so I didn't quite get that.
Did you just call my plan
a fucking mistake?
We told her everything.
- She told us shit.
- Mm-hmm.
We can't trust her.
[Devon] Yeah.
This is it.
Looks like she's not here yet.
I mean, what if it's a trap?
Maybe it is, I don't know. Maybe it's not.
But we fucking need her. [sighs]
[phone buzzing]
Don't answer it.
[buzzing continues]
- Where's Mark?
- Excuse me?
This is the second day in a row
he's not here. Is he coming in?
Nondisclosure policy forbids.
He had a nosebleed before.
Is he okay?
Why?
[Helly] Why?
He's Department Chief.
Dylan is. In Mark's absence.
Kinda like you and Cobel.
Replace one part with another.
That's enough, Helly R.
Don't you mean Helly E?
Helena Eagan is my employer.
You are my subordinate and this
behavior constitutes insubordination.
Yeah, no shit.
Leave it open.
I told you about us.
What?
[Gretchen] I told my husband about you and me this morning.
[Dylan] Um...
Was he glad for us?
No.
Well, he should be because I'm...
I'm making you happy.
[Gretchen] I know.
And he's not.
I can't see you anymore.
He threatened to quit.
And I don't know if he's still going to.
But maybe if I tell him
that this is over...
- No, no, no. Hold on.
- This is all my fault.
- I never should have come here.
- Wait.
Gretchen, my life started
when you came here.
That's not true.
You have so much going for you.
No, I have nothing else.
I have... I have this and...
and I have fucking pencil erasers.
[sighs] I'm sorry, I have to go.
[Dylan] No, wait, wait.
Um... Uh... [breathes
shakily] Gretchen G...
- Oh, my God. [chuckles, breathes shakily]
- Um... I love you.
And I know I'm just an innie,
but I love you all the way, I do.
Gretchen...
I made this for you.
I can give you a life. Please.
[cries]
[whispering] I'm so sorry.
[breathes shakily] Gretchen.
[breathes heavily] Gretchen!
[breathing heavily, sniffles]
[breathes shakily]
[Helly] You should keep it.
Give it to someone you meet down here.
It's just O&D and the goat people.
[Helly] That we know of.
She's my wife.
She's not your wife...
Because no one would treat someone
they love the way she's treating you.
Like all the outies treat us.
Like everything's for them.
Okay, well,
what the fuck is there to do about it?
At the end of the day, we're still stuck
down here, with no lives and no family.
Irving was your family.
- Dude.
- And he left you a message.
The black hallway.
I don't know if he knew where it leads,
but he thought it was important and they convinced you to turn your back on him for some outie woman you don't even know.
You know it's your fault
we're down here at all, right?
No, it's not.
And if we're so different from our outies, then how come we couldn't tell when you were gone?
- Irving could.
- [scoffs] Mark couldn't.
Sorry, I guess
I'm an asshole down here too.
Hello, Mark.
How are you?
Oh, my God, so good.
My wife's being held prisoner at Lumon and I just got brain surgery in my basement.
How have you been?
We're allies now, there's no need to...
Oh, we're allies now,
we're not neighbors anymore?
- Sorry, I-I just... I guess I'm confused.
- Can you...
This birthing cabin,
you can take us there, right?
So we can talk to his innie.
[Ms. Cobel] Not yet.
Even under the cover of dark,
it's perilous.
We wait for night.
- Oh, it's perilous. Okay.
- [Devon] Okay, yeah.
You want us to wait until the evening?
We don't even know
if he's completed the file yet.
I assume no.
What file?
Cold Harbor.
And if you've completed it...
well...
"Well" what?
She's already dead.
Jesus Christ.
She better be fucking alive.
- No! Fuck this. We're leaving. Right now.
- [Devon] Hold on. Wait, - Mark... Okay... - I'm trying to help you.
Mark.
She is there and we are out here
in the middle of fucking nowhere.
[Devon] I know
and we're gonna get her out, but listen, that's what we're doing here, right?
Call Mr. Milchick.
Tell him you're unwell
and won't be coming in today.
Do it now.
Oh, my God.
[Ms. Cobel] If he smells chicanery,
he'll lock you out of the building.
[stammers]
- How about fuck off? How about that?
- [Devon] Wait.
- [scoffs] I mean... [chuckles]
- Mark.
- No, fuck that. No...
- Hold on. Stop. Don't go anywhere.
- no fucking way.
- [Devon] Mark, wait.
- Listen to me.
- [Mark] Absolutely not.
- Do you have any idea how insane she is?
- [Devon] Yes, I do.
- [Mark] Do you know what she did?
- [Devon] Mark, listen to me.
- Listen to me. Take a breath.
- No, I can't.
- We can't do it.
- Mark, there is literally no other option than to do what the fuck she says right now.
For Gemma.
[breathing heavily]
She knows where she is, Mark.
[Helly] Okay, Irving.
[sighs]
Fuck this place.
I never hurt anyone.
I want you to know that.
I drove people places.
I didn't ask what happened to them
once they get there.
Is that what today is?
I'm sure you know this is very
disappointing and reeks of ingratitude.
[inhales deeply] Done. [sighs]
Anything else?
Key card.
Please report to the elevator and wait.
[Miss Huang] I'm sorry, Dylan G.
I should have facilitated better.
That's enough.
[inhales heavily]
It's not your fault. [sighs]
[Drummond]
So this is "tightening the leash"?
Our most vital refiner
missing in the wind, on what was to be Lumon's finest day.
This is your fault.
I have followed protocol, Mr. Drummond, but I thank you for your remonstration.
A needlessly complex
word for a simple idea.
Apologize for the word.
- Sir...
- Apologize for the word.
I apologize.
Shorter.
I'm sorry.
Again.
[breathes heavily]
Mr. Drummond...
Again.
[breathes heavily]
Devour feculence.
It means "eat shit," Mr. Drummond.
- What did you just say to me?
- I am manager of the severed floor, which means two things.
First, I am owed a measure of respect,
even by my superiors.
Second, and more obvious, that said floor
comprises the whole of my jurisdiction.
To put that monosyllabically, it's not my fault what Mark Scout does when he is not at work.
It's yours.
[breathing heavily]
[exhales heavily]
[line ringing]
[phone ringing]
[Mr. Milchick] Mr. Scout. Where are you?
Uh, well, I'm...
I was worried about these nosebleeds.
So we drove to this clinic
out in Soil Hill and, um, you know, they want to do a few more tests.
Let me send a car.
[inhales sharply]
You are a priority employee and you should be under Lumon care.
May I get your exact location?
I, um...
- [sighing]
- Mr. Scout?
[sighs]
I'm not sick.
I just needed the day, okay?
[Mr. Milchick] May I ask why?
[sighs]
No.
I've just got life stuff.
Isn't that what Lumon's all about?
Balance?
I mean, work is just work, right?
Do you know what I mean, Mr. Milchick?
Mr. Milchick?
[inhales sharply] I have your word
you report to work tomorrow?
You do. Yeah, um,
I'll... I'll be there. I promise.
Good. And thank you for calling.
[handset settles in cradle]
[train rattling]
[announcer on PA, indistinct]
[clerk] Here you go, sir.
Thanks.
This line goes as far as you can go.
I can't know where you get off.
And you can never come back to Kier.
Do you understand?
No.
Won't Lumon come after you?
[Burt] You asked me why I severed...
I liked the idea that
I could be innocent again.
Part of me.
But then my innocent part
fell in love with you.
[Irving] I want to remember it.
[Burt] Probably better we don't.
I've never been loved before.
Not really.
Well, now you have.
How does it feel?
I don't know. I...
Don't you want to know how it felt?
It's not possible.
[Irving] Burt...
It's okay.
Just go.
I'm... I've never had this.
- I know.
- My whole life.
[Burt] I know.
I want to.
I wanna have it.
[Burt] Irving.
I'm ready.
[whispers] I'm ready.
We can't.
I'm ready.
We can't!
Bon voyage...
buddy.
Burt...
bye.
[train horn blows]
[elevator bell dings]
[sighs]
[Helly] Left, left, right.
Right, down the hall, right, right, left,
down the hall, left.
Left, right, down, left... Fuck.
[breathes heavily]
[whispers] Right,
all the way down the hallway, turn left, right, left, down the hall, left.
Fuck.
Right, left, right down
the hallway, right, left, down the hallway, left, left, left, right, left, left...
You tricked me.
My Helly.
What the fuck?
We're going to cottage five.
I don't have anyone scheduled.
She's one of Jame's.
No one's to know.
Miss Marsha White, ninth floor.
Specialties Department.
I'm looking for a gold thimble.
[engine rumbles]
[breathing shakily]
- Hi, Mark.
- [breathing shakily] - [Mark] Wait. What? - You're okay. You're fine.
- [breathing shakily]
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
If you walk out that door,
he's just gonna come right back in again.
- What is this?
- It's gonna be okay.
Can I... You wanna walk with me?
Sorry, just come with me.
[breathing shakily]
You're good. Yeah.
- [Mark groans] Are you my...
- [Devon] She just wanted to talk.
[fire crackling]
[Mark breathing heavily]
Do you remember
the last thing that you said to me?
She's alive.
Mmm.
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org