[breathing shakily]
Where's my mom?
Not here. You told me
we weren't inviting her tonight.
I have to call her.
[Marcus] Wait, wait.
You didn't hit up Jewel?
Where's all the shit?
Um… The cheese, the beer, the... Kirby, I don't know. We made a whole list.
- [knocking]
- Fuck, they're here.
Who is?
[Marcus] All right. We have tonic.
I'll call Giordano's.
- [knocking]
- I'll call them. You grab that.
Hey, hello. I wanna place... Yeah. Okay.
- Lakshmi Awad?
- Are we announcing arrivals now?
[guests chattering]
- [Clarence] Hey, hold the door.
- Hey, Kirby.
Hey. [kisses]
Where is the birthday boy?
- Oh.
- Hey. You steal that off Ben's desk?
Barely cracked open.
Still counts as a gift.
So, who else is coming tonight?
From the office?
I'm guessing Jules. Miles is on deadline.
He'll bail the first chance he gets.
Abby wants us to wind down
on our flood story.
She killed my follow-up piece
on padded claims.
What's going on? You and Marcus okay?
I think so.
[Lakshmi] Good.
Want me to grab some photos tonight?
Give him a break?
Where's his camera?
- [knocking]
- Just prop it open.
Hi.
[guests chattering]
- [Bertie] Oh! Oh, my God.
- Good to see you.
[Bertie] Whoa, don't wait.
Don't... Get in here.
You know you want to party tonight.
You know you want to party.
[Marcus] You're standing way too tall
for getting down.
[party guest] The Cubs are an institution
built on letting us down.
That's what we deserve.
- Jordan's not from Chicago. Is he?
- [Bertie] We drink to Marcus!
[party guests cheering]
Wait, wait, wait. Where's the cake?
He needs to blow out some candles.
Oh, there's no cake. I'm sorry. I… - I'm sorry. I didn't have time. - [Lakshmi] Oh, well, that's all right.
You need to go in there.
- [Marcus] Hey.
- [grunts, breathing shakily] Uh, I don't know how I got here and, um… Being married to you just doesn't seem real. [inhales deeply]
Happy birthday.
[party guests cheering]
[party guests laughing, chattering]
Marcus.
Yeah. Good to see you.
[chuckles]
[breathes heavily]
[game character grunting]
Come on.
[Dan] Hey, Howard.
- [Howard groans]
- [game announcer] You lose.
I saw last night's crime stats.
You okay?
Yeah. First warm week of spring,
Asters bloom, people kill each other.
[game announcer] You lose.
How's your girl?
The one you brought by.
My source.
What was your read on her?
That you shouldn't have brought her
into a morgue.
She was fine with it, man.
Until she wasn't.
Did her wounds match Julia Madrigal's?
[stammers] You know, that's hard to say.
Her scars are pretty old.
Can I check out Julia's autopsy report?
No. Police made their arrest.
They'd have to release it.
Was anything left inside of her?
Eh, mud, debris.
I mean, she was pretty far down that pipe.
Nothing else?
Like what?
Okay.
Her father gave me this for reference.
[Dan] Mm-hmm.
Did her dad come in to identify her?
No, he wasn't up to it. He sent a cousin.
[sighs]
- [Dan] Was she killed at the site?
- [Howard] No, she's a body dump.
See? Some broken blood vessels
under the armpits, so he dragged her far.
You think she was still alive?
Well, it's a C3 fracture but, uh, she couldn't do much more than breathe by then, even after he opened her up.
See? Ribs intact.
I swept inside the cavity.
There's nothing there.
So, you can let your source know
you followed up.
[sighs]
- Thanks, Howard.
- Mm-hmm.
[Dan] What's this?
Oh, it's just debris from the site.
We found a lot of it down in that pipe.
Radium ore, Midway Chemical Company.
Radium's been off the market
since the '50s, okay?
So that has been down there
a lot longer than she has.
Where is that, uh… - Can I? - Yeah, not for publication.
Howard, um… [smacks lips] [inhales deeply] Can you bring her out?
You up for it?
[inhales deeply] Yeah.
Okay.
I know you're a delicate soul.
So, [sighs] we got three cracked ribs from external trauma.
There's tissue piling up her back
from being dragged.
Hey, come on. Like...
This is what you asked me for.
Look again. [panting]
The radium… It was inside of her.
It wasn't until Cantigny
that I heard a horse scream.
When the gas moved in.
[Harper] No.
The dogs would bark first. [chuckles]
- That's right.
- [Harper] Yeah.
Yeah. They could smell it.
[Harper] Oh, yeah. Yeah.
- Then it would hit the horses.
- Mm-hmm.
Then the rest of us.
[Harper] Yeah. That's right.
That's right.
Uh… I'll stop if I've told you this before.
Well, we have to stop now anyway.
Um… [inhales deeply] She's just coming in now, so… I have to go.
- Mmm.
- But, hey, you tell me.
What do you think?
How do I look?
You're here to see Julia?
- Yeah. [chuckles]
- Is she your girl?
Well, no. She's not mine.
Uh, not this time.
I'll see you, Leo.
[guest] Hi.
- Here you go.
- [elder] Thanks, sweetie.
You're welcome.
[Harper sighs]
- You need the pen?
- [Harper chuckles] No, I just went out to grab these. [stammers]
You can take one if you want.
[chuckles] I'm okay, thanks.
You visiting someone you served with?
- Why'd you say that?
- [clicks tongue] Your gig line.
- Oh.
- It takes training for a man to match his buttons to his buckle.
- [Harper] Right. [chuckles]
- [chuckles] I see.
[Julia chuckles]
Uh, you shouldn't wear your hair
like that. Not at work.
No... Don't touch me.
- [Gordie] Hey, Julia.
- [chuckles] [Gordie] You're half an hour early.
[Julia] Yeah,
well, my last client didn't show.
- [chuckles]
- How's your week been, Gordie?
Ah, better now that you're here.
- Yeah. [chuckles] That's sweet.
- I got two good ones for you.
- [Julia] Yeah.
- [chuckles]
[Spanish music playing in the distance]
[voice mail] You have no new messages.
Hey. Dad?
[Raymon] Back this way.
Sorry, sorry. I was with a client.
Regional keeps denying his benefits.
I've filed for them three times.
Yeah, well, I've had to make
some executive decisions.
- Knives and forks.
- [chuckles] - [Raymon] Dishes. - What's this one?
Los Solitarios.
I've played them for you before.
You said you liked it.
[Raymon] Tupperware?
Uh, maybe next to the sink.
Where is this?
That's Glencoe.
North Shore?
I never go there.
[Raymon] Yeah, you didn't seem
to be having too good a time.
What about this?
Hmm. On the counter's fine.
Hey. I was looking
for clips on your assault.
There are none.
You're still working on Madrigal?
For now.
[sighs] Okay.
There won't be much to pull.
We ran a blurb on it,
and there was a beat-up in the Reader.
Do you have a police report?
I wanted to compare it
with the Madrigal autopsy.
Did you speak to the medical examiner?
What was inside of Julia?
Okay, uh… It's problematic that you work here.
I mean, that we work together.
You can't be my colleague
and my source at the same time.
I have to be able to ask you questions
and vet your answers. Right?
To see if I'm lying?
To verify what we publish.
Fine.
Can you tell me what you meant when
you said he left something inside you?
Come on.
What are we doing here?
He left matches inside of me.
- Matches? Like light a match, matches?
- A matchbook.
From the Bee Happy bar with this address.
This must have been a bar before.
- It's actually a good spot for it.
- No, I checked the city records.
There has never been a bar
at this address.
[Dan] That's what was inside of Julia.
[breathes shakily]
[sighs]
What is it?
Can you… walk me through
what happened to you that day?
Where were you?
I was by the North Avenue Beach.
You were alone?
I was walking my dog.
You're married to Marcus, right?
Mm-hmm.
Were you guys living together back then?
Why does that matter?
Did he usually walk the dog with you?
He wasn't there.
I was alone.
- I was walking my dog by the beach and I...
- Hang on.
Hang on, Kirby.
Do you have any family?
My mom.
We talked about her.
No, we never talked about your mom.
Is she local?
I think so.
You don't know where your mom lives?
- I did. I just... I don't...
- [scoffs] But you won't tell me?
- I can't. It's...
- Listen, I'm not trying to trip you up.
Kirby, these are
very basic questions that I...
For you, but not for me.
Not today.
- [breathes heavily]
- Okay.
You... You don't have to
have all the answers now. It's okay.
I don't need them now. Okay?
I just don't want to get it wrong.
Me neither.
Anything you have
that can corroborate your story, that would help.
Okay.
Is there a cover?
You can make donations inside.
[church vocalists] ♪ We will celebrate
his good life ♪ ♪ We will celebrate with joy ♪ ♪ We will celebrate his life ♪ ♪ We will celebrate his joy ♪ ♪ Celebrate our Lord's good life ♪ [church vocalists] ♪ Let us celebrate our gracious Lord ♪ ♪ Who teaches us to give him more ♪ ♪ Than we ever dreamed that we could give before ♪ Yeah. Yes!
- [Rachel] Hallelujah, hallelujah.
- [church members cheering] [Rachel] Oh, so nice for coming down.
Nice to see you. Good to see you.
[gasps] Barbara, good to see you.
How you doing? Oh, thanks.
Kirby?
Everybody. [breathes shakily]
- This is my daughter.
- [church members] Aw.
[laughs]
Hi. Hi. Hey.
Hi.
Mom, can we get out of here?
I just came to get my stuff.
I need my hospital records
and my photos, okay?
- Oh.
- Okay?
[Rachel inhales deeply]
Oh, Heavenly Father, thank you
for bringing my daughter back to me.
Oh, Heavenly Father, we know
you have the power to transform.
Heavenly Father, we know that
you are the redeemer and the healer.
Oh, Heavenly Father,
we feel your spirit moving in us today.
And we ask that you always, always
keep you... keep her in your sight.
[church members] Amen.
Praise the Lord.
Here. There might be some in there.
This isn't the one I need.
It's, uh... I need photos and journals
from after the hospital.
Well, I may have tossed them.
I don't know. Why do you need all this?
There's another woman.
She's been killed, and we think it might be the same man.
So we're covering her story.
And you're helping?
Check your old suitcase. It's in the back.
[grunts]
Thanks.
- Who's making you do this?
- No one. I want to.
Why?
Oh, look, you were with me… When I opened for The Effigies.
Okay, yeah.
[Rachel sighs]
♪ …Save me
If I give any more of my brain ♪ ♪ We've been down this before And I don't wanna do it anymore ♪ - ♪ Why is it okay for you, you, you ♪ - [Rachel] Half those people are dead now.
Or in real estate.
[Rachel] Come here, baby!
- It's my daughter!
- [Kirby chuckles] Oh, look what's happening now.
[Rachel laughing]
[Kirby] It's so embarrassing. [chuckles]
I thought you were great. You were great.
Why don't we talk anymore?
That was your call.
But I told you, you're welcome to come
to services anytime you want.
[crowd cheers]
I've never seen any radium before.
Did Julia ever talk about any friends?
Boyfriends?
She never even talked about herself.
Her mind was always on everyone else.
- I mean no ill against her.
- Of course.
But her problem was she didn't know
to be scared till it was too late.
Scared of who?
She wouldn't say.
Then how'd you know?
[sighs] She changed a few weeks
before she stopped coming.
This was a woman
who could nut-kick a linebacker.
Then suddenly I'm walking her to her car?
Didn't make sense.
- She thought someone was following her?
- She must have.
Otherwise, [chuckles]
she just wanted to hold my hand?
She mention calling the cops?
She never said.
She believed in that.
Going through the system.
She got me this place.
Did all the paperwork.
[scoffs]
She was a diamond.
Rarest fucking kind.
Appreciate your time.
I wanted to follow up on Julia Madrigal.
She make any stalking complaints
before her disappearance?
I didn't think you guys were interested.
Not much of a write-up
in your paper about her.
- It was just a holding piece.
- Well, what else are you waiting on?
Did Ms. Madrigal
make any stalking complaint...
I can't comment on that.
What about the second victim?
She claims you have the wrong suspect.
I wasn't aware of any second victim.
I don't know how that's possible.
She knows you.
Is this who you're talking to?
Sharon Leads. Is that your source?
Sharon, or Kirby,
or whatever she's calling herself.
You build a story off of her,
and you'll end up printing a retraction.
Her wounds seem to be consistent
with Ms. Madrigal's.
The ME confirmed it.
That may be so, but Kirby barely had
any memory post-assault.
And then a few months later,
she completely broke down.
Had to be admitted to Chicago-Read
for observation.
Well, she seems pretty sure now.
[stammers] I brought her in
to ID the suspect.
She blanked on him,
but she connected to the victim.
I guess she went with that.
What about Ms. Madrigal's
stalking complaints?
Yeah, she was being stalked.
And now he's in jail for her murder.
Pawel Banik was stalking her?
Read up on your source
before you start speculating.
[Marcus] Your mom called.
Said you left pretty upset.
[Kirby] Yeah, she's a lot.
What are you doing?
[Marcus] I'm testing out
some new film stock.
When was I supposed to come home?
A couple hours ago.
You're not mad?
Do you want me to be?
You messed up my birthday.
You went to see your mom
for the first time in months.
I know something's up.
Then why aren't you asking me about it?
[Marcus] When you wanna tell me, you will.
You wanna talk about it?
No.
[Marcus] Okay.
Then drink your beer.
[thud]
[louder thud]
[panting]
[breathes shakily, panting]
[telephone rings]
[breathing shakily]
- [Harper] You don't need that.
- [gasps, breathes shakily] [Harper] I'm not in the house.
How'd you get inside?
[Harper] You let me in.
[breathes shakily] I don't know you.
[Harper] You did.
- You will.
- [Julia breathes shakily] [Julia] What are these?
How did you take them?
[Harper] Oh, they're from tomorrow,
but you may not be there.
Watch your step.
[Julia gasps, breathes shakily]
[Harper] When I close my eyes, the memories I have, I don't know where they're from anymore.
Do you think that
you can remember the future?
[gasps]
[breathes shakily]
New request.
Pull everything you have on Sharon Leads.
I usually like
to get my sources' names right.
Call it professional pride.
- I pulled your employment application.
- From here?
Yeah. From here.
You put down that you went to U of I?
And worked at the Tribune?
I didn't lie to get this job.
"Sharon Leads." Is that from the police?
Do you want me to walk you through
what they left out?
I took these after they discharged me
from the hospital.
[Dan] You were in there for a bit?
I thought I was paralyzed.
Took a while to come back.
For this kind of assault, - the PD write-up is... It's pretty light. - Yeah, it would be.
They took my statement
when I was on pain meds.
They said they were gonna come back,
but they never did.
[Dan sighs, inhales sharply]
Then tell me what I'm missing here, Kirby.
Were you still living
in Wicker Park back then?
Yeah, that was off of Monroe.
- To be closer to the Tribune?
- Mm-hmm.
You wanted to be a reporter.
Why aren't you doing that?
I was out for too long.
This is all I could get.
And you couldn't give the police
any kind of ID? Not even a rough sketch?
He came up from behind me.
But I don't know how no one else saw him.
[sighs]
There were so many people.
That's... That's not in here.
There's no witnesses listed.
I know.
There were so many people,
and then there just weren't.
And I was alone.
Before it happened, did you have any...
Any break-ins? Any wrong numbers?
No.
But I knew something was… off.
I would come home,
and it was like someone had just left.
Julia was being stalked.
She filed reports.
She said he had been in her house.
You think he was watching me?
[sighs]
Hey.
Is there anything else
you need to tell me?
[breathes heavily]
I don't want anyone else in the office
to know that I'm your source.
Okay.
I understand.
[Kirby] Does Julia's dad
know we're coming?
[Dan] Yeah. The service
should have finished about an hour ago.
You got kids?
- Just one.
- That's enough. [sniffs]
- How old?
- Twelve.
He's really got his shit together, my kid.
Much more than I do.
- You'll get there.
- [Dan chuckles] You and Marcus thinking about it?
Um, we haven't really talked about kids.
So, he's shot for you before?
[Kirby] What do you think?
About your husband?
You haven't formed your own opinion
on the guy yet?
I think he's kind.
[Dan] That's not my read.
He's a martyr.
All decency but no compassion.
Well, you're not married.
Nope.
But I'm highly eligible.
Listen, you might need to hang back, okay?
I only told Julia's father
that I was coming, so…
[Spanish music playing]
[person speaks Spanish]
[in Spanish] Julia was baptized
at that church - and we finally get to bury her there. - [Dan] Mr. Madrigal.
[Julia's aunt speaks Spanish]
[in English] Turn around.
[Dan] Mr. Madrigal, I'm Dan Velazquez...
[Raymon] No. I'm done. I'm tired.
I can't do this anymore today.
[Dan] Mr... Mr. Madrigal,
we spoke on the phone, remember?
Maybe try again after everyone's left.
No, I can't push him too much.
Maybe the family made a statement.
Yeah?
Hey, uh, I worked with Julia.
I'm her friend actually.
Okay.
I didn't know when to do this,
but she lent me these.
And I didn't think
I should hang on to 'em.
[speaks Spanish]
- [speaks Spanish]
- [Julia's cousin] Yeah.
Uh, leave those on the counter.
- Thank you.
- Are you sure you guys don't need anything else from me?
[Dan] If you have a statement,
I'll take it.
How do you know I'm not a reporter?
Which outlet?
- Daily News.
- [Dan chuckles, sniffs] Yeah, you're taking your time with that deadline.
They've been out of print for ten years.
Ah. [chuckles]
Ah.
Know what's funny is
I'll bet you not many people know that.
Yeah.
Yeah, I write for the Sun-Times.
Oh.
We're still in business.
Barely.
I'm Dan Velazquez.
Oh… Oh, sure.
I-I read you. You, uh...
Yeah, you wrote about Julia.
You knew her?
Nah, I live close.
I've been following the news.
- I hear that they made an arrest.
- [Dan] Yeah.
Yeah, we'll see if it sticks.
Oh, uh… You think it was someone else, huh?
Come on.
You're not very good at this, buddy.
- Yeah, you sound just like my editor.
- [laughs] Sure.
All right.
- What else should I be doing?
- Oh, I don't know.
[sighs] Maybe not standing around
talking to me.
Well, that's what the job is.
Yeah. Well… No.
Why's everyone else gone?
[dial tone]
[dialing]
[line rings]
[operator] 911, what's your emergency?
[Julia breathes shakily] Please.
Someone's in my house.
[operator] Are they in the house now?
[Julia breathes shakily] No.
No, I don't think so.
[operator] Ma'am, how do you know
someone was there? Did you see them?
[Julia] No, I never do,
but he was here. He was here.
[operator] I'll send someone out.
[Julia] It won't matter.
He'll know you're coming.
[line rings]
[Julia] Hello.
[Julia] Stop. Just stop!
I called the police.
[Harper] They'll be there in 18 minutes.
[Julia] They're here now.
[Harper] No, they're not.
[Harper] You see, I'm, uh… I'm already with you when they arrive.
I'm with you every moment. I'm… [Harper] I'm with you through every… Everything that has happened.
Everything that will happen.
I'm with all of you.
[dial tone]
[breathing heavily]
[Kirby] Hey. Hey, Dan.
I heard his voice. It's him.
[Harper] I'm with you every moment. I'm… I'm with you through every… Everything that has happened.
Everything that will happen.
I'm with all of you.
You took this without telling anyone?
It doesn't matter.
You heard what he said, "all of you."
There's more women.
We can't refer to this tape
without the family's permission.
I will go back. I will...
I will go talk to her father.
CPD needs to know.
They obviously didn't look too hard
for exonerating evidence.
- Why did she hide the tape?
- Because she knew he was coming.
And that's all she had time to do.
[Abby] If you need more help on this,
Bertie's already raised his hand.
I'm good with her.
[Abby] And the other victim, your source.
What did you find out about her?
She held up just fine.
[sighs]