[workers chattering in Polish, Swedish]
[chattering continues]
[shouting, laughter]
[rumbling]
Hallå?
Hallå? [speaks Swedish]
[speaks Swedish]
[panting]
[dog growls]
[dog growling]
[growling continues]
Easy.
Where'd you come from?
[breathing heavily]
[growling continues]
See this? Huh? Go get it.
[dog barking, snarling]
He should've been here.
You heard the recording.
When else could it have been?
I don't know. I don't know
what I heard anymore.
What am I supposed to do now?
[breathes heavily]
[Kirby] This is where you live now.
That was my place in grad school.
This... This is where you work.
I'm a "mechanical technician"?
You'll find out when you show up tomorrow.
I can't do that.
You have to. If you do not go home
or you do not go to work, whoever is expecting you, they will call the police.
And when you try to tell them
what happened to you, they will not believe you.
They'll take you to the hospital.
- Did that happen to you?
- [breathes shakily] This is who you are now.
This is who you have to be.
You can do this. I have many times.
[breathes shakily] Where are you going?
[Kirby] It's gonna be okay.
Can I help you?
Is Dan Velazquez here?
[resident] I'm sorry.
I don't know who that is.
He lives here.
He doesn't anymore. Sorry.
How long have you lived here? I'll leave.
Just tell me how long.
A few years.
- Do you get mail?
- Yeah.
No, something from the previous owner.
Letters, bills, anything like that?
No, I didn't keep some random guy's bills.
Is that all?
Yeah.
[elevator bell dings]
[door clatters]
[line rings]
[person on phone] Hello?
Hey. Um, is Rachel there?
[person on phone] Who?
[sniffs, sighs]
Morning, Kirby.
[grunts]
[grunts] Sorry. I was working late,
and I crashed here.
Okay.
[breathes heavily]
[sighs]
[wheels rolling]
[Clarence] No, I don't think...
[speaks indistinctly] What? Yeah, I… [Jack] Kirby.
I know your clips took forever,
but I have them.
I... I promise. The Berwyn robberies. Here.
[sighs] Right. Thank you.
Mind if I take this back?
Of course.
[sighs]
Morning, Kirby.
[Kirby sighs]
- Hey, where's Dan?
- Who?
Um...
Did you contact CPD
about the Klara Meiser police report?
"Meiser"? I don't remember that.
The background on... on Julia Madrigal.
Wait... Uh, "Meiser,"
that's the suspect's name?
I thought it was something else.
Yeah, Pawel Banik.
The DA's expecting
to finalize the plea this week.
The... He's... He's pleading guilty?
[Bertie] He got a good deal.
The police just wanted to close it up.
What about the other women?
[stammers]
Have you heard something else?
- Does Banik have other victims?
- No, it isn't him.
[Bertie] What do you mean?
There... There are other women.
Why... Are we not covering it?
Abby's already in there, guys.
Um. Uh... Whatever lead you have,
you should probably bring it up.
[Bertie] Kirby, you coming?
[sighs]
[Abby]
Jeff, I want you on postgame at Wrigley.
[Jeff] Yeah, I can probably cover both,
depending on traffic.
[Abby] Okay. Yeah, that's better.
And, uh, where are you two
on the flood follow-up?
We're waiting to hear back
from the insurance companies.
It looks like they're gonna
deny the claims.
I've got the rundown
on last night's homicides.
All right. Raise your hand if anyone
wants to jump in on any of these.
"Greg Hunnam, domestic dispute,
North Halsted.
Arthur Morris, gunshot victim
at Booster and Fairfax.
Likely gang-related."
- [Clarence] I'll take that one.
- All right, who's next?
[Abby] "Dan Velazquez"?
[senior reporter] No fucking way. Dan?
- What?
- [senior reporter] What happened?
- [Lakshmi] Who's he?
- Dan used to work here.
[Abby] I brought him over
from The Observer.
Most of you probably don't know him.
Well, that's just wrong.
[senior reporter]
Abby, where did it happen?
Some bar. "Sid's."
No, that's wrong.
[reporter] I've seen shows there.
It's near, uh, Uptown Square.
[Abby] Kirby, are you okay?
Did you know him?
[breathing heavily]
[breathing shakily]
[breathing echoes]
[echoing] Kirby.
Kirby?
You okay?
[blues music playing]
♪ Else… wouldn't have ♪ ♪ Gone so far from me ♪
[song ends]
Harper.
[sniffs]
I picked a good day. You remember me.
What do you mean? I always remember you.
Listen, uh… I need you to talk to me.
Clear. None of the, um,
horseshit about the lights.
Oh, they're always there.
You would talk about them too.
You talk to people about Klara?
Who?
[Harper] You know.
You know who I'm talking about.
Right.
Right, the dancer from the tape?
What about the tape?
I... Uh...
It reminded you too much of Paris.
Is it here?
You give it to them?
- What are you looking for?
- The tape.
The one you took from me.
The one with Klara.
Who?
No, no. Don't start with that.
That's why I came today.
Today is a good day.
I know it is.
What do you want from me?
I don't have your tape.
Yes. Yes, you do. You do.
I know you have it.
And you're gonna give it to someone.
And that's how they find me.
So… I know that you have it.
If I do, I don't know where it is.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
[grunting, panting]
Fucking here.
Okay. Okay, Leo.
Hey, look at me.
Hey.
You just need to remember.
That's all. Just remember.
Then take me back to the house.
I'll be better there.
You know… [chuckles] …you're doing fine here.
You are.
You only need to think for a minute.
Just for a minute.
Where is it? Where's the tape?
Harper? When did you get here?
[inhales deeply, sighs]
What happened?
Dan's dead.
That's why it wasn't you.
I went through everything
I own last night.
You went to that address on the ID?
It's the same place
I lived in grad school.
But now I'm supposed to have dropped out on May 15th, 1986, the day of your assault.
How do you know that?
I went through photos, books, clothes.
It's all the same until that day.
Do you remember
what I told you about particles?
How sometimes they can become entangled, like there's a thread running through them, connecting them?
Now I think there's
three of us on that thread.
How do we get off of it?
Maybe if you remove one of the particles, the rest can break free.
And then what happens?
He might be the one who's connecting us.
So I don't know what'll happen.
I don't wanna feel this way anymore.
So I don't care what happens next.
You remember where you're going?
Uh, I was following you.
- Then why are you ahead of me?
- What do you mean?
Are we close? Huh?
Very close.
Holy shit.
[sighs] They're gone.
Goddamn, Harp. [chuckles]
I can't see the lights.
[Harper] Oh, good.
I don't have to hear about them anymore.
What's all this? You picked up
even more junk, huh?
- How long you been here now?
- I'm not too sure.
Where's the tape? What'd you do with it?
You ever go back?
- Watch any White Sox games?
- [Harper] Where'd you hide the tape?
You already give it to someone?
That's all I want.
Go back, watch Cicotte, Jackson, - you know. - Leo, shut the fuck up!
Where's the tape?
You know me.
You know that I won't tell anyone
about you, about the house.
I don't want anything.
I just want what I had. Take me back.
[Harper] That can't happen,
and you know that.
Still won't work for you.
Never will.
Then you do it. Open the door.
I can't do that.
- Fucking open it!
- [grunts] - I just wanna go home! - Get your hands off.
I just wanna go home. I wanna go home!
Open it! [breathes shakily]
- Open it!
- Or what?
I can hit back. I'm not Klara.
- You piece of shit. [grunting]
- [grunting] Fuck.
[breathing heavily]
When we dumped her, you told me she was gonna tell everyone about the house.
I knew you were lying.
You left the fucking tape.
You didn't think I'd find it?
I thought the house took it.
Things just disappear here.
- Yeah, right in my pocket, you dumb fuck.
- I need it, Leo.
Oh, please.
You want it because you're all over it.
Your voice, your house, Klara.
Someone found you with that tape.
Anybody else could too.
But I don't care about the fucking tape,
okay? You can have it.
We're gonna go back together,
back to the day that we found this place.
Then I will tell you where it is.
I'll tell you.
I don't need to do that.
I can just come back to today, and we can do this all over again, however many times that we need to.
You tried that with Klara.
She saw through you. I will too.
I know why you don't wanna go back.
Because you have nothing there.
There's nothing behind you.
There's nothing ahead of you.
That's why you'll never leave this house.
Because no one wants you anywhere else.
[grunts]
[grunting, gasping]
[gasping]
[panting, grunting]
[gasping continues]
[panting]
[gasping stops]
[elevator bell dings]
The Black Lions fought at Vietnam,
but they could be in earlier wars.
You're sure that's the tattoo
you saw on him?
Can you call any regiment clubs?
See if there are local chapters.
Then we can... Hey.
What?
[Jinny] What?
Everyone's different.
It happened again.
- Just get as many records as you can.
- Okay.
Hey, Kirby. What's up?
Um, can I ask you a random question?
[Marcus chuckles] Always.
- [Kirby] You served in Vietnam, right?
- Yeah, that's right.
The 28th Regiment,
do you know who they are?
Yeah, of course. They're a big deal.
Would they have fought any earlier?
In Korea or maybe even World War I?
[Marcus] Maybe. They're a legacy regiment.
Would the VA have names of
any locals who fought there?
Not from World War I.
VA's only been around since the '30s.
But I can ask the Legion for some records.
It'll take 'em a few days
to get back to me. How come?
I can't wait that long. [sighs]
Mmm.
Your wife, uh... How's she doing?
Oh, Vicky. She's great.
She's great.
What is that? [breathes shakily]
When did you take these?
I didn't. You pulled these for me.
They're from the Dan Velazquez
byline negatives.
For the piece on his murder?
Am I covering it?
No, no. You just pulled them from storage.
Because I work in the archives.
[Marcus] Yeah.
Clarence is on this.
He probably needs your help
tracking down Dan's articles.
[breathing heavily]
Hey. Can I help you?
I'm fine, thanks.
Great. What are you doing at my desk?
Uh, Kirby told me to wait here.
The archivist?
Why would she tell you to sit here?
Because, um… It's okay. I was going.
Who are you?
I'm a… m-mechanical technician.
For the building?
Those are for the article
on Dan Velazquez?
Uh, yeah,
I'm trying to pull any highlights.
Abby said his best stuff was
from the early '80s, but I'm not that far back yet.
Are you covering what happened to him?
I... I guess. There's not much to throw in.
What about the police report?
There any leads?
It was light. [sighs]
Maybe a... a theft, a drug deal gone bad.
Medical examiner's report isn't out yet.
[sighs] Did the police see who robbed him?
No, uh... He was the one stealing.
[sighs] Yeah, he'd been doing shitty
for a while.
Whoever he was robbing had a knife,
and… [chuckles] …that was that.
The police tell you that?
Dan had some other guy's stuff on him.
Why would Kirby leave you here?
Like I said, I was going. [sighs]
Are you stealing that off my desk?
No, this is Kirby's.
- You need to go now.
- What's going on?
- Don't touch me.
- Careful. Come with us, okay?
- When did you get here?
- [officer] Is there anybody we can call?
Someone who can take you home?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean you don't know?
[sighs]
- All right, we gotta go.
- Please, please.
- Ma'am, it's okay.
- Please listen to me. I'm waiting here.
- Okay.
- She's coming back, - and I'm waiting for her. Please. - We'll find her.
All right, thank you.
- What happened?
- A woman came in off the street.
Police had to get her out.
Jinny?
- [Marcus] Don't know. Do you know her?
- [sighs] Yeah, I told her she could be here.
Okay, and who are you?
[scoffs]
Iris?
Oh, hi there. How can I help you?
Who sent you over?
I came about Dan.
I worked with him at the Sun-Times.
He had a good run there.
He hasn't been there for a while though.
I'm actually not there anymore either.
So, why are you here?
I'm not usually a stop on the tour.
I wanted to see him.
No, you don't.
Not like this.
And they couldn't find
anyone else to ID him.
Good news was I could do it myself.
That was a first for me. [sighs]
He was cut, right?
Like this?
How do you know that?
'Cause I know who killed him.
[Iris] Then you really should
tell the police.
I have.
They won't listen.
They said he stole something,
and I need to know what that was.
Well, if you're working at press,
then I'm sure you're gonna get your hands on my report as soon as it's released.
Do you think he would steal, Iris?
That's what the police are saying.
That Dan… was a thief.
But he never kept anything for himself.
He told other people's stories. [chuckles]
Everything he took, he passed on.
And whatever he has, he took it for me.
You sound very sincere.
I'm gonna get a cup a coffee.
You want one?
- No.
- [Iris] Okay, then.
Oh... Be careful over there.
See you in a minute.
- Hey. Did you get everything you need?
- Yeah. Thanks, Howard.
[rumbling]
[Klara] Know how to work that thing?
[Harper] Getting there.
[Klara] How'd you swipe it?
[Harper] I paid for it. You don't have
to steal when you have money.
[Harper] All right, get going.
[Klara speaks French]
[Harper] No, not like that.
Like at Teenie's. Just be you.
- No French.
- [glass shatters] [Klara] Why? It remind you too much of Paris?
- [Harper] Yeah, maybe.
- [grunts]
[groans, shouts]
[grunting]
[grunting, panting]
- [grunts]
- [glass shatters]
[grunts]
- [chokes]
- [Harper grunts]
[both grunting]
[panting]
[grunts, shouts]
[both grunting]
It was never you.
It's this house.
[both grunting]
That's right. It's my fucking house.
[Kirby chokes]
[breathes heavily]
[groans]
[audience applauding]
[speaking French]
Merci, Chicago, et bonne nuit!
[jazz music playing]
You shouldn't be here, Harper.
Well, that's not much of a hello.
It's been two years.
Thought you'd be happy I'm still alive.
What are you, uh...
What are you so mad about?
I'm not mad. [chuckles]
I don't think about you at all.
Sure you do.
What about the letters I wrote you?
You get those?
No, I didn't get any letters.
Oh.
- I mean, I can tell you what they said...
- I don't care really.
I have something for you.
[sighs]
[scoffs] What? [chuckles]
You've... You've stopped liking presents?
- [Klara] I brought this back for you.
- I brought this back for you.
It got caught on your pocketknife, right?
And you sewed it.
Uh...
[chuckles] H... How'd you know that?
- [chuckles] Uh, it's from Paris.
- It's from Paris.
Only you've never actually been there,
have you?
How are you doing this?
[drawer closes]
[door opens, closes]
[watch beeping]
[beeping continues]
[beeping rapidly]
[chuckles]
[beeping stops]
[Leo] Legion. Support your local Legion.
Legion. Support your local Legion.
- Support your local Legion.
- [passerby] No, thank you.
- [Leo] Is this it?
- I guess.
[lock clicking]
- [Harper] You know what you're doing?
- [Leo] Uh-huh.
[Harper] Could be someone home.
[Leo] There's... There's an inch of dust
on the shutters.
No one's here.
[Leo] Whose house is this anyways?
[speaks indistinctly]
[Leo] There's three sets of silver here.
How many people live in this place?
[objects clattering]
- [gunshot]
- [grunts, screams] - Jesus! Harp? - [groaning] Whoa. Whoa, whoa. Easy... Easy, ma'am.
Get out.
[Harper groaning]
[gun cocks]
- Leo!
- [Kirby] Stay down.
Please. [panting]
- I thought nobody was here.
- You don't care who's here.
No, I swear I would...
I wouldn't have hurt you. I wouldn't.
Because I have a gun,
and you're on the ground.
If you just let me go, I can go right now.
I'll just walk out the door. I'll just
walk out the door right now, please.
And you won't come back?
[Harper] No, never.
You'll never see my face again. I promise.
You can't not be who you are.
Second son of a German mother.
When she died, no one wanted you.
Not even the nuns.
And they'll take anyone.
At least that's what you tell yourself
in your head.
[breathing shakily]
And it makes you think
that the world owes you.
And that you can take whatever you want
from whoever there is.
But this is mine.
This is my house.
[Harper stammers]
How are you doing this?
- I don't know you. I don't...
- No.
[Harper breathing heavily]
Not today.
But I am always with you.
Get out, or I'll kill you.
I've done it before.
[grunting, panting]
[grunts]
[door closes]
[panting]
You hurt? Hey, what happened?
What happened?
- I don't know.
- Huh?
Where'd you go, huh?
- [Leo] Hey. Hey, hey.
- [grunts] [groans] No, don't touch it. Don't touch it.
[breathes sharply]
Leo, what's going... What's going on?
Why am I dressed like this?
What? You got clothes on.
No, no. My... My uniform. I...
I wa... I was wearing my uniform.
What uniform?
What do you mean?
My... My uniform. Our uniform.
The same one that you're wearing.
- Where would you get a uniform?
- What are you talking about?
From when we were in France.
The f... The uniform that you're wearing.
When we fought together.
- We first got talking at Saint Adalbert's.
- No. [sighs]
You never made it over to fight.
Stop messing around, okay?
I was there.
We both were.
We fought together.
No, we didn't.
[sighs] Yeah, yeah.
Right.
So, what did you, uh...
What did you get in there?
What?
Inside. What'd you get?
I don't know. It's just a... some horse.
It's not a horse. It's a Pegasus.
Horses don't have wings.
It's just wood. It won't be worth much.
[Julia] Hey, Dad. Good to see you.
[chattering]
[Jinny] These may look
like any other stars, but they don't belong here.
Billions of years ago,
we collided with another galaxy.
And these few stars,
they're all that's left of it.
And now, all we can ask is,
what comes next?
[Latin music playing]
Hey.
How are you?
If you're trying to get me
to buy you a drink, you've already missed the last call.
All right.
Then give me yours.
If I can guess what's in your pocket,
you have to hand it over.
I don't have any cash, and this is fake.
It's fine. I just want your drink.
[clears throat]
Go for it.
Your jacket pocket, the inner one,
you carry a notebook.
It's about this size.
Have I interviewed you before?
Nope.
What do you write in here?
Whatever people tell me.
[chuckles] Those are my notes.
I'll be quick.
You're very strange.
You sure I never interviewed you before?
You tell me.
I know you.
From where?
[sighs]
[chuckles softly]
If you ever remember,
you know where to find me.
[door clatters]
[door continues clattering]
[Kirby] Grendel.
[dog whimpers]
["One Too Many Mornings" playing]